{"id": 2502, "data": "wwwwe mmmmuch timmmme little wwwwith thats wwwwhat commmmes wwwwith mmmmidcaste anything commmmplain lot people things wwwworse Oh boy depressed", "label": [[135, 144, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2503, "data": "@slycbiskut way much rain here gettin colder nothing like guys get", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"], [26, 30, "B-LOC"], [38, 44, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2504, "data": "I care anyone says suicide stupid response possible crisis There always another way rather killing yourself Suicide cowards way it okay", "label": [[2, 6, "B-EVENT"], [19, 26, "B-EVENT"], [52, 58, "B-EVENT"], [91, 98, "B-EVENT"], [99, 107, "I-EVENT"], [108, 115, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2505, "data": "Dude really grab suicide kill us both", "label": [[17, 24, "B-EVENT"], [25, 29, "B-EVENT"], [30, 32, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2506, "data": "@LeahSottile consideration Glenn Jones commit suicide killed Bundyville", "label": [[0, 12, "B-PERSON"], [27, 32, "B-PERSON"], [33, 38, "I-PERSON"], [39, 45, "B-EVENT"], [46, 53, "I-EVENT"], [61, 71, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2507, "data": "Malad RailwayStation ke bridge par chard ek yuvak ne di suicide karne ki dhamki Usse bridge se utarkar le gaye wo wapas bridge par chard ke suicide karne ki dhamki dene laga Moke par RPF GRP Police mojud Yuvak ko lagatar utrane samjhane ki koshish jari pictwittercomBDCaG1tWWT", "label": [[6, 20, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2508, "data": "How depressed Hes successful streamer", "label": [[4, 13, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2509, "data": "like im selfindulgent mood bc im actually cranky losing personal files lmao question whether depressed like wanna know kiss challenges arerin short ficdrabble style", "label": [[8, 21, "B-EVENT"], [22, 26, "I-EVENT"], [42, 48, "B-EVENT"], [93, 102, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2510, "data": "At least 200 civilians killed another 400 received injuries suicide bombings battles military operations past one month across Afghanistan said Civilian Protection Advocacy Group Afghanistan CPAG", "label": [[23, 29, "B-EVENT"], [60, 67, "B-EVENT"], [68, 76, "I-EVENT"], [94, 104, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2511, "data": "Bit depressed humans could stoop low thats reality tbh", "label": [[4, 13, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2512, "data": "im depressed student rn school", "label": [[3, 12, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2513, "data": "Koe Katachi hit really close home me suicide mix along alone trouble fitting making friends moved got crying end An emotional rollercoaster ride would go enjoy every second of", "label": [[4, 11, "B-PERSON"], [37, 44, "B-EVENT"], [102, 108, "B-EVENT"], [154, 159, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2514, "data": "Dazai name Suicide game", "label": [[11, 18, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2515, "data": "Lenvie de suicide est imminente", "label": [[10, 17, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2516, "data": "And ass still depressed Grimes claims removed part eyeball cure seasonal depression", "label": [[14, 23, "B-EVENT"], [24, 30, "B-PERSON"], [73, 83, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2517, "data": "if I die die kinda mood", "label": [[5, 8, "B-EVENT"], [9, 12, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2518, "data": "@GreninjaGirl666 Mine bothGoes depression", "label": [[0, 16, "B-PERSON"], [31, 41, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2519, "data": "Damn trying stop Ellie committing toddler suicide 247 really leaves needing nap", "label": [[17, 22, "B-PERSON"], [42, 49, "B-EVENT"], [76, 79, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2520, "data": "@olivosartstudio Oh I things similar time Thanks giving name I researching now", "label": [[0, 16, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2521, "data": "LatestNews Consumer Credit Counseling Service 888 5511270 Kate Spade found dead NYC home leaves heartbreaking suicide note telling daughter its fault pictwittercomAjt6t1pmKC", "label": [[58, 62, "B-PERSON"], [63, 68, "I-PERSON"], [110, 117, "B-EVENT"], [80, 83, "B-LOC"], [84, 88, "I-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2522, "data": "suicide joke depression joke mental illness joke QUIT FAKING SUICIDES FOR CLOUT NOTICES ATTENTION ETC shit okay people actually struggle suicidal thoughts etc taken seriously bc shitty ass people FAKING SUICIDES", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"], [13, 23, "B-EVENT"], [29, 35, "B-EVENT"], [36, 43, "I-EVENT"], [61, 69, "B-EVENT"], [137, 145, "B-EVENT"], [146, 154, "I-EVENT"], [203, 211, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2523, "data": "Please dont put Im depressed lol I honestly dont even know Im gonna able go I basically want curl ball die lol happy though", "label": [[19, 28, "B-EVENT"], [103, 106, "B-EVENT"], [111, 116, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2524, "data": "@paulissima real life offline worry Happy", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"], [30, 35, "B-EVENT"], [36, 41, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2525, "data": "And inherent contradictions Your Philosophy go us depressed wages United States buy less items For instance Housing Costs way higher Our Budgets previous generations", "label": [[50, 59, "B-EVENT"], [66, 72, "B-LOC"], [73, 79, "I-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2527, "data": "depression real", "label": [[0, 10, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2528, "data": "Broke Im depressed Woke I havin Big Sad bitch", "label": [[9, 18, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2529, "data": "Maharashtra Yavatmal jilheke suicide Pariwar k liye MORAL Support k udbodhan PL", "label": [[0, 11, "B-LOC"], [29, 36, "B-EVENT"], [52, 57, "B-EVENT"], [58, 65, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2530, "data": "Whenever I feel depressed I cheer thinking unbelievably raggedy mama broke confessed got wooden legs real feet mic drop", "label": [[16, 25, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2531, "data": "I feel sis Attempting suicide every time face problem sick", "label": [[22, 29, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2532, "data": "walang kwenta pagsearch ko puro suicide hotlines ano gagawin ko dyan eh di naman yan hinahanap ko", "label": [[32, 39, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2533, "data": "Committing suicide admitting I neither like beyonc zendaya", "label": [[0, 10, "B-EVENT"], [11, 18, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2534, "data": "c faux le truc de tokyo suicide gngn", "label": [[24, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2535, "data": "2 years ago Chester Bennington committed suicide Just days seen smiling family Check mates regardless gender Havent heard while let know care God knows goes long long fucking way", "label": [[12, 19, "B-PERSON"], [20, 30, "I-PERSON"], [31, 40, "B-EVENT"], [41, 48, "I-EVENT"], [64, 71, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2536, "data": "Its fun duo que Solo que puts suicide watch", "label": [[30, 37, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2537, "data": "Im 8 3040 Im depressed", "label": [[13, 22, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2538, "data": "Imagine youre 5th grade Enjoying last days school Watching recess kids play tetherballkickball fourSquare like You relax shade best friends talking fun youll summer Now youre depressed high schooler", "label": [[24, 32, "B-EVENT"], [175, 184, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2539, "data": "If people see someone depressed get help might inspire well During Metoo movement many started share stories seeing many woman power media share theirs", "label": [[22, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2540, "data": "day553 dairycremecorner delicious beattheheat heatwave staycool fact 14 22 Veterans complete suicide everyday US Not receiving recent care local VA Get Veteran friends", "label": [[93, 100, "B-EVENT"], [110, 112, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2541, "data": "What issues world Everyone depressed makes slightly depressed", "label": [[27, 36, "B-EVENT"], [52, 61, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2542, "data": "Just like someone look good depressed also look good dealing anxiety You dont know panic attack leaving house Here signs someone anxiety High Functioning Anxiety via @YouTube", "label": [[28, 37, "B-EVENT"], [61, 68, "B-EVENT"], [83, 88, "B-EVENT"], [89, 95, "I-EVENT"], [104, 109, "B-LOC"], [129, 136, "B-EVENT"], [154, 161, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2545, "data": "I Fake Suicide I came closest Ive ever killing I care attention exact reason I ignored everything I realised I idiotic dumb I deleted everything", "label": [[2, 6, "B-EVENT"], [7, 14, "I-EVENT"], [39, 46, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2546, "data": "sun depressed", "label": [[4, 13, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2547, "data": "ok ur depressed u tried removing ur eyeballs", "label": [[6, 15, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2548, "data": "@Top10Causes", "label": [[0, 12, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2549, "data": "Why hell would this Unless suicide", "label": [[27, 34, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2551, "data": "@btsbighit thank thing kept going last 6 months I contemplated suicide much throughout time guys helped anyone else ever has I love guys Thank", "label": [[0, 10, "B-PERSON"], [50, 62, "B-EVENT"], [63, 70, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2552, "data": "Ye @TheArijitSingh k songs sad mood sunlo suicide k khayal lag jaty yar His voice terebinabnalengyikbhedam", "label": [[3, 18, "B-PERSON"], [42, 49, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2553, "data": "Father girl killed murdersuicide talks daughter wife pictwittercomAiU5HFTDD3", "label": [[12, 18, "B-EVENT"], [19, 25, "B-EVENT"], [25, 32, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2554, "data": "Good points Im sure Revathe pass onact these But seems lack emergency response sorts In MIT whenever suicide students encouraged go talk counsellors especially close deceased", "label": [[101, 108, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2555, "data": "@TiffCollegHill6 umm u click says following someones photo", "label": [[0, 16, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2556, "data": "Baba wan make person commit suicide abi", "label": [[21, 27, "B-EVENT"], [28, 35, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2557, "data": "We disagree And ok kinda cute Not depressed sad old hurting negative lonely sad Ill still f kinda cute But ok", "label": [[34, 43, "B-EVENT"], [44, 47, "B-EVENT"], [52, 59, "B-EVENT"], [60, 68, "B-EVENT"], [69, 75, "B-EVENT"], [76, 79, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2560, "data": "Had dream I getting locked mom threw nutr bullet I got I depressed bc reason guard ex mine like bruh wtfff u lookin cute bae", "label": [[57, 66, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2562, "data": "maga Carla n eve rn making depressed two weeks hurry fuck I", "label": [[27, 36, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2563, "data": "Medical Student Found Hanging In Hostel Room In Rajasthans Bikaner Medical Student Found Hanging In Hostel Room In Rajasthans Bikaner A medical student allegedly committed suicide hanging hostel room police said Saturday pictwittercom4x8BqjxjIq", "label": [[22, 29, "B-EVENT"], [33, 39, "B-LOC"], [40, 44, "I-LOC"], [48, 58, "B-LOC"], [59, 66, "B-LOC"], [115, 125, "B-LOC"], [126, 133, "B-LOC"], [89, 96, "B-EVENT"], [100, 106, "B-LOC"], [106, 111, "I-LOC"], [162, 171, "B-EVENT"], [172, 179, "I-EVENT"], [180, 187, "B-EVENT"], [187, 194, "B-LOC"], [195, 199, "I-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2564, "data": "CW suicide attempt folks cruel mentally ill", "label": [[3, 10, "B-EVENT"], [31, 39, "B-EVENT"], [40, 43, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2565, "data": "Aint niggas used never past face pics always tweet emo depressed stuff", "label": [[55, 64, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2567, "data": "Im already depressed long contract them desperate Adidas come save us I buy kit", "label": [[11, 20, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2570, "data": "ICYMI If Youve Ever Wondered How Suicide Prevention Text Line Works", "label": [[33, 40, "B-EVENT"], [41, 51, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2571, "data": "Craig lost brother Gavin suicide almost two years ago wants make sure one else feels way Gavin did Craig challenged paddle Avon Descent raise money @zero2heroAU Donate itsmycause charity love pictwittercom79EMNw1Y5N", "label": [[0, 5, "B-PERSON"], [19, 24, "B-PERSON"], [25, 32, "B-EVENT"], [89, 94, "B-PERSON"], [99, 104, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2572, "data": "book its based on dont know things transferred film sure movie ie stans suicide", "label": [[72, 79, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2573, "data": "Many people taken mental health break lives whether stress anxiety depression Only truly SICKinthehead individuals would use mental health break them agree opinion", "label": [[18, 24, "B-EVENT"], [25, 31, "I-EVENT"], [52, 58, "B-EVENT"], [59, 66, "B-EVENT"], [67, 77, "B-EVENT"], [125, 131, "B-EVENT"], [132, 138, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2574, "data": "Commercial Suicide Via Twitter", "label": [[11, 18, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2576, "data": "im depressed", "label": [[3, 12, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2577, "data": "We homeless veterans also veterans committing suicide high numbers budget cuts lack support find another 30B white elephant HS2", "label": [[35, 45, "B-EVENT"], [46, 53, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2578, "data": "@rawdawgbuffalo sound good big bro Save everything thats NOT pork beef", "label": [[0, 15, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2579, "data": "Joker upon time Hollywood Batman Suicide Squad Birds Prey Top Gun Dune Jumanji 2 WW 1984", "label": [[16, 25, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2581, "data": "Depressed Sila Dark DP Ako Primitive boy", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2582, "data": "Moms depression tied kids emotional intellectual development", "label": [[5, 15, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2583, "data": "Netflix cuts suicide scene 13 Reasons Why KPRC2 pictwittercom6KqgmTSWok", "label": [[13, 20, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2584, "data": "Im sorry im depressed cats missing", "label": [[12, 21, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2589, "data": "@readingsarah Oooh Pictures please", "label": [[0, 13, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2590, "data": "bitch feel depressedrude", "label": [[11, 20, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2591, "data": "Udh sangat hopeless Suicide biar gak ngerasain sakit", "label": [[20, 27, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2592, "data": "Depressed hours bitches", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2593, "data": "I want suicide", "label": [[7, 14, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2594, "data": "I capability joke suicide attempt I healed trauma comedy I cope You right make joke someone elses trauma That makes asshole", "label": [[18, 25, "B-EVENT"], [26, 33, "I-EVENT"], [43, 49, "B-EVENT"], [98, 104, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2595, "data": "@TomBelshaw You WelcomeCheers", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2596, "data": "I learned mom dads cousins son committed suicide My mom getting shame kid around brothers age dads family fucking awful confronting feelings hiding them", "label": [[31, 40, "B-EVENT"], [41, 48, "I-EVENT"], [120, 131, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2599, "data": "Tonto never food house workers always depressed Blessing Osom shares shocking details pictwittercomXdH7nEo6Zr", "label": [[38, 47, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2600, "data": "Depressed happy care", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"], [10, 15, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2601, "data": "Do ever feel depressed finishing game really really loved enjoyed When happens usually sit ass feel like shit cant even watch anime finishing judgment", "label": [[13, 22, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2602, "data": "I dont know Allen West coined term I think its best along Jihad Squad Suicide Squad So shout Allen West", "label": [[12, 17, "B-PERSON"], [18, 22, "I-PERSON"], [70, 77, "B-EVENT"], [93, 98, "B-PERSON"], [99, 103, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2604, "data": "Word People mad withering decaying", "label": [[16, 25, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2605, "data": "Oui alors je pensais quil tait en taule mais ma expliqu quil sest suicid", "label": [[66, 72, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2606, "data": "Its sad realize depression true friend", "label": [[16, 26, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2607, "data": "How know Elon would allow anyone buy into supercharger network IMO suicide Tesla so uncontroversial advantage left eroded CCS chargers", "label": [[9, 13, "B-PERSON"], [67, 74, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2608, "data": "At low point everything seems meaningless Look unto God give helping hand Dont loss hope God mighty power give meaning life suicide option Tomorrow get belle", "label": [[30, 41, "B-EVENT"], [124, 131, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2609, "data": "@Cube Rebecca ignored making desert", "label": [[0, 13, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2610, "data": "Suicide west", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2611, "data": "OMFG I downloaded app I straight look like grandpa NOW IM DEPRESSED", "label": [[58, 67, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2612, "data": "mag pa opaw ko bi para ingnon depressed", "label": [[30, 39, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2613, "data": "I wonder hair long enough commit suicide with enkibot", "label": [[26, 32, "B-EVENT"], [33, 40, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2615, "data": "@patrickthepoet How offend us We love you", "label": [[0, 15, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2616, "data": "I home work drinking coffee", "label": [[2, 6, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2619, "data": "@WWisewolf What oversight realise I following you Am though Great blog post integrity", "label": [[0, 10, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2620, "data": "But hes Suicide Squad though", "label": [[8, 15, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2623, "data": "The world never forget horrible tragedy done name islam kill many Americans possible Done suicide terrorists even value lives", "label": [[56, 60, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2624, "data": "@tooshort55 LOL WTHwas I wonder That funny They silly", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2625, "data": "Year YOUTH ngayon pero bakit maraming cases ng suicide sa mga Youth So sad STOPSUICIDE YEAROFTHEYOUTH", "label": [[47, 54, "B-EVENT"], [79, 86, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2626, "data": "Its exhausting like millennials depressed bc its hard build ur friends u also feel like trash bag", "label": [[32, 41, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2627, "data": "MyGuruMyPride Saint Ram Rahim Ji The fast competitive world led large number depressed people In times Ture method meditation given Saint Dr @Gurmeetramrahim Singh Ji Insan helps live stress free healthy life pictwittercomtsEJsMO7oQ", "label": [[20, 23, "B-PERSON"], [24, 29, "I-PERSON"], [77, 86, "B-EVENT"], [141, 157, "B-PERSON"], [158, 163, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2628, "data": "Female suicide bomber kills eight northwest Pakistan Daily Mail Online", "label": [[7, 14, "B-EVENT"], [22, 27, "B-EVENT"], [44, 52, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2629, "data": "Small budget niche nonholiday rls Super30 fck 95 haklas career lifetime Tum bakre log ikatta hoke mass suicide kar lo", "label": [[103, 110, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2630, "data": "Describe ur life poll polls onlinepoll TwitterKapamilyaPoll TwitterPoll twitterpoll survey boring sadlife suicide Sad", "label": [[106, 113, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2631, "data": "orangtua harus belajar dari pengalaman orangtua gak tau kalau menurut mereka ah cuman hal sepele tapi menurut kami itu salah satu pemicu stress sampai ngebatin dan bisa berujung suicide sih", "label": [[137, 143, "B-EVENT"], [178, 185, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2632, "data": "No main reason Brexiteers didnt plan And cant expect 60m people pulling together 174m misleads people voted economic suicide", "label": [[117, 124, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2633, "data": "Accuser got call Hillarys hitmen office talked suicide children", "label": [[47, 54, "B-EVENT"], [17, 25, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2634, "data": "Exercising regularly cuts risk depression 16 study suggests def worth read pictwittercomOT9aYkfht3", "label": [[31, 41, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2635, "data": "Heyo putting there think its okay treat others like garbage try excuse saying issues youre depressed dont act surprised person pestered much blocks you Friends like arent real friends", "label": [[91, 100, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2636, "data": "@2jacksandastaff hahaha Dont worry certainly wont", "label": [[0, 16, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2637, "data": "@DeionSanders I changed life help football saved depression almost suicide But today continue help others", "label": [[0, 13, "B-PERSON"], [49, 59, "B-EVENT"], [67, 74, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2638, "data": "time last week I best time dancing parting drinking friends Im bed sad depressed", "label": [[71, 80, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2639, "data": "seriously tired everyone posting faceapp pictures How old you 2", "label": [[10, 15, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2640, "data": "@Sprite3 Ha sounds like another crazy great plan xo", "label": [[0, 8, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2641, "data": "@TheJASHJAY As someone thats suffered depression years affect beliefs personality etc expressly said one cant assume shit means saying", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"], [38, 48, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2642, "data": "Dawg depressed hearing sauce instant mood changer", "label": [[5, 14, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2644, "data": "Over course year 5821 people died suicide UK Office National Statistics 2018 Thats nearly 16 people EVERY day Learn free lifesaving skills online now Takes 20 minutes pictwittercomZ2kwHQTAwr", "label": [[34, 41, "B-EVENT"], [42, 44, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2646, "data": "okay im narcissist", "label": [[8, 18, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2647, "data": "Suicide never answer kids", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2648, "data": "depressed sad T H I C C", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2649, "data": "If youre depressed stressed clap hands", "label": [[9, 18, "B-EVENT"], [19, 27, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2650, "data": "tbh aion wanna think results tomorrow fail ill extend studies relapse back depressed bullshit fuck la lulus alhamdulillah gagal plan everything again nak mati mf grind ig", "label": [[38, 42, "B-EVENT"], [75, 84, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2651, "data": "know reach goals achieve fucking much b depressed man", "label": [[40, 49, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2652, "data": "Suicide see tear fall eye", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2653, "data": "Not true studies shown even low skilled workers still depress wages Highly skilled immigrants innovate start businesses higher rate native born populations leads higher quality life higher wages", "label": [[54, 61, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2654, "data": "So much suicide prevention thing use this Does also count billboard Or signs", "label": [[8, 15, "B-EVENT"], [16, 26, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2655, "data": "Syria The American al Qaeda suicide bomber Opinion", "label": [[0, 5, "B-LOC"], [10, 18, "B-LOC"], [28, 35, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2656, "data": "Lmaooooo yes That I aint gonn like college thats gross mindset lil rn All chikas grown ups abt college life become well But fun still fun Cheers college Where feel depressed get wild atst", "label": [[164, 173, "B-EVENT"], [35, 42, "B-LOC"], [95, 102, "B-LOC"], [145, 152, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2657, "data": "How sad We soldier leave Afghanistan committed suicide rather return The @USArmy refused send burial detail The American Legion VA vet orgs provided military honors Pretty sick ask me", "label": [[25, 36, "B-LOC"], [37, 46, "B-EVENT"], [47, 54, "I-EVENT"], [73, 80, "B-PERSON"], [112, 120, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2659, "data": "@HonestAbe72 I seen people legally upset not Rightly so passed Ellis Island Have forgot that Have forgot Great Depression Americans jobs fails 2", "label": [[0, 12, "B-LOC"], [35, 40, "B-EVENT"], [63, 68, "B-LOC"], [69, 75, "I-LOC"], [111, 121, "B-EVENT"], [122, 131, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2660, "data": "Me siento como cuando fui suicide commando", "label": [[26, 33, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2661, "data": "Sundays suicide days", "label": [[8, 15, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2663, "data": "Id love tweet day today I work must get done Ill tweet I can God bless everyone tcot", "label": [[3, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2664, "data": "Happy Birthday @PCIGU", "label": [[15, 21, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2665, "data": "A depressed high school 17 year old girl psychiatric medication since 14 indicted manslaughter emotionally supporting text virtual boyfriend Conrad Roy Jr attempted suicide four times prior FreeMichelleCarter ImpeachTheCommonwealth", "label": [[2, 11, "B-EVENT"], [82, 94, "B-EVENT"], [95, 106, "B-EVENT"], [107, 117, "I-EVENT"], [141, 147, "B-PERSON"], [148, 151, "I-PERSON"], [152, 154, "I-PERSON"], [155, 164, "B-EVENT"], [165, 172, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2666, "data": "The solution depressed Norman Reedus @wwwbigbaldhead seriously one best world one contradict pictwittercom1CHSoCHoCO", "label": [[13, 22, "B-EVENT"], [37, 52, "B-PERSON"], [23, 29, "B-PERSON"], [30, 36, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2667, "data": "Going see UP tonight yay I love movie nights boytoy lt3", "label": [[27, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2668, "data": "need comments next part trouble amp im gonna post second part youi comment yall", "label": [[24, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2669, "data": "And hes taking stab kids commit suicide bullying", "label": [[15, 19, "B-EVENT"], [25, 31, "B-EVENT"], [32, 39, "I-EVENT"], [40, 48, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2670, "data": "Camp Wiggi Training YMCA 10am 7pm long day I love camp friends lt3", "label": [[20, 24, "B-LOC"], [45, 49, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2671, "data": "My review Avengers Infinity War1010 epic fight1010 great cinematography1010 bop sound effects1010 great slight comedy1010 best one Marvel1010 watch again prob myb bcs 1010 traumatic 1010 gave temporary depression", "label": [[202, 212, "B-EVENT"], [172, 181, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2672, "data": "yea time suicide doesnt sound bad", "label": [[9, 16, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2673, "data": "Mini Rocky Stanleys couch hopping already", "label": [[5, 10, "B-PERSON"], [11, 19, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2674, "data": "If county assembly passes PunguzaMzigo stuff thats suicide", "label": [[51, 58, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2675, "data": "Lets meet Stratford", "label": [[10, 19, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2676, "data": "Irony @McCreadyForNC job creator NC also founded online store This Land 2014 American craftspeople economically depressed areas struggled market goods broader audience ncpol nc09", "label": [[6, 20, "B-PERSON"], [33, 35, "B-LOC"], [77, 85, "B-LOC"], [112, 121, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2677, "data": "@managingmadrid nacho know better either amount exp cant playing suicide balm across area man already pressure", "label": [[0, 15, "B-PERSON"], [65, 72, "B-EVENT"], [102, 110, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2678, "data": "kmt dis shit ahh depress", "label": [[17, 24, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2679, "data": "What thought process brings people form suicide", "label": [[40, 47, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2680, "data": "Im seriously getting depressed I damn good terrifying", "label": [[21, 30, "B-EVENT"], [43, 53, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2681, "data": "talk about 1 sweetest human 2 psychopath depressed I love death 3 nonexistent 4 selfish problematic 5 UGH THE SWEETEST LIKE UM 6 anxious annoying fuck 7 kayoot I wanna meet drop emoji Ill send questions", "label": [[41, 50, "B-EVENT"], [58, 63, "B-EVENT"], [129, 136, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2682, "data": "TWITTER MYSPACE FACEBOOK UNBLOCKED AT SCHOOL LOVE IT", "label": [[38, 44, "B-LOC"], [45, 49, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2684, "data": "@5lilf", "label": [[0, 6, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2685, "data": "Because thats important thing right When someone commits suicide motivator often feeling worthless But everyone infinitely valuable alive legacy die at least die natural death The PERSON matters TheMagicians", "label": [[49, 56, "B-EVENT"], [57, 64, "I-EVENT"], [89, 98, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2686, "data": "lets depressed together sis", "label": [[5, 14, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2687, "data": "twitter looks like im single taken depressed love heart broken hoe loyal please dont think actually know tweets", "label": [[35, 44, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2688, "data": "depressed", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2689, "data": "passed fourday vacation wonderful went back hometown visited many places childhood memory", "label": [[44, 52, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2690, "data": "@amandabynes hey u kisses argentina", "label": [[0, 12, "B-PERSON"], [26, 35, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2692, "data": "Pakistan Suicide blast trauma hospital center Dera Ismail Khan 3 killed 8 injured Pakistan DeraIsmileKhan Hospital TraumaCentre Blast InternationalNews NedrickNews NationNews HindiNews NewsAlert Terrorism TerroristAttack", "label": [[0, 8, "B-LOC"], [9, 16, "B-EVENT"], [30, 38, "B-LOC"], [82, 90, "B-LOC"], [106, 114, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2693, "data": "Four killed suicide blast DIK hospital two cops martyred attack ARYNews", "label": [[12, 19, "B-EVENT"], [30, 38, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2694, "data": "Saw MidSommar worst possible headspace Great movie goddamn I feel depressed nauseated noooooope", "label": [[66, 75, "B-EVENT"], [76, 85, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2695, "data": "followfriday People I actually know amp talk Twitter @timshady @monkeyonthelam @galliguez @referralweb reply back missed u", "label": [[53, 62, "B-PERSON"], [63, 78, "B-PERSON"], [79, 89, "B-PERSON"], [90, 102, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2696, "data": "Heres theory maybe I get high revision order escape depression", "label": [[52, 62, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2698, "data": "Chloe appears This room", "label": [[0, 5, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2701, "data": "@pameladetlor I kind want one I idea Id get I strong nopain policy life", "label": [[0, 13, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2702, "data": "Japans suicide rate 19 per 100000 US suicide rate 13 per 100000 The US shitload guns Japan virtually none", "label": [[0, 6, "B-LOC"], [7, 14, "B-EVENT"], [34, 36, "B-LOC"], [37, 44, "B-EVENT"], [68, 70, "B-LOC"], [85, 90, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2703, "data": "eemm yess know explain happens actually like im depressed forget simple things days get blurred thought process messed slow impact memory", "label": [[48, 57, "B-EVENT"], [112, 118, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2704, "data": "On Good deep depressed Nice", "label": [[13, 22, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2706, "data": "suicide machinesPOTSHOT2", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2707, "data": "Im sorry that Its great conundrum Wages depressed one afford live Trumpeters say Just leave go somewhere else wbetter jobs With morons Everywhere expensive days anyways", "label": [[40, 49, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2708, "data": "Also 2000 Palestinians bombed Iraq suicide bombers killed thousands Iraqi shias since American invasion 2003 Thats history Iraq withe Palestinians", "label": [[10, 22, "B-LOC"], [30, 34, "B-LOC"], [35, 42, "B-EVENT"], [86, 94, "B-LOC"], [68, 73, "B-LOC"], [123, 127, "B-LOC"], [134, 146, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2709, "data": "Our corn feeling depressed", "label": [[17, 26, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2710, "data": "I reconnected Facebook old friend high school She reacted Robin Williams suicide posting lots memes reaching depressed folks ignoring cries help Not long afterwards unfriended blocked negativity shrug", "label": [[34, 38, "B-LOC"], [39, 45, "I-LOC"], [58, 63, "B-PERSON"], [64, 72, "I-PERSON"], [73, 80, "B-EVENT"], [109, 118, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2712, "data": "DecisionOnAwarInThisVery important partOfTheWorld suicide commitmentYet known powerful didnt feel realities happened started cant stope it The stop war decided IranianThereforeUSA its allies must resolve without", "label": [[50, 57, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2713, "data": "My batch mate NUST EME committed suicide one year desperate unemployment HE IS NO MORE feel that", "label": [[23, 32, "B-EVENT"], [33, 40, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2714, "data": "@RichieAllenShow Alan Turing depicted 50 pound note assassinated rather commit suicide knew much state secrets gay regarded security risk time gay illegal", "label": [[0, 16, "B-PERSON"], [17, 21, "B-PERSON"], [22, 28, "I-PERSON"], [72, 78, "B-EVENT"], [79, 86, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2715, "data": "Un astrode menace de dtruire toute vie sur terre La NASA dcide en ultime recours denvoyer le cur dun petit village de Provence en mission suicide", "label": [[138, 145, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2716, "data": "school hasnt even properly started im already depressed", "label": [[46, 55, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2717, "data": "I wish DC could make live action movies truly showcase best parts characters storylines I fell love with They really need take note well Aquaman Suicide Squad compared live action movies tried", "label": [[145, 152, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2718, "data": "My parents know anything anymore Im never telling Im nonbinary bc I know theyd freak I know theyd cut rest fam And I cant really tell Im depressed bc bullshit", "label": [[137, 146, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2720, "data": "piece art marc bijl stedelijk museum amsterdam its called suicide machine edgy fave piece pictwittercomOZILCyvvn8", "label": [[58, 65, "B-EVENT"], [37, 46, "B-LOC"], [30, 36, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2722, "data": "Illegal immigration diversity its suicide Legal immigration only", "label": [[34, 41, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2723, "data": "That feeling realise problem bigger deeper far reaching thought possible Honestly researching upcoming report AntiSemitism Cant remember feeling low before I thoroughly thoroughly depressed", "label": [[180, 189, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2725, "data": "Man great sense humour Venky Pachad", "label": [[23, 28, "B-PERSON"], [29, 35, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2726, "data": "Jesus commiting suicide", "label": [[16, 23, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2727, "data": "Read last night Andrew T Kaisers book missionaries suicide considered most terrible revenge wonder its true enemies guy pictwittercomq31ob3IbRd", "label": [[16, 22, "B-PERSON"], [23, 24, "I-PERSON"], [25, 32, "I-PERSON"], [51, 58, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2728, "data": "Cumedores de aa com pexe em suicide watch", "label": [[28, 35, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2729, "data": "DEPRESSED IN A VERY LONG TIME MIGHT B DYING STAY TUNED one fish see neck want punched", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"], [38, 43, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2731, "data": "Approximately 22 Veterans day commit suicide Would least 22 Twitter friends please copy tweet Not RT Veterans Crisis Line 8002738255 Thank @TheFaulkLine", "label": [[30, 36, "B-EVENT"], [37, 44, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2732, "data": "found got pushed chair hit head wheelbarrow last night I took beating Thank vodka", "label": [[62, 69, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2733, "data": "Reflecting blessed week beautiful friends inspirational places @SupportUoS @inequilibrium Llandudno Conway Sunderland Deeside ASIST @MHFAEngland @LivingWorks @DawnHardman suicide mentalhealth workplace pictwittercomtBE284xH63", "label": [[63, 74, "B-PERSON"], [75, 89, "B-PERSON"], [132, 144, "B-PERSON"], [145, 157, "B-PERSON"], [158, 170, "B-PERSON"], [171, 178, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2735, "data": "She attempted suicide", "label": [[4, 13, "B-EVENT"], [14, 21, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2736, "data": "@JackAllTimeLow @AlexAllTimeLow Have AWESOME show tonight boys Wish I cldve gone watch u guys again", "label": [[0, 15, "B-PERSON"], [16, 31, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2737, "data": "Story actually brutal working conditions hospitality high rate suicide amongst chefs Shame didnt change cover", "label": [[63, 70, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2738, "data": "I want happy", "label": [[7, 12, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2739, "data": "@MsDanette2u yes I read ur tweets check often I wish I couldve tried ur brownies", "label": [[0, 12, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2740, "data": "The frequency people think Im upbeat outgoing always happy blows mind Today someone said I lighting room I horribly depressed I understand it Im good liar", "label": [[116, 125, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2741, "data": "Inb4 bullied suicide vile allies respecting pronouns", "label": [[5, 12, "B-EVENT"], [13, 20, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2742, "data": "Thinking inconsistent Harleys hair Suicide Squad pictwittercommOVQsKnL5p", "label": [[22, 29, "B-PERSON"], [35, 42, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2744, "data": "Suicide 10th leading cause death United States Saddened say Ive three friendscolleagues commit suicide past three years Whats best way work together save lives", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"], [33, 39, "B-LOC"], [40, 46, "I-LOC"], [47, 55, "B-EVENT"], [88, 94, "B-EVENT"], [95, 102, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2746, "data": "talk perspective I depressed lmao", "label": [[19, 28, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2747, "data": "My depressed ass slept day much mess go grocery store I guess I food one small bag rice eat tomorrow", "label": [[3, 12, "B-EVENT"], [40, 47, "B-LOC"], [48, 53, "I-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2748, "data": "Sitting net cafe boreddddd cant wait internet new home gets workingg I upload CRAZY pics x", "label": [[12, 16, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2749, "data": "problems I multiship Ive ignored 34 people theyre shipped with Most single ships come piss poor excuses theyre never onIm depressed biggest one Thats happened 5 times", "label": [[122, 131, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2750, "data": "@ marynabadenhors Thanks comment Maryna The explore vids great", "label": [[0, 17, "B-PERSON"], [33, 39, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2751, "data": "uh Im depressed I dont even eat", "label": [[6, 15, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2754, "data": "omfg miss much im watching fancam im depressed pictwittercompD2Bz5NmyB", "label": [[37, 46, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2755, "data": "Imagine asking someone open struggle suicide theyre going top themselves Everyday Im reminded disgusting place world", "label": [[37, 44, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2757, "data": "Walking home school I look like loner funny day school today", "label": [[8, 12, "B-LOC"], [13, 19, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2758, "data": "Havent even checked Binance today I want depress myself", "label": [[41, 48, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2759, "data": "Gender dysphoria mental illness military accept people pre Existing conditions We need mentally fit men women serve We already enough problems service members committing suicide dont need increase", "label": [[17, 23, "B-EVENT"], [24, 31, "I-EVENT"], [87, 95, "B-EVENT"], [96, 99, "I-EVENT"], [159, 169, "B-EVENT"], [170, 177, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2761, "data": "@silentinfinite hey abi nice see online", "label": [[0, 15, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2762, "data": "Ive called job something regarding suicide friend you know Im talking about They wrote I took care friend declining mental state", "label": [[35, 42, "B-EVENT"], [116, 122, "B-EVENT"], [123, 128, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2763, "data": "god reverse seasonal depression get worse starts getting warmer", "label": [[21, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2764, "data": "stop depressed jus b happy", "label": [[5, 14, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2765, "data": "Education must separated religionthese future suicide bombers Disgusting mulla ans yes", "label": [[46, 53, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2766, "data": "decided watch night museum made good decision cuz hilarious three cherubs cute", "label": [[20, 26, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2767, "data": "im big depressed need someone hold hand im gonna cuddle bear read au", "label": [[7, 16, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2769, "data": "@pixel8ted Things move quickly Twitterverse YCM quickly became team effort @fridley @Glebe2037", "label": [[0, 10, "B-PERSON"], [75, 83, "B-PERSON"], [84, 94, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2770, "data": "Excuse anything happens anyone women Im wondering could considered accessory That girl bullied poor boy committed suicide going jail Arent least bit worried doing Its right STOP", "label": [[87, 94, "B-EVENT"], [104, 113, "B-EVENT"], [114, 121, "I-EVENT"], [128, 132, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2771, "data": "What happens body feel anxious depressed eft gottmaninstitute love connection anxiety depression feelings healing trauma psychotherapist selfcare", "label": [[23, 30, "B-EVENT"], [31, 40, "B-EVENT"], [78, 85, "B-EVENT"], [86, 96, "B-EVENT"], [114, 120, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2772, "data": "tfw living Europeans good people attempt suicide cant", "label": [[11, 20, "B-LOC"], [33, 40, "B-EVENT"], [41, 48, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2773, "data": "smart would considered headcanons get peoples heads would conversation Neither original thread talking headcanons all Think twice defending suicide baiting", "label": [[140, 147, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2774, "data": "depressed guy credo que chato", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2775, "data": "@priyankachopra committing suicide asthma patient", "label": [[0, 15, "B-PERSON"], [16, 26, "B-EVENT"], [27, 34, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2776, "data": "depressed locals strange", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2777, "data": "They also count someone chosen commit suicide parked school parking lot school shooting These numbers purposely inflated", "label": [[31, 37, "B-EVENT"], [38, 45, "I-EVENT"], [53, 59, "B-LOC"], [79, 87, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2778, "data": "@JoelMadden oh well ill try stay long", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2779, "data": "What happened inter students committed suicide", "label": [[29, 38, "B-EVENT"], [39, 46, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2781, "data": "@kelsol24 You bright confident woman Kelsey fine", "label": [[0, 9, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2782, "data": "Same kidding im depressed two ways", "label": [[16, 25, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2783, "data": "Depressed maybe thot", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2784, "data": "Suicide Or Murder @YouTube", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"], [11, 17, "B-EVENT"], [18, 26, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2785, "data": "Well moment one day I think current future looks bright We heard anything Suicide Squad The Batman WW84 silent The Flash never going get made", "label": [[74, 81, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2787, "data": "@FayetteSO searching 48 year old man slipped away Swat home declaring suicide cop The Sheriff says shot bb gun deflected taze came knives duct taped hands fox5atl @PhotoZornFOX5 pictwittercom3Iz1zavyuc", "label": [[0, 10, "B-PERSON"], [70, 77, "B-EVENT"], [99, 103, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2788, "data": "Suicide Squad 2016", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2789, "data": "Phenomenal twist atrocious saga suicide bombingfemales nothing stop perhaps", "label": [[32, 39, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2790, "data": "Ohh God that Narcissistic behavior", "label": [[13, 25, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2792, "data": "suicide", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2793, "data": "Pakistan 11 persons incl 4 policemen killed attack involving least one female suicide bomber DI Khan district KPK province", "label": [[0, 8, "B-LOC"], [37, 43, "B-EVENT"], [78, 85, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2795, "data": "@TSMMyth @Dehgo Its depression Its accepted cuz everyone likes feeling gives you", "label": [[0, 8, "B-PERSON"], [9, 15, "B-PERSON"], [20, 30, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2796, "data": "And think Im looking forward coming dc movies especially joker one yes Ill watch Janes Gunns suicide squad", "label": [[93, 100, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2797, "data": "sah tokyo qui bute le professeur et qui se suicide aprs wtf", "label": [[43, 50, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2798, "data": "play suicide pimpin man", "label": [[5, 12, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2799, "data": "a country unborn daughter go vinder Do tell suicide Beat troubles bell", "label": [[44, 51, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2800, "data": "SOCALLED suicide influence incredibly potent toxic MEDICALdrugs warning extent dangers unbelievable indescribable reality alterations making IATROGENIC HOMICIDE You check God KNOWS", "label": [[9, 16, "B-EVENT"], [152, 160, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2801, "data": "Reality show allegation kosam kuda udyamam chestunnara Can front Ramoji house airing Adult comedy show like Jabardast OU students r loosing respect got Telangana movement Where u wen inter students committed suicide", "label": [[198, 207, "B-EVENT"], [208, 215, "I-EVENT"], [152, 161, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2802, "data": "As men top rate death suicide Man Brain campaign focuses mens mentalhealth WLUK", "label": [[16, 21, "B-EVENT"], [22, 29, "B-EVENT"], [62, 74, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2803, "data": "depressed everything cant help stopping water coming eyes whenever Im alone", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2804, "data": "Stream 630PM MST Been getting late tbh depressed Hope see there", "label": [[39, 48, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2805, "data": "id hoeing around much that im depresoeing hoeing depressedlike feel empty inside though got cum literally dripping type thing know", "label": [[49, 58, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2806, "data": "PS China Billionares far nice research The U S falling behind every sector satisfaction quality life education Highest suicide numbers years constant racial division rampant police brutality Jeffrey Epstein Your country sucks", "label": [[43, 46, "B-LOC"], [3, 8, "B-LOC"], [119, 126, "B-EVENT"], [181, 190, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2808, "data": "The ideology suicide bombs mass shooting nothing islam nothing christianity There mass shootings per year US alone islamic extremist attacks whole world", "label": [[13, 20, "B-EVENT"], [32, 40, "B-EVENT"], [106, 108, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2809, "data": "ohh I money she takes poppys wallet", "label": [[22, 28, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2811, "data": "Shocking sad The leader ThreeSelf Church official church approved Chinese government committed suicide July 16 He writes under state controlthe church like church like club like company Im exhausted", "label": [[66, 73, "B-LOC"], [85, 94, "B-EVENT"], [95, 102, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2812, "data": "Oof Sorry struggling I insomnia top chaotic sleep schedule doesnt help ive bed ridden thanks feeling depressed since thursday", "label": [[10, 20, "B-EVENT"], [36, 43, "B-EVENT"], [101, 110, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2813, "data": "Self love gay", "label": [[5, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2814, "data": "hey twitter im back n depressed", "label": [[22, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2815, "data": "We tweeted similar things time guess were depressed", "label": [[42, 51, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2816, "data": "Like much shit happened last month Im really depressed like Im losing people I try doesnt go anywhere like idk anymore cause Im starting lose people Im scared cause its outta control", "label": [[45, 54, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2817, "data": "@NotAPretender Ive even watched episode clips humanfails", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2818, "data": "Le Tokyo se suicide avant de tuer le professejr", "label": [[12, 19, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2819, "data": "todo el dia hablando de naruto vos queres q suicide", "label": [[44, 51, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2820, "data": "They Party Open Borders bc enough sane Americans vote them Will recent expected voter fraud actions D party provide support VOTER ID LAW VOTER ID LAW DEATH OF D PARTY Boomerang Suicide Q Cant come soon", "label": [[39, 48, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2821, "data": "Female Suicide Bomber Kills Six In Pakistan", "label": [[7, 14, "B-EVENT"], [35, 43, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2822, "data": "@Hades u score LMFAOOOO", "label": [[0, 6, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2823, "data": "There arguments atheism like arguments suicide soul", "label": [[39, 46, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2824, "data": "MLK 1958 In present crisis America achieve either racial justice ultimate social psychosis lead domestic suicidethis crisis potential democracys fulfillment fascisms triumph @HouseJudiciary Freedom", "label": [[27, 34, "B-LOC"], [81, 90, "B-EVENT"], [174, 189, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2825, "data": "Latinas 100 record playing Im honestly kinda impressed", "label": [[0, 7, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2826, "data": "thank god depressed", "label": [[10, 19, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2828, "data": "@TheSongBird75 Thats twisted I hated CAMHS too said I mild depression ignored early diagnosis BPD xx", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"], [59, 69, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2829, "data": "I mean whats crazy probably believe everything trying argue I think depressed Dan Mullen Kirby Smart", "label": [[68, 77, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2830, "data": "ones stupid annoying ones narcissistic manipulative", "label": [[26, 38, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2831, "data": "like freddie cute", "label": [[5, 12, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2832, "data": "Yay Just ordered gurtenfestivaltixoasis franz ferdinand kings leon", "label": [[46, 55, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2833, "data": "CW suicide Basically whole life When I first listened Linkin Parks music kid really spoke crying along In End repeat depressive episodes I got it But Chester got it I could I reasoned Maybe wisest but", "label": [[3, 10, "B-EVENT"], [117, 127, "B-EVENT"], [150, 157, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2834, "data": "Ive never depressed Post Malone isnt coming Indiana next tour", "label": [[10, 19, "B-EVENT"], [44, 51, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2836, "data": "@MonmouthFF Ive already submitted THE BATEMAN LECTURES ON DEPRESSION Hope guys funny autobiographical doc looks like this pictwittercomT8Ha8Ysx7N", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"], [58, 68, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2837, "data": "Reds fans officially suicide watch", "label": [[21, 28, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2838, "data": "That means wed get 4 MCU movies 2021 plus The Batman The Suicide Squad 2021 gonna big year", "label": [[57, 64, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2839, "data": "I love humpday", "label": [[2, 6, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2840, "data": "I realized I start tweeting Im verge mental breakdown irl", "label": [[37, 43, "B-EVENT"], [44, 53, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2841, "data": "Quand je dis que je veux mourir jattends pas quon dise non ou je ne sais quoi je veux quon dit suicide toi en live insta", "label": [[95, 102, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2842, "data": "Yall wondering Im depressed Its", "label": [[18, 27, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2843, "data": "How good thing say Some come online lose senses People dealing depression suicide think making someone commit suicide something laugh about", "label": [[63, 73, "B-EVENT"], [74, 81, "B-EVENT"], [103, 109, "B-EVENT"], [110, 117, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2845, "data": "Im Feeling Very Disappointed Depressed Today Im Really In A Dark Place Atm", "label": [[16, 28, "B-EVENT"], [29, 38, "B-EVENT"], [60, 64, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2846, "data": "BREAKING Suicide bombing northwestern district Pakistan killed least three people injured several others DIKhan SuicideBombing", "label": [[9, 16, "B-EVENT"], [47, 55, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2847, "data": "On ne ment pas en annonant un suicide alors que cest un problme technique Pour le reste fiabilit du rseau je comprends videmment les frustrations", "label": [[30, 37, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2848, "data": "When new tablet arrives Im going hard making career art Its currently I I feel least ok doing Probably greatest thing centre life around Ill take overworking feeling constantly depressed tired", "label": [[177, 186, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2849, "data": "@gmpolice CHRIS CUMBERLAND CHIEF SUPER LCP IS SUICIDE BUMMER AND HIS SOON TO BE EX WIFE ISNT SUICIDE BUMMER AND I WANT HER IN IDF AS PRIVATE MAJOR 2YR THEN ISRAELI POLICE AS MY STAR DETECTIVE I FANCY HER PANTS OFF OATH YHW", "label": [[0, 9, "B-PERSON"], [10, 15, "B-PERSON"], [15, 26, "I-PERSON"], [46, 53, "B-EVENT"], [93, 100, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2850, "data": "@TheBlueTurkey why You got one buggin ya", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2851, "data": "Yo creo q @estefaop54 quiere q suicide", "label": [[10, 21, "B-PERSON"], [31, 38, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2852, "data": "want suicide", "label": [[5, 12, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2855, "data": "The death former NHLer Greg Johnson probably suicide police say pictwittercomyNod8xJsSm", "label": [[4, 9, "B-EVENT"], [23, 27, "B-PERSON"], [28, 35, "I-PERSON"], [45, 52, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2856, "data": "These online clothes shops make normal people depressed Everything plunge bra And its its basic Its upsetting", "label": [[46, 55, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2858, "data": "@graceandmanners u calling trent liar Haha Thats awesome Toronto show trouble getting into sir", "label": [[0, 16, "B-PERSON"], [57, 64, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2859, "data": "Apparently face resting Im either judging everyone looking depressed wth", "label": [[59, 68, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2860, "data": "ny closed eric", "label": [[0, 2, "B-LOC"], [10, 14, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2861, "data": "Mom 3 killed apparent murdersuicide man met dating app family says", "label": [[22, 28, "B-EVENT"], [28, 35, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2862, "data": "I think Captain Marvel 2 first 2023 Marvel Studios lot get Carol Danvers inevitable sequel James Gunn hands full Suicide Squad 2021 Guardians Galaxy Vol 3 wait 2023 result", "label": [[91, 96, "B-PERSON"], [97, 101, "I-PERSON"], [113, 120, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2863, "data": "Im sick tired this And KNOW nothing going change No one going shit Im fucking depressed this I cant fucking take it Im close killing least would better dealing day day bullshit", "label": [[78, 87, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2864, "data": "It sucks suffering anxiety depression remembering hurt person love put through Just I think Im good mind reminds Im not", "label": [[19, 26, "B-EVENT"], [27, 37, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2867, "data": "How Im severely depressed beyond", "label": [[16, 25, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2868, "data": "Starting get depressed Gonna try stay though", "label": [[13, 22, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2869, "data": "Plz I probably wont win @miyaki404 pictwittercomYtLQclr6zx", "label": [[24, 34, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2870, "data": "Ricky telling story work goes this guy reminds you Hes manically depressed And I just I Bro", "label": [[0, 5, "B-PERSON"], [65, 74, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2871, "data": "So anybody wanna write depressed newly powered Peter", "label": [[23, 32, "B-EVENT"], [47, 52, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2872, "data": "@CannataNFL @houtz @Suttonlacesout podcast come warning may cause depression McGlinchey", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"], [12, 18, "B-PERSON"], [19, 34, "B-PERSON"], [66, 76, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2873, "data": "Why even retweet asshole The tweet I want see day election day 2020 Im hoping suicide note along rest them", "label": [[78, 85, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2874, "data": "All hail James Gunn Cant wait directing Suicide Squad", "label": [[9, 14, "B-PERSON"], [15, 19, "I-PERSON"], [40, 47, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2877, "data": "Lord give pride man bringing male suicide rates absolutely trouncing womens", "label": [[34, 41, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2878, "data": "Fantastic photos So happy best night life And yes I usually get little depressed high over I think its normal", "label": [[71, 80, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2881, "data": "@Rubberbandits Alright Blindboy Whats hot take Altright lads saying depression mental illness real That attention seeking 1st world problem Personally think theyre trolls wonder thought Cheers", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"], [68, 78, "B-EVENT"], [79, 85, "B-EVENT"], [86, 93, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2882, "data": "suicide Jesus Wishing people face tragedy swayed believe theoretical religious system disgusting After little brothers suicide Christians tried convince act God get attention Disgusting", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"], [119, 126, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2883, "data": "@torie007 great night nice meeting last night You sweetheart xoxoxo bye now", "label": [[0, 9, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2884, "data": "Today marks 2 years since losing aunt suicide liveliest soul ever I miss much She legit ride die", "label": [[38, 45, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2885, "data": "Showing committing suicide murder thats side Twitter I dont ever want come across pictwittercomu5ZbeSHZQa", "label": [[8, 18, "B-EVENT"], [19, 26, "I-EVENT"], [27, 33, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2886, "data": "@Allegromouse And good morning you", "label": [[0, 13, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2887, "data": "If death penalty prohibited criminals use social security If death penalty prohibited criminals use suicide", "label": [[3, 8, "B-EVENT"], [100, 107, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2888, "data": "@Kameshvari I thought Imogen Heap dude first time I heard her She sings low first album", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2892, "data": "The Natural Climate Climate fine Doomsday Cult end causing Death Destruction yall Need find self meaning How soon till excusing Climate Suicide Martyrs", "label": [[59, 64, "B-EVENT"], [136, 143, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2893, "data": "@LonLonRaanch", "label": [[0, 13, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2895, "data": "Its distressing many creative minds losing suicide Is increasing mental illness Exhaustion A sense lived well enough Should distressing This enormous life feel like exhausted potential", "label": [[65, 71, "B-EVENT"], [72, 79, "I-EVENT"], [80, 90, "B-EVENT"], [124, 135, "B-EVENT"], [165, 174, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2897, "data": "narcissistic", "label": [[0, 12, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2898, "data": "The greatest tragedy life finding something totally right totally wrong time depressed", "label": [[77, 86, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2899, "data": "What world living in He trying win votes commit political suicide", "label": [[58, 65, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2900, "data": "aint debate suicide", "label": [[12, 19, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2901, "data": "2 years ago My greatest idol childhoodteenage years hero died suicide Hi @ChesterBe I watching live again @mikeshinoda I wish continue inspiring people go on As me Maybe finish line I dunno", "label": [[73, 83, "B-PERSON"], [106, 118, "B-PERSON"], [57, 61, "B-EVENT"], [62, 69, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2902, "data": "Kae FaceTimed Madrid I supposed depressed go work now", "label": [[14, 20, "B-LOC"], [32, 41, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2904, "data": "I rly know talk anyone anymore due moods aggressively rabid depressed angry", "label": [[41, 53, "B-EVENT"], [60, 69, "B-EVENT"], [70, 75, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2905, "data": "dont cry love heavy angst character death mentions of suicide pictwittercom8ELW4hxRSw", "label": [[20, 25, "B-EVENT"], [36, 41, "B-EVENT"], [54, 61, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2906, "data": "Social media letting run you consume depress you Finding success it Listen I say pictwittercomwgwHWqnisQ", "label": [[37, 44, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2907, "data": "Suicide girl", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2908, "data": "u tell students depressed cos one us leaves building even 7th fire alarm xx", "label": [[16, 25, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2909, "data": "I love pretending depressed quirky", "label": [[18, 27, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2910, "data": "North East Wales suburban depressed arguably Scouse", "label": [[11, 16, "B-LOC"], [26, 35, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2911, "data": "please dont hold gun like that first rules gun safety dont finger trigger ready shoot never point anything willing shoot", "label": [[80, 85, "B-EVENT"], [115, 120, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2912, "data": "@gizeemmtk cest la soire du suicide", "label": [[0, 10, "B-PERSON"], [28, 35, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2913, "data": "killers nobody died dead people entire month half protestors committed suicide hk government disappeared view", "label": [[61, 70, "B-EVENT"], [71, 78, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2914, "data": "When civilians blood takes life Taliban A Taliban militants suicide vest goes among militants kills wounds 15 people This clearly shows humanity life meany thats taliban kill civilians Talibanloss Talibanfailed Alfathfailed pictwittercomDH9iR5qH5b", "label": [[60, 67, "B-EVENT"], [94, 99, "B-EVENT"], [100, 106, "B-EVENT"], [170, 174, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2916, "data": "rblpn @kaaeyl You know I could listen every version War Pigs ever recorded", "label": [[6, 13, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2918, "data": "depressed cowboy pictwittercomnylgthrIa0", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2919, "data": "Ce que tu fais l cest une incitation au suicide Cest puni par la loi je crois", "label": [[40, 47, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2921, "data": "brokenheart hurt pain broken hate sadness suicidal depressed sadness selfhate sadlove worthless lonely alone", "label": [[0, 11, "B-EVENT"], [12, 16, "B-EVENT"], [17, 21, "B-EVENT"], [34, 41, "B-EVENT"], [42, 50, "B-EVENT"], [51, 60, "B-EVENT"], [61, 68, "B-EVENT"], [69, 77, "B-EVENT"], [78, 85, "B-EVENT"], [86, 95, "B-EVENT"], [96, 102, "B-EVENT"], [103, 108, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2922, "data": "Wait I quoting video I mean Im depressed I want least funny god damn it", "label": [[31, 40, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2924, "data": "Ronna little girl seriously need find respectable job one reputation committing suicide You lying almost much Sanders Guiliani Pence rest Trumps Criminal Administration Trumps tax cut benefited top 1", "label": [[69, 79, "B-EVENT"], [80, 87, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2926, "data": "MTA studying Verrazzano suicide prevention efforts NewYork Transit NYC MTA", "label": [[24, 32, "B-EVENT"], [51, 58, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2927, "data": "NP Pelosi hasnt discouraged them If caucus unifies shell move forward w impeachment Itd suicide to But would mass suicide elections country 2020 impeachment goes badly I think reps flip impeach Wednesday", "label": [[88, 95, "B-EVENT"], [114, 121, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2928, "data": "ever really good dream wake become depressed dreamed isnt real bc thats im rn", "label": [[35, 44, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2929, "data": "@Eclipsed23 Thanks I neglecting health due depression stress Dont brush teeth Shower That kind stuff", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"], [43, 53, "B-EVENT"], [54, 60, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2930, "data": "Fair Id depressed I phone too", "label": [[8, 17, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2931, "data": "Suicide", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2933, "data": "Ce serait un suicide politique de donner 50 du Trop pour construire un stade pour une quipe temps partiel Jamais le conseil de ville de St Pete va accepter cela et encore moins le maire", "label": [[13, 20, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2934, "data": "This thing low key suicide tool The way hooks neck gets caught door handle ears", "label": [[19, 26, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2935, "data": "G Im depressed", "label": [[5, 14, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2936, "data": "@TezMillerOz actually eight million Stephenie Meyer fans suggestion change it No one blame myself", "label": [[0, 12, "B-PERSON"], [36, 45, "B-PERSON"], [46, 51, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2937, "data": "Life stupid af overrated suicide aint bad Im favor it but I judge", "label": [[25, 32, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2938, "data": "Cure hopelessness Otherwise suicide rate Indian Army pictwittercomiqa1SNWyT8", "label": [[5, 17, "B-EVENT"], [28, 35, "B-EVENT"], [41, 47, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 2939, "data": "Bon ok mais quel est le rapport avec tokyo qui se suicide apres avoir tuer le professeur", "label": [[50, 57, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2940, "data": "@ejf11 Thank ff", "label": [[0, 6, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2941, "data": "1 word 2 syllables XANAX", "label": [[19, 24, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2942, "data": "2009 Therapist gonna okay Im you 2019 Im also depressed bith GTH", "label": [[46, 55, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2943, "data": "No need depressed it", "label": [[8, 17, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2944, "data": "Considering launching limited Early Adopter tickets first conference female suicide next May These cheaper later Early Birds But only sold prerelease programme speakers Would buy Early Adopter ticket WomensHealth", "label": [[76, 83, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2946, "data": "I thought Suicide Squad second Damn it Please cast Bane @JamesGunn", "label": [[10, 17, "B-EVENT"], [56, 66, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2947, "data": "E isso foi uma das coisas que fez eu gostar Arkham Asylum e City Pq ela no era esperta pq ela sempre foi burra Isso dava um ar legal pra personagem Mas dps de Suicide Squad Fazer oq Agora ela tem que ser super esperta", "label": [[159, 166, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2949, "data": "Reagan Bush 43 Trump GOP used MAGA slogan robbed treasury Reagan robbed Soc Sec savings fund gave us inflation trickle down Bush gave Banks trillions started wars Trump give us recession depression Dems cleaned behind them", "label": [[0, 6, "B-PERSON"], [7, 11, "B-PERSON"], [15, 20, "B-PERSON"], [58, 64, "B-PERSON"], [124, 128, "B-PERSON"], [163, 168, "B-PERSON"], [187, 197, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2950, "data": "I do I also hate suicide boiz fanbase", "label": [[17, 24, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2951, "data": "@beardoctor tnx much too If I block lice gone thanks lot @beardoctor friend", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"], [57, 68, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2952, "data": "Bhai aap ke darr se ye log suicide na kar lebaksh do", "label": [[27, 34, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2953, "data": "Keep telling people juice levels get potent living pain hating Suicide Thats juice", "label": [[63, 70, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2954, "data": "@thelittlefox stuff cute", "label": [[0, 13, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2955, "data": "@TuckerGoodrich @japantimes Autonomic emotion regulation bereavement depression", "label": [[0, 15, "B-PERSON"], [16, 27, "B-PERSON"], [69, 79, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2956, "data": "Who lied 2016 primary rigged every time LOST race even though knew lies would depress voter turnout reduce faith government could ever hope bring affordable healthcare", "label": [[78, 85, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2957, "data": "Is every japanese author makes feel depressed", "label": [[9, 17, "B-LOC"], [36, 45, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2959, "data": "Could one puff cannabis ease depression", "label": [[29, 39, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2961, "data": "oh dont go out buy alcohol drink home like depressed piece shit am", "label": [[43, 52, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2962, "data": "Vitamin B12 deficiency cause memory loss depression How check levels", "label": [[29, 35, "B-EVENT"], [36, 40, "B-PERSON"], [41, 51, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2963, "data": "Reading 5 volumes New52 Suicide Squad make appreciate Oscar Award winning movie little bit more pictwittercomv3LVgPkIR4", "label": [[24, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2964, "data": "@NEQuilterEtsy thanks much NEQ", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2965, "data": "Its two years since tragic death ChesterBennington Here piece I wrote suicide KeithFlint took life earlier year", "label": [[33, 40, "B-PERSON"], [40, 50, "I-PERSON"], [70, 77, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2967, "data": "im drunk dont make depressed", "label": [[19, 28, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2968, "data": "nondepressed people like u depressed saw eat burrito day", "label": [[0, 12, "B-EVENT"], [27, 36, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2969, "data": "Thats point even though groups bullied also supported home communities trans groups higher suicide rate This seems suggest struggling identity closer causal link suicide family harassment", "label": [[31, 38, "B-EVENT"], [91, 98, "B-EVENT"], [123, 133, "B-EVENT"], [162, 169, "B-EVENT"], [177, 187, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2971, "data": "We started get distant started talk again I felt happy talk", "label": [[15, 22, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2973, "data": "Im either good sex Im depressed lol probably", "label": [[22, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2974, "data": "Does apply selfishness helping others Like yeah Id love feel fucking sick depressed general state things without putting blinders rest world I mean I absolute selfinterest I also like good things", "label": [[69, 73, "B-EVENT"], [74, 83, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2976, "data": "She depressed gained weight She brother continued father feared would miss lot I would pray affirm happiness life I wanted someone love treat mother like Queen is", "label": [[4, 13, "B-EVENT"], [57, 63, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2977, "data": "Suicide Attempt March 8th 2019 2019 pictwittercomxywBwIWboZ", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2978, "data": "@realDonaldTrump KAG2020 I Veteran Spouse REVICTIMIZED Lawyers Attorneys Lawfirm scammed Settlement I Veteran Spouse Victim RegencyFurniture Md @GovLarryHogan Muslim Owner disregards paying settlement coworker witness committed suicide pictwittercomaWiH8mKShI", "label": [[0, 16, "B-PERSON"], [144, 158, "B-PERSON"], [218, 227, "B-EVENT"], [228, 235, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2979, "data": "How Hillary knows many suicide victims This joke real serious question", "label": [[4, 11, "B-PERSON"], [23, 30, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2980, "data": "exactly way makes seem like suicide kind revenge plan depressed andor suicidal people get back everyone show also put message adults apparently completely clueless help", "label": [[28, 35, "B-EVENT"], [54, 63, "B-EVENT"], [70, 78, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2981, "data": "Here different image continue see effects Sullen Spirit forces host semitrance state heavy gloomy depressed oppressed Just amazing see understand this Getting now going get Tucker Carlson fixLOL pictwittercomGqJqjQtdeA", "label": [[91, 97, "B-EVENT"], [98, 107, "B-EVENT"], [108, 117, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2983, "data": "theres bigger issue fandom people think youve met taylor life turns happiness always happy like im depressed", "label": [[99, 108, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2985, "data": "Rowlet Revelation Dartrix Dragon Decidueye Decide EyeSuicide LittenRevelation TorracatRevelation IncineroarIncarnationSuicide PopplioPeople BrionneBible Revelation PrimarinaBible Revelation Pikipek TrumbeakPikachu ToucannonCan YungoosVictory Gumshoos GrubbinGhost", "label": [[53, 60, "B-EVENT"], [118, 125, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2986, "data": "honestly would eat even wasnt depressed", "label": [[30, 39, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2987, "data": "Le suicide de Carlos PARTIE 22 pictwittercompORTBiAYEF", "label": [[3, 10, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2988, "data": "Disagree Y F call godinhistory Teensy weensy narcissistic Suicide often well planned out crisis It makes perfect sense people So please go stuff pie hole course U care anyone says Red flag supreme ignorance pictwittercom3ObZ4dLRjW", "label": [[45, 57, "B-EVENT"], [58, 65, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2989, "data": "@JosephTheGreat dont see mate bit far home", "label": [[0, 15, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2990, "data": "Romeo Juliet one read plays hundreds years It represents exact thing read schools movie watched billion times But seems nobody rewrote Shakespeares suicide romance Hypocrites", "label": [[148, 155, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2991, "data": "Saw FB Pro Evo apparently Spurs third shirt Ive seen shirt number times recent weeks usually posted folks markets far flung holiday destinations Surely cant real Marketing suicide thfc neverred pictwittercomTgb1xfDGW6", "label": [[172, 179, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2993, "data": "You see Biggie see Pac see success outcome See Jesus see Judas see Caesar see Brutus See success like suicide", "label": [[102, 109, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2994, "data": "ive actually really depressed lately kind sucks ngl", "label": [[20, 29, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2996, "data": "normally depressed nothing actually good thing plunged map hell", "label": [[9, 18, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2997, "data": "Mdr je suicide", "label": [[7, 14, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 2998, "data": "@2", "label": [[0, 2, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 2999, "data": "Vem logo suicide squad", "label": [[9, 16, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3000, "data": "I daily throwing migraines 25 years Six years ago I major lumbar fusion done keep walking I still suicide headaches different still horrible 24 hour pain low back I addict", "label": [[98, 105, "B-EVENT"], [149, 153, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3001, "data": "@MTA says studying Verrazzano suicide prevention efforts We already know works Its time implement installation suicide barriers No studies @NYGovCuomo @StevenMatteo @siadvance @MaxRose4NY @JustinBrannan pictwittercomiSLBRNy3sv", "label": [[0, 4, "B-PERSON"], [30, 37, "B-EVENT"], [139, 150, "B-PERSON"], [151, 164, "B-PERSON"], [165, 175, "B-PERSON"], [176, 187, "B-PERSON"], [188, 202, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3002, "data": "half depressed half wants raid Area 51", "label": [[5, 14, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3003, "data": "I look gross pic funny post lol Astro big spooning hes snoring looks like straight died love snotty cat lmao pictwittercomXQsrtgjFSM", "label": [[83, 87, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3004, "data": "PT 6 yep ok I reason suicide exists pictwittercomTNQ2RWP3hX", "label": [[21, 28, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3005, "data": "Posthumously rip Bill Hicks new asshole joke two kids committed suicide", "label": [[54, 63, "B-EVENT"], [64, 71, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3006, "data": "The Gmez family story made public @nytimes @Newsweek Do recognize them A teen dead suicide A father desperate raise girls A hometown terrorized criminal organization created US prisons uses Glocks AR15s thx lax gun laws", "label": [[34, 42, "B-PERSON"], [43, 52, "B-PERSON"], [78, 82, "B-EVENT"], [83, 90, "B-EVENT"], [133, 143, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3008, "data": "Quelquun pour remonter le moral Feeling depressed", "label": [[40, 49, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3010, "data": "How depression anxiety differ people cancer Clinical update offers guidance clinicians might alter practice explore psychiatric symptoms cancer patients pictwittercomcnIfIi0mGc", "label": [[4, 14, "B-EVENT"], [15, 22, "B-EVENT"], [128, 136, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3012, "data": "Her another woman I know whose mum committed suicide said right things instead really experienced grew up graduated got married left SJ supportive PWD communities behind", "label": [[35, 44, "B-EVENT"], [45, 52, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3013, "data": "I think its common sense parent ever thinks child difficult parent practicing favouritism parents insane ideas ideal child long child arrive kids driven suicide pressured rigid ideals itself", "label": [[153, 160, "B-EVENT"], [161, 170, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3014, "data": "cant waitto kms ill put u No gon suicide pact Im dying w fam", "label": [[33, 40, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3015, "data": "The person invented shit obviously bored considering suicide This shit", "label": [[53, 60, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3016, "data": "@fallenhapjm @underworldyeol", "label": [[0, 12, "B-PERSON"], [13, 28, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3017, "data": "Je laime vraiment pas en plus il men au suicide lune de ses exs", "label": [[40, 47, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3018, "data": "I would planned fucking beach day des eddie hoes truly DEPRESSED", "label": [[55, 64, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3019, "data": "People work think depressed sad im staring resting bitch face actuality Im fucking mean choreography head", "label": [[18, 27, "B-EVENT"], [28, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3020, "data": "showing fringe Jews So nearly 12 Palestinians support suicide bombing Tell sick culture glorifies martyrs blow maximize killing innocents Sickos", "label": [[120, 127, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3021, "data": "Been dang near impossible pry away Twitter today I figured though yall depressed too This website happy people Thank fuck", "label": [[71, 80, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3024, "data": "Sneaker Pimps Tesko Suicide Official Video via @YouTube", "label": [[20, 27, "B-EVENT"], [47, 55, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3025, "data": "Scotts Bluff Nebraska Seriously considered suicide", "label": [[43, 50, "B-EVENT"], [13, 21, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 3026, "data": "People often joke suicide despite depressing subject often leads times people legitimately thinking suicidal thoughts others wont listen its late", "label": [[18, 25, "B-EVENT"], [34, 44, "B-EVENT"], [100, 108, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3028, "data": "Niggas talking murder wack cause take somebodys life meanwhile wearing FTP listening Suicide Boys 2019 I think lost life bro", "label": [[15, 21, "B-EVENT"], [85, 92, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3029, "data": "DCEU Recap 9 Despite standalone movies franchise originally Suicide Squad Wonder Woman supposed connections overall story Notably Steppenwolf would appear former movie ReleaseTheSnyderCut @RTSnyderCut @CDawsonAuthor pictwittercomtWphUsXbu3", "label": [[60, 67, "B-EVENT"], [188, 200, "B-PERSON"], [201, 215, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3030, "data": "@melissamoog Date always end twittering anything web site", "label": [[0, 12, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3031, "data": "I support trans people sometimes I feel like Im supportive I get depressed cause Im trying hard make difference yet Im still failing", "label": [[65, 74, "B-EVENT"], [125, 132, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3032, "data": "@theresanoelle Okay Ill keep look it", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3033, "data": "Yo boys people using suicide clout", "label": [[21, 28, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3034, "data": "@prophetlady im christian read persecution alot recieve alotsince march", "label": [[0, 12, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3035, "data": "waking 8 hour depression nap pictwittercomlkz3KZqCw9", "label": [[14, 24, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3037, "data": "I would die Do die Suicide", "label": [[19, 26, "B-EVENT"], [15, 18, "B-EVENT"], [8, 11, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3038, "data": "im always depressed", "label": [[10, 19, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3040, "data": "@verkoren The blipfm song posted twitter", "label": [[0, 9, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3041, "data": "Depressed Thats tweet", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3042, "data": "@randomblink Hey Can Follow please", "label": [[0, 12, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3044, "data": "Being close loved one mine committed suicide I take major offense ridiculous uninformed post You terrible person say least", "label": [[27, 36, "B-EVENT"], [37, 44, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3045, "data": "dear @netflix Im extremely disappointed decision remove suicide scene @13ReasonsWhy suicide mental illness real every day life cant edited out exists point show educate hide problem", "label": [[5, 13, "B-PERSON"], [27, 39, "B-EVENT"], [56, 63, "B-EVENT"], [70, 83, "B-PERSON"], [84, 91, "B-EVENT"], [92, 98, "B-EVENT"], [99, 106, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3046, "data": "Tiens et l @zedravidalatina", "label": [[11, 27, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3048, "data": "There plenty heterosexual people earth I dont understand think suicide Gay people cant physically children good one world overpopulating two adopt child need family What wrong", "label": [[63, 70, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3049, "data": "Eh misal aku donorkan semua badanku trs mati termasuk suicide ga sih Ga boleh suicide dosak", "label": [[54, 61, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3050, "data": "@jacquelinerinda hey jacwhatever isGOOD LUCK", "label": [[0, 16, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3051, "data": "But 999999999999999999 conversations depressed like hi yeah I hate myself yesterday I feel I incompetent everything Ive added fresh details catechism Why I Am A Monster functionally its same", "label": [[37, 46, "B-EVENT"], [62, 66, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3052, "data": "95 suicide terrorist attacks conducted encourage foreign occupiers leave terrorists home country @davidcnswanson", "label": [[3, 10, "B-EVENT"], [97, 112, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3054, "data": "@monnie Raincheck You come see stage one day soon", "label": [[0, 7, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3058, "data": "Bien que la thse du suicide soit privilgie lhypothse de laccident nest pas carte", "label": [[20, 27, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3059, "data": "@hadiqazeeshan Yephe", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3060, "data": "i depressed cause fat ya heard me gates got dying", "label": [[2, 11, "B-EVENT"], [44, 49, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3061, "data": "Low key depressed Im good", "label": [[8, 17, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3062, "data": "@ashduranduran Me too Its soo cool", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3063, "data": "I used 2 feel suicide cowards way u leave everybody pain 2 clean mess however 2 must immeasurable amount pain said u something heinous take life face consequences thats coward", "label": [[14, 21, "B-EVENT"], [52, 56, "B-EVENT"], [105, 109, "B-EVENT"], [135, 139, "B-EVENT"], [140, 144, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3064, "data": "call fat anything even tho easily finish im depressed appetite still normal", "label": [[44, 53, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3065, "data": "Suicide note pictwittercomeEJBWwdJhj", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3066, "data": "I know depression alcohol addiction blend", "label": [[7, 17, "B-EVENT"], [26, 35, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3067, "data": "Suicide toi", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3068, "data": "Oncologists high suicide rate driven unique emotional challenges face ASCO19 pictwittercomBn8d18cw21", "label": [[17, 24, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3070, "data": "Oh Dave I sorry hear this What tragedyIts perfectly normal feel like this suicide family years ago I know like I hope family friends talk even doctor gets much Sending hug pictwittercom1dMWTnH1Un", "label": [[3, 7, "B-PERSON"], [74, 81, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3071, "data": "Barry like today Or yesterday Even day shit For see Barry found stuck Groundhog Day type effect Although good looking Tom Hanks dissuade contemplating suicide out satsplat", "label": [[0, 5, "B-PERSON"], [52, 57, "B-PERSON"], [137, 150, "B-EVENT"], [151, 158, "I-EVENT"], [118, 121, "B-PERSON"], [122, 127, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3073, "data": "Me watching friends hang without depressed ass wanna become house never leave anxiety tells ass Im needed bc I aint shit pictwittercomyg8eV74p6T", "label": [[33, 42, "B-EVENT"], [78, 85, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3074, "data": "@ccchapman Yeah Ive seen 28 problems Were working lemons though", "label": [[0, 10, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3075, "data": "thank you I feel spirit suicide pleasantly pictwittercomS1Hxz7gRDD", "label": [[24, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3078, "data": "heres problem stan person movie franchise look fucking definition stan find particular celebrity practice fucking preach dickhead genuine people depressed mentally insane result stanning", "label": [[145, 154, "B-EVENT"], [155, 163, "B-EVENT"], [164, 170, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3081, "data": "love life like bachelorette except contestants clinically depressed fire humor", "label": [[58, 67, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3083, "data": "Idk understand ppl chose suicide way escaping freeing pain judgements", "label": [[25, 32, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3084, "data": "So people depressed depressed", "label": [[10, 19, "B-EVENT"], [20, 29, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3085, "data": "ImranKhan DC suicide bombing attack hospital today PakistaniTaliban pictwittercomOSRReLiwJX", "label": [[13, 20, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3086, "data": "At least Im narcissistic", "label": [[12, 24, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3087, "data": "Black Is The New Black Black Dark Darkest Darkness AddamsFamily ChristinaRicci depression depressed pictwittercomh7di5ekIg5", "label": [[29, 33, "B-EVENT"], [34, 41, "B-EVENT"], [42, 50, "B-EVENT"], [79, 89, "B-EVENT"], [90, 99, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3088, "data": "showing family meetings years going bc depressed pictwittercomSO4wf0lW88", "label": [[39, 48, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3089, "data": "Female suicide bomber kills eight northwest Pakistan The Telegram", "label": [[7, 14, "B-EVENT"], [44, 52, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 3090, "data": "If business decided work others isolate self would commercial suicide If one person marriage decides everything alone never work partner theyd divorced alone Same applies Uk We greater worker others", "label": [[62, 69, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3091, "data": "First time Ive agreed Im depressed pictwittercomwejk6LHaN5", "label": [[25, 34, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3092, "data": "im really gonna depressed life huh", "label": [[16, 25, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3095, "data": "Study Sexual minority adolescents higher rates depression", "label": [[47, 57, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3096, "data": "Remember I got two free suicide boys tickets Brooke bc shes best person Ive ever met I would like happen someone give freetickets", "label": [[24, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3098, "data": "Nobody I imitate ppl bullies", "label": [[21, 28, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3099, "data": "Im sad depressed good", "label": [[7, 16, "B-EVENT"], [3, 6, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3100, "data": "k child I really really loved peanut butter spread cheese depressed thought childhood snack would make feel better", "label": [[58, 67, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3101, "data": "update shes cheater im alone depressed", "label": [[29, 38, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3104, "data": "@JustinePHAC @agnosticQuest @onfiremission The talk resilience recognition pain suffering normal part healing process Depression make seem alone unique suffering recognition essential health", "label": [[0, 12, "B-PERSON"], [13, 27, "B-PERSON"], [28, 42, "B-PERSON"], [75, 79, "B-EVENT"], [80, 89, "B-EVENT"], [118, 128, "B-EVENT"], [152, 161, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3105, "data": "Sam Dyson nice rebound performance", "label": [[0, 3, "B-PERSON"], [4, 9, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3106, "data": "If bias produce x 101 didnt debut ill depressed while This first time feel devoted produce series SONGHYEONGJUN YUVIN KIMYOHAN choseungyeon NamDohyon PRODUCEX101 I stan idiot kids cutie pie hyeongjunnie pictwittercom6FNtlAEZYX", "label": [[38, 47, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3107, "data": "The Suicide Squads narrative spreads across Fake MediaMore Social Media Summit needed expose them", "label": [[4, 11, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3108, "data": "sigh wanna like rip head cuz im depressed n im gonna punch headboard bed", "label": [[32, 41, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3111, "data": "Portugal sabedoria", "label": [[0, 8, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 3112, "data": "SpiritualGuruOfMillions Saint Ram Rahim The fast competitive world led large number depressed people In timethe true method meditation given Saint Dr @Gurmeetramrahim Singh Ji Insan helps live stress free healthy life@derasachasauda pictwittercomnnUQOvAHbm", "label": [[84, 93, "B-EVENT"], [150, 166, "B-PERSON"], [217, 232, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3113, "data": "@mileycyrus take care", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3114, "data": "Im sorry youre feeling depressed get better take time self care something enjoy If easy lmao I wish", "label": [[23, 32, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3115, "data": "And lets realbeing broke stressed depressed etc exacerbate emotions parents stuff spills household If life hitting hard might lil patient empathetic", "label": [[25, 33, "B-EVENT"], [34, 43, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3116, "data": "@oxbloodruffin Wait wait wait Do mean tell newsinfo twitter 100 reliable How Chelsea anyway", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3119, "data": "Gee wonder why If really care suicide rates trans people accept said trans people instead using happens due oppression oppress more", "label": [[30, 37, "B-EVENT"], [108, 118, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3121, "data": "Destruction land due fracking making feel depressed Sounds like perfect time drink LaCroix Blackberry Mango DrinkLaCroix", "label": [[42, 51, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3122, "data": "We even making comparison Heath Ledger", "label": [[26, 31, "B-PERSON"], [32, 38, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3123, "data": "Yh cares earns money song suicide As long retains public image would matter", "label": [[26, 33, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3126, "data": "Umuulan lang tangina depress agad xd", "label": [[21, 28, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3128, "data": "Woman almost committed suicide losing son gives birth triplets one year", "label": [[13, 22, "B-EVENT"], [23, 30, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3129, "data": "Orange County devotes 600000 first suicideprevention program", "label": [[35, 42, "B-EVENT"], [0, 6, "B-PERSON"], [7, 13, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3130, "data": "@derasachasauda SpiritualGuruOfMillions The fast compitative world led large number depressed People In timethe true method meditation given Saint Dr@Gurmeetramrahim Singh ji Insan helps live stressfree healthy life pictwittercomDOZk3xtQmx", "label": [[0, 15, "B-PERSON"], [84, 93, "B-EVENT"], [149, 165, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3131, "data": "good heart generation suicide", "label": [[22, 29, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3132, "data": "It really makes depressed think humanity actually shit", "label": [[16, 25, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3133, "data": "Im afraid losing people im afraid losing", "label": [[3, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3134, "data": "Dershowitz 1st wife Sue Barlach learned affair destroyed important legal papers retaliation She hospitalized beat her Dershowitz sued custody 2 kids The mental physical abuse allegedly led commit suicide", "label": [[153, 159, "B-EVENT"], [160, 168, "I-EVENT"], [169, 174, "I-EVENT"], [189, 195, "B-EVENT"], [196, 203, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3135, "data": "Elizabeth freakin awesome Shes following now", "label": [[0, 9, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3136, "data": "Fat chicks personality lit fat depressed", "label": [[31, 40, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3137, "data": "tw suicide scene bodyguard well use blank I know was I broke hardest sentence somehow rewatching hurts first time pictwittercom7gxfZyofQf", "label": [[3, 10, "B-EVENT"], [97, 102, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3139, "data": "@sitapati That sounds lovely Are conventions might sponsor group like ours Wed love come", "label": [[0, 9, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3140, "data": "Kabul July 19 2019 Islamic suicide bomber exploded car outside Kabul University killing 9 people including traffic policeman injuring 33 others Police received intelligence attack coming know when", "label": [[27, 34, "B-EVENT"], [0, 5, "B-LOC"], [63, 68, "B-LOC"], [69, 79, "I-LOC"], [80, 87, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3141, "data": "Thats ironic statement That lunatic antisemite racist screeching trump supporters crazy Shes desparaging mentally ill dozens millions Americans included Diversity strength its suicide", "label": [[105, 113, "B-EVENT"], [114, 117, "I-EVENT"], [176, 183, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3142, "data": "ya te queda otra mas que compartir @glitterndior sam te quiero pictwittercomtxOsZIz7GI", "label": [[35, 48, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3143, "data": "My 6 year old fine I sobbed depressed hours after thats asking", "label": [[28, 37, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3144, "data": "Jusko naman Nakaka depress hahahahahaha", "label": [[19, 26, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3145, "data": "calling debby ryan", "label": [[8, 13, "B-PERSON"], [14, 18, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3146, "data": "I clients office took phone call guy line telling hes going it turn admitted hes feeling depressed advised person seek help So glad black brothers facing mental health issues head on", "label": [[89, 98, "B-EVENT"], [154, 160, "B-EVENT"], [161, 167, "I-EVENT"], [168, 174, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3147, "data": "LatestNews Negative thoughts destructive emotions bring pain unhappiness depression misery lives addresses pendemic issues pictwittercomz3vZigSEaa", "label": [[11, 19, "B-EVENT"], [20, 28, "I-EVENT"], [29, 40, "B-EVENT"], [41, 49, "I-EVENT"], [61, 72, "B-EVENT"], [73, 83, "B-EVENT"], [84, 90, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3148, "data": "He powerful story He also great song preventing suicide Kudos him God Bless", "label": [[48, 55, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3149, "data": "Kassidey", "label": [[0, 8, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3150, "data": "Yeah 13 year old daughter detainee left She committed suicide All could say I failed her No Donald WE USA Under leadership failed her It Ivanka", "label": [[44, 53, "B-EVENT"], [54, 61, "I-EVENT"], [102, 105, "B-LOC"], [137, 143, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3151, "data": "Claramente ya dejaron de intentar competir Gunn dijo que da fecha de GotG porque tiene que terminar primero Suicide Squad tho", "label": [[108, 115, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3152, "data": "Took decide hiddleston suave charming depressed sulk whiny angry He hits moods well I think right way pull", "label": [[38, 47, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3153, "data": "think depression manifested aggression ive never wanted beat somebodys ass much", "label": [[6, 16, "B-EVENT"], [28, 38, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3154, "data": "yawa suicide HAHAHA", "label": [[5, 12, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3155, "data": "16 yo nibbi blew suicide bombing DIKhan", "label": [[17, 24, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3156, "data": "Bulletin Travelawareness Travelsecurity Pakistan DeraIsmailKhan Female suicide bomber kills eight northwest Pakistan", "label": [[40, 48, "B-LOC"], [108, 116, "B-LOC"], [71, 78, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3157, "data": "There earlier suicide attempt", "label": [[14, 21, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3158, "data": "theyre going flat lie criminal activity which btw sue defamation falsely accusing least come convincing story expose actually know happens suicide threat made", "label": [[139, 146, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3159, "data": "In ways I feel happy many people think I do But I feel depressed pictwittercomNJ86JENU51", "label": [[55, 64, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3162, "data": "Everyday suicide goes higher list options solve problems", "label": [[9, 16, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3163, "data": "Sabi ni Maam hindi porket stress ka depress ka na Depression daw yung may mga nangyari sa buhay mo noon na hanggang ngayon apektado ka pa din sa pangyayaring yun I FELT THAT hahaha I really really felt that Hanggang ngayon nararamdaman mo pa din yung sakit nun", "label": [[36, 43, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3166, "data": "You younguns need better job getting assisted suicide laws passed rest states then", "label": [[46, 53, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3167, "data": "I even right depressed I cutest best friends I found doorstep @NiveenAz Leen guys best pictwittercommCLXinB7Rk", "label": [[13, 22, "B-EVENT"], [62, 71, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3168, "data": "The best cure worry depression melancholy brooding go deliberately forth try lift ones sympathy gloom somebody else Arnold Bennett inspiredailyinspirationalquotemotivateyourself pictwittercomBfZiFRTmf2", "label": [[20, 30, "B-EVENT"], [96, 101, "B-EVENT"], [116, 122, "B-PERSON"], [123, 130, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3169, "data": "@AC360 You depressedimagine I feeling along friends family This awful happening Its unbelieveable 2019 45 telling people color go back came fromagain I say unbelievable This scary core", "label": [[0, 6, "B-PERSON"], [11, 20, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3170, "data": "depressed whole ass year foo 3", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3171, "data": "know im depressed pictwittercomvdeHkYUWSZ", "label": [[8, 17, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3173, "data": "@MarkH WOW OK Im feeling motivated now", "label": [[0, 6, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3175, "data": "This morning two security personnel martyred firing raid checkpoint Dera Ismail Khan terrorists bodies taken hospital suicide bomber blew inside civil hospitals trauma centre say officials spot", "label": [[118, 125, "B-EVENT"], [109, 117, "B-LOC"], [161, 167, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3176, "data": "Exercise lowers risk depression risk ages researchers find", "label": [[21, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3178, "data": "Baby let see around downtown Its either slums palaces fountains Its either sleek black limo life lead limbo Scald mouth hot chocolate long ago Stuff mouth zero calorie White Snow", "label": [[20, 28, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 3179, "data": "Some courageous journalism publications Daily Mail Are depression pills driving patients commit suicide via @MailOnline", "label": [[55, 65, "B-EVENT"], [89, 95, "B-EVENT"], [96, 103, "I-EVENT"], [108, 119, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3181, "data": "Depressed need hug man randomly touched @ sally beauty", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"], [40, 47, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3182, "data": "Work makes depressed", "label": [[11, 20, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3184, "data": "suicide sabay bumalik ka lang ulit pictwittercomy5riNf7DMX", "label": [[0, 7, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3185, "data": "What call Elton John suicide vest Fag grenade", "label": [[10, 15, "B-PERSON"], [16, 20, "I-PERSON"], [21, 28, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3186, "data": "truly made steve carrell dressed gru account 2 years ago memes getting attention now link account Depression risen", "label": [[98, 108, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3189, "data": "@foodsbitch I know I busy mesmerized Richard Alpert", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"], [37, 44, "B-PERSON"], [45, 51, "I-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3191, "data": "Dear humans unless performing ritual suicide nonpolyester clothing juvenile distraction Free embarrassment put cotton backpack blessed heatwave goseahawks", "label": [[37, 44, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3194, "data": "Someone commits suicide every 40 seconds", "label": [[8, 15, "B-EVENT"], [16, 23, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3195, "data": "Mureed murder case Eyewitness attempts suicide Karachi pictwittercomQkn8wxido4", "label": [[39, 46, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3196, "data": "sarcastic depressed", "label": [[10, 19, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3197, "data": "Koko said distraught informed Robins suicide Akka And Koko passed away last year", "label": [[37, 44, "B-EVENT"], [30, 36, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3198, "data": "Is bad I try stay busy 247 I dont think depressed things bad things life Lmao", "label": [[40, 49, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3200, "data": "Depressed brands like thing bad appropriative I worry Long John Silvers social media person actually chronic depression", "label": [[0, 9, "B-EVENT"], [101, 108, "B-EVENT"], [109, 119, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3201, "data": "thats suicide meal", "label": [[6, 13, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3202, "data": "3 months ago day nine suicide bombers unleashed terror country brought standstill As Sri Lanka limps back normalcy lets remember hundreds families lost loved ones Their wounds may heal pain never LKA SriLanka", "label": [[22, 29, "B-EVENT"], [200, 208, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 3203, "data": "Just tweeted hour back guys body found Matunga committed suicide due financial problem leaving back twin sons wife", "label": [[39, 46, "B-PERSON"], [47, 56, "B-EVENT"], [57, 64, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3204, "data": "@kelpel Too late try fit NoCal Ive long I either fit theres hope", "label": [[0, 7, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3205, "data": "@RealHatter Shes vacation", "label": [[0, 11, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3206, "data": "IM LITERALLY AN EGOISTIC NARCISSISTIC MIRACLE SPIRITUAL LYRICAL INDIVIDUAL R U KIDDING ME", "label": [[25, 37, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3207, "data": "Jviens de voir Tokyo se suicide aprs avoir tuer le professeur sur le profil @LittleArabe cest bon jle dteste il vien de niker srie", "label": [[76, 88, "B-PERSON"], [24, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3209, "data": "@BethIsBaffled WOW Beth went myspace listened tracks u recorded Theyre really good", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3210, "data": "trying celebrate graduating moving house trying enjoy summer depressed lol LOL pictwittercomai7kGttt5J", "label": [[61, 70, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3211, "data": "@JayteKz got lot thoughts head right depression hitting hard right Im hanging love man", "label": [[0, 8, "B-PERSON"], [37, 47, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3214, "data": "Helping depressed employeesanother farright initiative", "label": [[8, 17, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3215, "data": "Same pharse radical terrorist suicide bombers say hit button", "label": [[30, 37, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3216, "data": "Running 2 hours late I sorry lets raise money American Foundation Suicide Prevention", "label": [[66, 73, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3217, "data": "A Globo nosso suicide squad", "label": [[14, 21, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3218, "data": "Deepika talks days depression TIME 110 GALA indiaforums", "label": [[19, 29, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3219, "data": "The funny thing Nietzsche WASNT nihilist denounced reading philosophy back still control actions brain But 90 people know NOW filtered lense abusive Nazisister wow I know this", "label": [[141, 148, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3220, "data": "This darkness hit me chefs looking turn heat restaurant kitchens Warning piece discusses suicide Its incredibly powerful confronting", "label": [[89, 96, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3221, "data": "This person threatening suicide now They want attention", "label": [[24, 31, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3222, "data": "Im depressed fuckkkkkk", "label": [[3, 12, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3225, "data": "@balsamiqMarco Your message inbox And reply you Please let know receieve it", "label": [[0, 14, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3226, "data": "This known repetition compulsion meaning individuals previous traumatic event increased risk future trauma experiences Suicide clusters obvious common consequence trauma repetition compulsion", "label": [[62, 71, "B-EVENT"], [100, 106, "B-EVENT"], [119, 126, "B-EVENT"], [163, 169, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3227, "data": "favourite asap rocky walking suicide hotline 18002738255 Retweet", "label": [[29, 36, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3228, "data": "Had dream I met Sarah Paulsonrealizing dream depressed", "label": [[45, 54, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3229, "data": "jlai fini et ya aucun suicide", "label": [[22, 29, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3232, "data": "24 All Supermarkets give away free food date separate food halls 25 Legalise assisted suicide 26 Ban love island Thats", "label": [[77, 85, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3233, "data": "hurts bad really dont want bother", "label": [[0, 5, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3234, "data": "@aplynch either job title would look nice resume Actually I take salary wo title", "label": [[0, 8, "B-PERSON"]]}
{"id": 3235, "data": "What I seen read regards villages Alaska straight western pioneersLocals carry gunsno alcohol allowed period towns Delivery supplies brought plane every onetwo weeksProbably 1 central supply storeHigh suicide", "label": [[34, 40, "B-PERSON"], [201, 208, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3236, "data": "absolutely nothing sister tickets lets make mess tour cleveland cant wait see hey mondayagain", "label": [[54, 63, "B-LOC"]]}
{"id": 3238, "data": "Orang lebih rela membuang duit 25 ribu beli rokok yg bahayakan kesehatannya Committed suicide Coba sebulan sudah bisa buat beli 15 gr emas Or kalau mau investasi akhirat bisa buat sedekah Per hari 25 ribu Jumlah yang besar Bs selamatkan 5 anak agar tak putus sekolah", "label": [[76, 85, "B-EVENT"], [86, 93, "I-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3239, "data": "Look Australia violence already declining instituted statist gun grab violence decline change Meanwhile violence decline USA similar didnt institute statist gun grab Also nongun suicide went amount gun suicide decreased hmmm", "label": [[5, 14, "B-LOC"], [70, 78, "B-EVENT"], [15, 23, "B-EVENT"], [104, 112, "B-EVENT"], [121, 124, "B-LOC"], [178, 185, "B-EVENT"], [202, 209, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3240, "data": "If Im honest I sort love suicide squeeze call simultaneously hating swing 32 call", "label": [[25, 32, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3242, "data": "Problem periods never know depressed life actually shitty af", "label": [[27, 36, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3243, "data": "SpiritualGuruOfMillions Saint Gurmeet Ram Rahim Singh Ji The fast competitive world led large number depressed people In time true method meditation given StDr MSG helps live stress free healthy life", "label": [[101, 110, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3244, "data": "Gillowel est tellement une grosse merde que Lapinchat sest suicid", "label": [[59, 65, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3245, "data": "Omg cat near suicide jump pictwittercom0dn3x71qm2", "label": [[13, 20, "B-EVENT"]]}
{"id": 3246, "data": "Shocking little media attention obit got Actually never saw anywhere WTF HRC talking abt You gave chance live long odds No late reprieve coming Take leave dignity Assisted suicide Ill With", "label": [[172, 179, "B-EVENT"]]}
