O	O
est	O
le	O
rapport	O
avec	O
les	O
philosophes	O
ici	O
On	O
traite	O
un	O
sujet	O
serieu	O
cyber	O
harclement	O
mais	O
malheureusement	O
de	O
nos	O
jours	O
il	O
faut	O
attendre	O
que	O
quelquun	O
se	O
suicide	B-EVENT
pour	O
rendre	O
compte	O
du	O
rel	O
problme	O
cest	O

N	O
I	O
m	O
writing	O
thread	O
memoira	O
memory	O
lacked	O
far	O
preety	O
much	O
sure	O
ve	O
next	O
No	O
suicidenot	B-EVENT
allIm	O
cowardeven	O
courageous	O
thatIm	O
start	O
againagain	O
studies	O
hopewillingness	O

hey	O
even	O
need	O
depressed	B-EVENT
goodbad	O
idea	O

Vladdie	B-PER
calls	O
way	O
sees	O
enough	O
women	O
color	O
already	O
Suicide	O
Squad	O
We	O
could	O
give	O
hoot	O
arewhat	O
care	O
WHO	O
seeing	O
something	O
makes	O
us	O
sick	O

everything	O
She	O
stopped	O
committing	O
suicide	B-EVENT
different	O
occasions	O
she	O
s	O
given	O
hope	O
room	O
breathe	O
I	O
love	O
art	O
Her	O
inspires	O
much	O
person	O
Amy	B-PER
amazing	O
human	O
deserves	O
support	B-EVENT
gets	O
23	O

@LBCIslander	B-PER
That	O
s	O
always	O
possibility	O
I	O
m	O
MP	O
actually	O
fulltime	O
soldier	O
parttime	O
local	O
cop	O
Just	O
pastime	O
really	O

sam	O
harcel	O
par	O
ses	O
camarades	O
de	O
classe	O
se	O
suicide	O
devant	O
eux	O
un	O
drame	O
vitable	O

dazai	O
singing	O
suicide	B-EVENT
mood	O

Crying	B-EVENT
I	O
m	O
entering	O
deep	O
depression	B-EVENT
Ca	I-EVENT
nt	I-EVENT
eat	I-EVENT
sleep	I-EVENT
That	O
s	O
worse	O
pain	B-EVENT
Emoji	O
Loudly	O
crying	O
face	O

yeah	O
apparently	O
graphic	O
suicide	O
scene	O
like	O
goes	O
detail	O
that	O
s	O
big	O
nope	O

lt	O
forever	O
make	O
smile	O

bro	O
guys	O
like	O
narcissists	O

I	O
m	O
gon	O
na	O
pretend	O
MoS	O
BvS	O
exist	O
Wonder	B-EVENT
Woman	I-EVENT
first	O
DCEU	O
movie	O
Then	O
forget	O
Suicide	B-EVENT
Squad	I-EVENT
make	O
second	O
film	O
JL	B-PER
Snyder	I-PER
Cut	O
if	O
happens	O
think	O
good	O
maybe	O
Aquman	B-PER
definitley	O
Shazam	B-PER
WW	O
Aqu	B-PER
Sha	I-PER
dc	O
dceu	O

Did	O
suicide	O
squad	O
start	O
filming	O
yet	O
Ever	O
since	O
signed	O
interest	O
piqued	O

I	O
know	O
try	O
get	O
ticket	O
Ill	O
depressed	O
bad	O
mood	O
GPF	B-EVENT
maybe	O
able	O
watch	O
all	O
kind	O
experience	O
favorite	O
band	O
Maybe	O
would	O
best	O
GET	O
matter	O
hard	O

What	O
weplanned	O
joint	O
suicide	O
tonight	O
x	O
Just	O
kidding	O
unless	O

good	O
evening	O
I	O
continue	O
suffer	O

Gedlembane	B-PER
commiting	O
Suicide	O
mirenda	O
via	O
@YouTube	O

When	O
getting	O
tilted	O
squad	O
yell	O
I	O
hit	O
fattest	O
shatter	O
life	O
Just	O
bot	O
DPS	B-PER
players	O
finally	O
kill	O
something	O
roommates	O
never	O
played	O
Overwatch	B-PER
next	O
room	O
confused	O
AF	O
pictwittercomub4aYVlsUu	O

do	O
nt	O
care	O
y	O
all	O
scrollin	O
fastly	O
skippin	O
tweet	O
perhaps	O
working	O
plan	O
2	O
months	O
Greatest	O
Suicide	O
Might	O
well	O
publish	O
book	O
Just	O
own	O
Not	O
suggesting	O
anyone	O
die	O
unless	O
want	O
to	O

So	O
what	O
Christ	B-PER
many	O
hours	O
life	O
sink	O
this	O
Hours	O
NEVER	O
get	O
back	O
I	O
m	O
already	O
depressed	O
minute	O
gave	O
nothingburger	O

Great	O
see	O
many	O
runners	O
ASICS	B-EVENT
10k	O
run	O
supporting	O
CALM	O
Campaign	O
Against	O
Living	O
Miserably	O
helping	O
prevent	O
male	O
suicide	O
biggest	O
killer	O
men	O
45	O
summerstreets	O
regentstreet	O
asics10k	O

@manuelkuhs	O
thank	O
made	O
day	O

attracted	O
girls	O
attempted	O
suicide	O
first	O
three	O
times	O
this	O
thought	O
wrong	O
gross	O
would	O
saved	O
years	O
therapy	O
depression	O
seen	O
two	O
relationship	O
movies	O
watched	O
thanks	O
bad	O
opinion	O

think	O
i	O
m	O
slowly	O
going	O
depression	O
Emoji	O
Weary	O
faceEmoji	O
face	O

Three	O
Common	O
EVENTonceptions	O
About	O
Depression	O

pessoa	O
que	O
pensa	O
em	O
suicidio	O
no	O
esta	O
na	O
sede	O
de	O
se	O
matar	O
e	O
sim	O
acabar	O
c	O
aquela	O
dor	O
dentro	O
dela	O

There	O
s	O
much	O
discover	O
I	O
time	O
get	O
depressed	O

@Rosherrrs	O
Oh	O
fisshing	O
compliments	O
gorgoues	O
drawing	O
XX	B-PER

Last	O
September	O
childrens	O
adopted	O
sibling	O
took	O
life	O
My	O
best	O
friend	O
never	O
kids	O
understand	O
This	O
next	O
walk	O
together	O
funds	O
suicide	B-EVENT
society	O
Please	O
take	O
look	O
page	O

I	O
ACTUALLY	O
HAD	O
SOME	O
CONCEPTS	O
FOR	O
MODEL	O
AU	B-PER
forgot	O
tweet	O
them	O
like	O
2	O
things	O

I	O
think	O
kise	O
stuff	O
going	O
absolutely	O
depressed	B-EVENT
boys	O
thinking	O
middle	O
school	O
fun	O
time	O

The	O
day	O
may	O
far	O
authority	O
adding	O
appropriate	O
drugs	O
water	O
supply	O
similar	O
device	O
able	O
elate	O
depress	B-EVENT
stimulate	O
paralyze	O
minds	O
whole	O
populations	O
purposes	O
Hayek	B-PER

Officials	O
Mother	B-PER
kills	B-EVENT
sons	O
sets	B-EVENT
house	I-EVENT
fire	I-EVENT
Elmhurst	B-LOC
murdersuicide	O

BBY	O
NOOOOOO	O
THE	O
PAIN	B-EVENT
IS	O
BACK	O
pictwittercomzNfRn8wzxc	O

Can	O
Dogs	O
Feel	O
Depressed	B-EVENT

I	O
really	O
miss	B-EVENT
20	O
pounds	O
lighter	O
remember	O
reason	O
skinny	O
alcoholic	O
depressed	B-EVENT
piece	O
shit	O
drug	O
problem	O
m	O
like	O
oh	O
nvm	O
d	O
rather	O
fat	O
happy	B-EVENT

g	O
envie	O
de	O
suicid	B-EVENT
je	O
veux	O
remettre	O
son	O
oeil	O
en	O
place	O
pictwittercomqAZLR2xSWD	B-PER

Soooo	O
I	O
could	O
leaving	O
shit	O
hole	O
town	O
3	O
days	O
going	O
trip	O
life	O
time	O
@gabbyfrappier	B-PER
nah	O
ask	O
depressed	B-EVENT
m	O
gon	O
na	O
weeks	O

I	O
have	O
nt	O
listened	O
Suicide	B-EVENT
Boys	O
cool	O
minutes	O
But	O
remember	O
why	O
shit	O
hypes	O
way	O
much	O

You	O
probably	O
spend	O
entire	O
life	O
alone	B-EVENT
re	O
self	B-EVENT
centered	I-EVENT
egotistical	I-EVENT
narcissistic	I-EVENT
child	O
drives	O
guys	O
suicide	B-EVENT
jokes	O
it	O
remorse	O
No	O
one	O
ever	O
love	O
real	O
you	O
fake	O
face	O
put	O
on	O

Bradys	B-EVENT
hand	O
placement	O
needs	O
improvement	O
lmfao	O

I	O
love	O
this	O
too	O
Do	O
nt	O
going	O
broke	O
you	O
Ill	B-EVENT
let	O
break	O
first	O
turn	O
anew	O
Paint	O
cheeks	O
shades	O
pink	O
paint	O
soul	O
blue	O

My	O
little	O
Girls	O
father	O
succumbed	O
depression	B-EVENT
committed	O
suicide	B-EVENT
last	O
night	O
How	O
I	O
ever	O
get	O
tell	O
daughter	O
never	O
see	O
best	O
friend	O

The	O
Suicide	B-EVENT
Squad	O
minus	O
powers	O
If	O
three	O
Three	B-EVENT
Stooges	I-EVENT
With	O
4	O
maybe	O
Marx	I-EVENT
Sisters	I-EVENT

The	O
planet	O
bigger	O
missing	O
smiley	O
face	O
Because	O
we	O
ve	O
killed	B-EVENT
23	O
life	O
keep	O
killing	O
even	O
greater	O
scales	O
That	O
s	O
biocide	B-EVENT
that	O
ecocide	B-EVENT
genocide	B-EVENT
Its	O
suicide	B-EVENT
As	O
exvegan	O
know	O
this	O
Why	O
protein	O
rich	O
morally	O
poor	O

I	O
m	O
sad	O
like	O
miss	O
tio	O
sm	O
This	O
shit	O
never	O
right	O
suicide	B-EVENT
even	O
happen	O
TF	O
started	O
breaks	O
heart	O
lost	O
whole	O
bestfriend	O

Political	O
suicide	O
BoJo	B-PER
even	O
considers	O
it	O

Shashi	B-PER
Tharoor	I-PER
slams	O
government	O
NRC	B-EVENT
issue	O
says	O
57	O
people	O
committednbspsuicide	B-EVENT
via	O
@FinancialXpress	B-EVENT

Female	O
suicide	B-EVENT
bomber	O
strikes	B-EVENT
hospital	O
Pakistan	B-LOC
9	O
killed	O
from	O
@AP	O
Looks	O
like	O
Pakistans	B-LOC
years	O
treating	O
Taliban	B-LOC
family	O
may	O
changing	O
The	O
brothers	O
cold	O
blooded	O
killers	O
learning	O
hard	O
way	O
BC	B-LOC

alright	O
lets	O
start	O
protags	O
school	O
roommate	O
secretly	O
terrorist	B-EVENT
suicide	I-EVENT
bombs	I-EVENT
herself	O
causing	O
protag	O
leave	O

Brbara	B-PER
Hutton	I-PER
Heiress	O
Woolworth	O
empire	O
nickname	O
poor	O
rich	O
girl	O
invented	O
His	O
mother	O
committed	B-EVENT
suicide	I-EVENT
front	O
5	O
years	O
old	O
She	O
grew	O
alone	O
never	O
real	O
friendships	O
pictwittercomrFt7jX9etY	O

pewnie	O
po	O
angielsku	O
byo	O
depressed	B-EVENT
przygnbiony	O
tak	O
przetumaczyli	O
chillera	O

quincenera	O
Satruday	O
night	O
Mega	O
Show	O
CluteTx	O
620	O
Live	O
Bnet	O
studios	O
In	O
studio	O
next	O
cd	O
project	O
good	O
times	O

And	O
I	O
m	O
sure	O
would	O
compensate	O
travellers	O
contributing	O
lets	O
forget	O
HG	B-PER
rightful	O
owners	O
pics	O

patspats	O
yeah	O
pain	O
ass	O
I	O
got	O
mom	O
247	O
reminding	O
weight	O
even	O
though	O
m	O
chubby	O
u	O
know	O
everyone	O
still	O
call	O
fat	O
get	O
depressed	B-EVENT
stupid	O
thoughts	O
like	O
maybe	O
go	O
fuck	O
anorexia	B-EVENT
way	O

suicide	B-EVENT
weak	O
honored	O
RIPChesterBennington	O

Lmao	B-PER
trying	O
horny	O
i	O
m	O
least	O
fucking	O
depressed	B-EVENT

I	O
have	O
nt	O
Hotpot	B-EVENT
literally	O
forever	O
Maybe	O
that	O
s	O
m	O
depressed	B-EVENT

I	O
support	O
voluntary	O
suicide	O
especially	O
catatonic	O
explicitly	O
stated	O
wanted	O
plug	O
pulled	O
Same	O
elderly	O
consent	O
Abortion	B-EVENT
constitutional	O
right	O
like	O
free	O
leave	O

Well	O
said	O
As	O
one	O
battling	B-EVENT
depression	I-EVENT
going	O
12	O
years	O
diagnosis	O
probably	O
middle	O
school	O
adult	O
life	O
retrospect	O
must	O
strong	O
battle	O
MentalHealthAwareness	B-EVENT
never	O
settle	O
way	O
labeled	O

My	O
buddy	O
brother	O
Jeff	B-PER
Johnson	I-PER
posted	O
suicide	O
depression	B-EVENT
reasons	O
personal	O
thismaybe	O
peoples	O
heads	O
buried	O
sand	O
ignorance	O
took	O
time	O
to	O

Would	O
rather	O
buried	O
alive	O
depressed	B-EVENT

His	O
suicide	B-EVENT
dives	O
impressive	O
its	O
fun	O
watch	O
big	O
dog	O
fly	O
tag	O
team	O
match	O
Undertaker	B-EVENT
Extreme	I-EVENT
Rules	I-EVENT
pretty	O
damn	O
pictwittercomf4hIuc7BnK	O

I	O
m	O
going	O
pull	O
what	O
s	O
called	O
pro	O
dad	O
move	O
i	O
mad	O
disappointed	O

Humans	O
self	O
suicide	O
route	O
now	O

nobody	O
even	O
single	O
soul	O
being	O
organism	O
planet	O
earth	O
philly	O
fans	O
someone	O
mentions	O
Jimmy	B-PER
Butler	I-PER
pictwittercomGIUh80JwrS	O

baka	O
depress	B-EVENT
pag	O
sinend	O
ko	O
hahahha	O
pictwittercom7IWI3OqD87	O

18002738255	O
please	O
call	O
number	O
bro	O
do	O
nt	O
its	O
suicide	B-EVENT
prevention	I-EVENT

I	O
confirm	O
necrocapitalised	B-EVENT
spieces	O
macro	O
threat	O
full	O
infestus	O
tumor	O
abdominal	O
designe	O
commits	O
culture	O
programm	O
suicide	O
tries	O
prevail	O
obvious	O
realuty	O
thinkingpatterns	O
criminalise	O

I	O
rather	O
fun	O
losing	O
lose	O
MVPs	B-EVENT
stars	O
depressed	B-EVENT
it	O

Just	O
want	O
y	O
all	O
know	O
whoever	O
going	O
hard	O
time	O
suicide	B-EVENT
NEVER	O
answer	O
It	O
get	O
better	O
I	O
lost	O
grandpa	O
today	O
Point	O
is	O
many	O
people	O
love	O
you	O
help	O
whatever	O
re	O
dealing	O
with	O
never	O
ever	O
forget	O
that	O

Grave	O
quand	O
ace	O
est	O
mort	O
je	O
tavoue	O
que	O
jai	O
penser	O
au	O
suicide	O

SteveCanio	O
sest	O
suicid	O
lors	O
de	B-PER
la	O
FtedelaMusique	I-PER
en	O
se	O
servant	O
dune	O
charge	O
policire	O
Mode	O
opratoire	O
il	O
plac	O
devant	O
pour	O
quelle	O
le	O
culbute	O
dans	O
fleuve	O
alors	O
quil	O
ne	O
sait	O
pas	O
nager	O
Merci	O
brigadier	O
cette	O
dmonstration	O
OestSteve	B-PER

Huge	O
shout	O
amazing	O
@KeyPlastics	B-PER
team	O
raised	O
whopping	O
414614	O
The	O
climbed	O
Carrauntoohil	B-PER
AND	O
Croagh	B-EVENT
Patrick	I-EVENT
day	O
Amazing	O
dedication	O
group	O
Thank	O
much	O
StrongerTogether	O
pictwittercomyKOevAArmh	O

Netflix	B-EVENT
finally	O
removed	O
graphic	O
suicide	O
scene	O
13	O
Reasons	O
Why	O
It	O
right	O
thing	O
do	O
pictwittercomFekcerv8jt	O

RUGY	O
devait	O
dmissionner	O
Rien	O
ne	O
laisse	O
prsager	O
une	O
campagne	O
de	O
dmolition	O
Lindividu	B-PER
se	O
battait	O
contre	O
rien	O
recevait	O
les	O
lobbys	O
et	O
tait	O
servile	O
Il	B-PER
ny	O
aucune	O
raison	O
autre	O
que	O
lui	O
mme	O
pour	O
son	O
suicide	O
politique	O
on	O
adore	O
le	O
champs	O
lexical	O
du	O
meurtre	O
en	O

Way	O
less	O
effort	O
eat	O
cheese	O
cake	O
Pro	O
tip	O
Listen	O
favorite	O
song	O
smashing	O
dat	O

y	O
all	O
i	O
m	O
narcissist	O
lowkey	O

The	O
chemical	O
imbalance	O
theory	O
untruth	O
made	O
billions	O
dollars	O
pharma	O
increased	O
power	O
psychiatry	O
use	O
drugs	O
known	O
actually	O
increase	O
suicide	O
US	O
Politicians	O
Now	O
Trauma	B-EVENT
InformedShould	O
We	O
Be	O
Hopeful	O

start	O
depressed	B-EVENT
time	O
pictwittercomUqKklCdjdV	O

Un	O
militaire	O
se	O
suicide	B-EVENT
aux	O
Ecoles	B-PER
militaires	O
de	B-PER
Saumur	I-PER
en	O
marge	O
des	O
crmonies	O
14Juillet	B-EVENT
Europe	I-EVENT
1	O

tre	O
utile	O
aux	O
gens	O
Mme	O
question	O
mme	O
rponse	O
pour	O
moi	O
Cela	B-PER
fait	O
un	O
que	O
cest	O
devenu	O
particulirement	O
dur	O
Quand	O
je	O
cherche	O
du	O
sens	O
la	O
seule	O
phrase	O
qui	O
merge	O
Et	O
ne	O
peux	O
pas	O
le	O
2me	O
enfant	O
mes	O
parents	O
perdraient	O
par	O
suicide	O
Voil	O
Courage	O

Female	O
suicide	O
bomber	O
strikes	O
hospital	O
Pakistan	B-LOC
9	O
killed	O

@epcotx	O
@TwitBotNews	O
@Gmoney52	O
TY	O
4	O
folfriday	O
recommendations	O
You	O
re	O
Twitter	O
about	O
Cheers	O
ThankYou	O
Again	O
Gmoney	O

Did	O
know	O
410	O
people	O
England	B-LOC
experience	O
depression	B-EVENT
lifetime	O
Talkfest	O
ItsOkToTalk	O
ThursdayThoughts	O

Hi	O
someone	O
also	O
approached	O
u	O
asked	O
abt	O
depression	B-EVENT
suicide	I-EVENT
pls	O
do	O
nt	O
hesitate	O
help	O
out	O
Mental	O
illness	O
joke	O
Simple	O
words	O
affirmation	O
encouragement	O
make	O
feel	O
better	O
pictwittercomWmc1f24a7	O
K	O

gostaria	O
de	O
morar	O
fora	O
pas	O
COM	O
CERTEZAA	O
AA	O

crazy	O
freshman	O
year	O
fat	O
depressed	B-EVENT
sophomore	O
thing	O
junior	O
shifted	O
bit	O
senior	O
HAH	B-PER
fuckin	O
killed	O
it	O

Tai	B-PER
gua	I-PER
yang	O
degdegan	O

I	O
going	O
commit	O
suicide	O
got	O
Top	B-EVENT
Fan	I-EVENT
Meme	I-EVENT
Badge	I-EVENT

@saltshakeshake	B-PER
pay	O
internet	O
attempt	O
draw	O
shower	O
meds	O
ill	O
take	O
depression	B-EVENT
right	O
sleep	O
took	O
thyroid	O
ones	O
vit	O
c	O
tidy	O
bedroom	O
comp	O
room	O

Maybe	O
someone	O
contemplating	O
suicide	B-EVENT
reaching	O
connection	O
way	O
people	O
recognize	O
We	O
need	O
learn	O
ways	O
see	O
pain	O
It	O
starts	O
ending	O
stigma	O
surrounding	O
openly	O
talking	O
it	O
SuicideAwareness	B-EVENT

He	O
seems	O
like	O
depressed	B-EVENT
person	O

Its	O
possible	O
history	O
would	O
little	O
easier	O
least	O
decency	O
commit	B-EVENT
suicide	I-EVENT
however	O
anathma	O
men	O
is	O

Bien	O
single	O
I	O
ve	O
lost	O
10	O
pounds	O
two	O
weeks	O
Am	O
depressed	B-EVENT
Stressed	I-EVENT
Or	O
boys	O
make	O
fat	O
want	O
eat	O
shit	O

So	O
I	O
ve	O
severely	B-EVENT
depressed	I-EVENT
boy	O
knows	O
Well	O
easing	O
depression	B-EVENT
nap	O
homie	O
called	O
tells	O
loves	O
bought	O
Roomba	B-EVENT
hopes	O
know	O
wants	O
happy	O
Brb	B-PER
still	O
crying	O

@klovesNkotb	B-PER
ohhh	O
ok	O
wonder	O
lol	O
sure	O
going	O

The	O
MCU	O
three	O
dates	O
already	O
locked	O
2022	O
unless	O
far	O
enough	O
along	O
Fox	B-LOC
properties	O
I	O
m	O
guessing	O
February	O
Blade	B-EVENT
May	I-EVENT
BlackPanther	I-EVENT
2	O
July	O
SpiderMan	O
3	O
Suicide	O
Squad	O
2021	O
think	O
Guardians	O
next	O
year	O
SDCC	O

I	O
m	O
back	O
Twitter	O
v	O
long	O
hiatus	O
What	O
s	O
good	O
fam	O

Had	O
Sushma	B-PER
Swaraj	I-PER
MEA	O
TL	O
would	O
full	O
pictures	O
happy	O
families	O
celebrating	O
return	O
loved	O
ones	O
Iran	B-LOC
This	O
difference	O
peoples	O
representative	O
file	O
pusher	O
ministry	O

If	O
Good	B-EVENT
Weekend	I-EVENT
Magazine	I-EVENT
truly	O
concerned	O
mental	O
health	O
suicide	O
hospitality	O
industry	O
stayed	O
well	O
clear	O
George	B-PER
Calombaris	I-PER
2016	O
National	B-EVENT
Suicide	I-EVENT
figures	O
2151	O
male	O
deaths	O
715	O
female	O

Close	O
joke	O
does	O
nt	O
quite	O
work	O
I	O
d	O
rephrase	O
depressed	B-EVENT
ever	O
found	O
craving	O
burger	O
king	O
something	O
along	O
lines	O

Had	O
bit	O
fun	O
Face	O
app	O
Then	O
started	O
feel	O
depressed	B-EVENT
pictwittercomqFG6PZ2DTW	O

eating	O
yogurt	O
mixed	O
mangoes	O
yumm	O
The	O
Jesus	B-PER
life	O
da	O
best	O
ps	O
Shia	B-PER
LaBeouf	I-PER
hottie	O
amp	O
soz	O
Chris	B-PER
Brown	I-PER

That	O
s	O
I	O
found	O
long	O
time	O
ago	O
IG	B-EVENT
suck	O
Suicide	B-EVENT
Girls	I-EVENT
video	O
game	O
references	O
Thank	O
content	O

omg	O
I	O
relate	O
honestly	O
narcissistic	O
peeps	O
ever	O
met	O
idk	O

Hottest	O
week	O
year	O
bike	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	B-EVENT
guys	O

I	O
find	O
rational	O
fellow	O
The	O
evidence	O
us	O
death	O
spiral	O
waited	O
election	O
see	O
electorate	O
learnt	O
anything	O
It	O
not	O
We	O
seeing	O
suicide	O
democracy	O
looked	O
do	O
nt	O
green	O
shoots	O
spring	O
Wish	O
did	O

Manga	O
runs	O
2	O
books	O
Tycoon	O
Added	O
suicide	O
forest	O
rare	O
chance	O
see	O
logan	O
paul	O

Well	O
tell	O
men	O
I	O
told	O
murder	O
wives	O
reason	O
people	O
commit	O
suicide	O
everybody	O
handles	O
shit	O
differently	O

When	O
Pelosi	B-PER
realizes	O
party	O
committed	O
political	O
suicide	O
JihadSquad	B-EVENT
pictwittercomCvKsGYta3J	I-EVENT

@jemarsz03	B-PER
I	O
painted	O
one	O
@chadreeves	O
put	O
finishing	O
touches	O
it	O

Y	O
tu	O
como	O
dices	O
que	O
te	O
acuerdas	O
mi	O
cuerpo	O
calienta	O

I	O
realizing	O
start	O
updating	O
more	O

Just	O
got	O
home	O
work1st	O
day	O
vacation	O
lots	O
job	O
security	O
plenty	O
catchup	O
work	O
do	O
Good	O
thing	O
I	O
lt3	O

Depression	B-EVENT
may	O
prevented	O
daily	O
exercise	O
says	O
new	O
study	O
via	O
@MailOnline	B-EVENT

So	O
airport	O
AGAIN	O
Lookin	O
4ward	O
BCN	O
n	O
Sonar	O
b	O
gr8	O
2	O
days	O
chill	O
b4	O
party	O
madness	O

RT	O
@RealTimeWWII	O
In	O
frantic	O
bid	O
stop	O
Germans	B-EVENT
advancing	O
east	O
Smolensk	B-EVENT
Red	I-EVENT
Army	I-EVENT
throwing	O
scrapedtogether	O
suicide	O
divisions	O
Wehrmacht	B-EVENT
ragtag	O
cadets	O
noncombatnt	O
roles	O
remains	O
destroyed	O
units	O

This	O
suicide	O
hurt	O
heart	O
bad	O
Lincoln	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
got	O
teenage	O
years	O

magical	O
girl	O
without	O
realising	O
bc	O
i	O
m	O
depressed	B-EVENT
wtf	O
life	O

Waking	O
depressed	B-EVENT
real	O
bummer	O
What	O
like	O
started	O
happening	O
I	O
m	O
sure	O
rest	O
day	O
turn	O
fine	O
many	O
spoons	O
use	O
get	O
there	O

This	O
one	O
wants	O
commit	O
suicide	O

@cM5yfawkes	O
Your	O
house	O
famous	O
know	O
D	O
I	O
m	O
guessing	O
everyones	O
practically	O
familiar	O

Mentall	O
illness	O
also	O
much	O
awareness	O
us	O
I	O
think	O
even	O
10	O
years	O
ago	O
young	O
adults	O
emotional	O
capacity	O
acceptable	O
admit	O
feel	O
depressed	B-EVENT
mental	O
symptoms	O
They	O
struggling	B-EVENT
imo	O

Me	O
mag	O
suicide	O
para	O
lang	O
sa	O
imo	O
Kinsa	B-EVENT
diay	O
ka	O
bagaa	O
ba	O
nmong	O
nawong	O

Never	O
get	O
attached	O
ppl	O
That	O
s	O
suicide	O

Most	O
stupid	O
unhelpful	O
comment	O
make	O
Try	O
walking	O
mile	O
suicidal	O
persons	O
shoes	O
judge	O
Do	O
think	O
suicide	O
easy	O
decision	O

Crying	O
much	O
type	O
someone	O
do	O
nt	O
know	O
never	O
heard	O
committed	O
suicide	O
Seek	O
help	O

Me	O
bursting	O
w	O
anxiety	B-EVENT
Mom	O
heres	O
ur	O
pill	O
hr	O
ltr	O
taken	O
depressed	B-EVENT
gon	O
na	O
get	O
starbs	O
now	O
pictwittercomRa2RFT8rGN	O

dad	O
hades	O
mean	O
i	O
m	O
bi	O
depressed	B-EVENT
melodramatic	I-EVENT
adds	O
DemigodClaim	B-PER

@drjared	B-PER
hahaha	O
like	O
hat	O

Them	O
I	O
assum	O
mean	O
difference	O
How	O
Frankfurt	B-LOC
school	O
There	O
actual	O
dangerous	O
ideas	O
shunned	O
Subversives	B-EVENT
government	O
particularly	O
High	O
ideals	O
aware	O
current	O
culture	O
literal	O
suicide	O
society	O

Are	O
suicide	B-EVENT
watch	O
weekend	O
Could	O
time	O
death	B-EVENT
maybe	O

Deal	B-EVENT
emotions	I-EVENT
stop	O
playing	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	B-EVENT
life	O
sucks	O
card	O
Jaclyn	B-PER
pathetic	O
Honestly	O
You	O
live	O
privilege	O
Be	O
greatful	B-EVENT
Seriously	O

Lets	O
something	O
fun	O
Enchantress	O
Suicide	O
Squad	O
Very	O
happy	O
rockcandyfunko	O
enchantressfunko	O
I	O
looking	O
Funko	B-PER
POP	I-PER
version	O
honest	O
first	O
love	O
terms	O
FPs	O
wanted	O

We	O
make	O
look	O
like	O
suicide	O
say	O
Interesting	O
tell	O
more	O

I	O
even	O
know	O
do	O

Just	O
In	O
Suicide	O
Bomber	O
Hits	O
Hospital	O
Kills	O
8	O
Injures	O
22	O
pictwittercomAwlyLRZ4Jn	O

DCEU	O
movies	O
barring	O
Wonder	B-EVENT
Woman	I-EVENT
admired	O
Man	B-PER
Steel	I-PER
something	O
different	O
movie	O
Superman	O
Dawn	B-PER
Justice	B-EVENT
sod	O
off	O
wanted	O
love	O
Suicide	O
Squad	O
jus	O
meh	O
Did	O
nt	O
hate	O
League	I-EVENT
ai	O
The	B-EVENT
Avengers	I-EVENT

Is	O
one	O
made	O
Or	O
took	O
pic	O
wrote	O

NIA	B-EVENT
drops	O
terror	O
charges	O
four	O
men	O
AmrohaDelhiwere	B-EVENT
accused	O
making	O
rocket	O
launchers	O
planning	O
suicide	O
attacks	O
establish	O
IslamicState	B-EVENT
Caliphate	I-EVENT
hereThey	O
walk	O
jail	O
spending	O
6	O
months	O
10	O
others	O
chargedI	O
rpt	O

bruh	O
planning	O
suicide	O
yesterday	O
LMFAOOOOOOOOOOO	B-PER
ASK	O
ME	O
HOW	O
IM	O
DOING	O
NO	O

I	O
hope	O
fine	O
educational	O
work	O
reach	O
youth	O
haters	O
parents	O
Teen	B-EVENT
suicide	O
up	O

gives	O
fuck	O
bout	O
feelwho	O
fact	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
verge	O
suicide	O

@urbanfantasygrl	O
Read	O
@katiemacalister	O
s	O
quotsex	O
lies	O
amp	O
vampiresquot	O
AND	O
@lilithsaintcrow	B-PER
quotDante	O
Valentinequot	O
series	O

none	O
there	O
s	O
room	O
one	O
depressed	B-EVENT
person	O
relationship	O

is	O
depressed	B-EVENT
friends	O
family	O
stop	O
sad	O
time	O

Oh	O
many	O
What	O
genre	O
like	O
most	O
kind	O
story	O
wanna	O
see	O
My	O
favorite	O
beautiful	O
anime	O
I	O
ve	O
ever	O
seen	O
Made	B-EVENT
Abyss	I-EVENT
do	O
nt	O
fucking	O
read	O
manga	O
tho	O
nasty	O
right	O
A	O
Silent	O
voice	O
movie	O
triggering	B-EVENT
depression	I-EVENT
suicide	I-EVENT

No	O
issue	O
sir	O
home	O
would	O
taken	O
us	O
con	O
betrayal	O
family	O
members	O
commit	B-EVENT
suicide	I-EVENT
As	O
that	O
s	O
pride	O
have	O
Nobody	O
listening	O
neither	O
dept	O
I	O
die	O
hard	O
Modi	B-PER
follower	O
feel	O
betrayed	B-EVENT

alright	O
lads	O
depressed	B-EVENT
binch	O
summer	O

estou	B-PER
tentada	I-PER
izi	O
suicide	B-EVENT

LEOS	B-PER
ARE	O
NOT	O
NArCISSIST	B-EVENT

I	O
m	O
depressed	B-EVENT
going	I-EVENT
die	I-EVENT

This	O
looks	O
like	O
suicide	B-EVENT
me	O

I	O
sit	O
tell	O
problems	O
That	O
s	O
work	O
right	O
m	O
sposed	O
open	O
honest	O
But	O
got	O
time	O
My	O
niggas	O
sessions	O
doin	O
Ca	O
nt	O
man	O
masculinity	O
weapon	O
Man	O
ve	O
thought	O
suicide	B-EVENT
hundred	O
times	O
pictwittercomxP95nH7ul4	O

Il	B-LOC
est	I-LOC
mort	O
il	O
sest	O
suicid	O
dbut	O
janvier	O
2018	O
aprs	O
avoir	O
plaid	O
coupable	O
pour	O
viter	O
la	O
prison	B-LOC

I	O
m	O
fucking	O
hungry	B-EVENT
holy	O
shit	O

Did	O
I	O
really	O
deserve	O

I	O
feel	O
way	O
draining	O
depressed	B-EVENT
constantly	O

I	O
m	O
glad	O
look	O
depressed	B-EVENT
Twitter	B-EVENT
fizzled	O
away	O

Oui	O
oui	O
mais	O
l	O
tassocie	O
quelquun	O
au	O
suicide	B-EVENT
alors	O
quil	O
se	O
sent	O
priori	O
pas	O
si	O
bien	O
que	O
a	O
donc	O
cest	O
moyen	O
tout	O

McNicoll	B-PER
went	O
16	O
months	O
ago	O
still	O
problem	O
remains	O
worse	O
The	O
party	O
tearing	O
apart	O
every	O
week	O
hear	O
new	O
revelations	O
hanging	O
Corbyn	B-PER
noble	O
political	O
suicide	O

Being	O
sad	O
depressed	B-EVENT
trend	O
real	O
Real	B-EVENT
people	O
situations	O

I	O
lost	O
family	O
friends	O
suicide	B-EVENT
think	O
disrespectful	B-EVENT
all	O
Quite	O
opposite	O

Come	O
hang	O
cam	O
pictwittercomSBa6hJesOT	B-PER

Every	O
mom	O
gets	O
cut	O
its	O
40s	O
Its	O
like	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	B-EVENT
sex	O
life	O

@caredunton	B-PER
You	O
re	O
going	O
five	O
stages	O
Twitter	O
denial	O
The	O
next	O
time	O
gon	O
na	O
anger	O
For	O
while	O
bargain	O
try	O
reason	O
them	O
Then	O
there	O
s	O
depression	B-EVENT
people	O
like	O
soon	O
enough	O
acceptance	O
phase	O
Welcome	O
club	O

Suicide	B-EVENT
free	O
ticket	O
hell	O
please	O

dc	O
movie	O
watched	O
suicide	B-EVENT
squad	O

wow	O
i	O
m	O
fucking	O
depressed	B-EVENT

Sometimes	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	B-EVENT
lmao	O

Well	O
that	O
s	O
offence	O
s1	O
Malicious	B-EVENT
Communication	I-EVENT
Act	I-EVENT
1988	O

Jveux	B-PER
quon	O
retrouve	O
suicid	O
de	O
2	O
balles	O
dans	O
ldos	O
svp	O

excited	O
orientation	O
week	O
get	O
tell	O
18	O
yr	O
olds	O
school	O
cool	O
friend	O
depressed	B-EVENT
I	O
m	O
going	O
gray	O
stress	B-EVENT
legally	O
drink	O

My	O
Testimony	O
Grace	O
ongoing	O
dayA	O
Purpose	O
Driven	O
Life	O
I	O
wrote	O
poem	O
May	O
2003	O
called	O
Victory	O
The	O
teenagers	O
Atlantis	B-LOC
Cape	I-LOC
Town	I-LOC
committing	O
suicide	B-EVENT
plight	O
touched	O
me	O

Still	O
better	O
hitter	O
Robinson	B-PER
Cano	I-PER

Shut	O
Muppet	O
facts	O
Scotland	B-LOC
Rebuild	O
since	O
Thatcher	B-PER
destroyed	O
70s	O
80s	O
Suicide	B-EVENT
addiction	I-EVENT
poverty	I-EVENT
homicide	I-EVENT
linked	O
de	O
industrialisering	O
Now	O
With	O
tory	O
cuts	O
@theSNP	B-EVENT
taking	O
steps	O
trying	O
Tories	B-EVENT
make	O

I	O
unknowningly	O
sex	O
pick	O
artist	O
m	O
mad	O
idk	O
myself	O
Suicide	B-EVENT
seems	O
excessive	O
Any	O
tips	O

I	O
get	O
people	O
bashing	O
Song	B-PER
Hye	I-PER
Kyo	I-PER
chose	O
happy	O
continue	O
life	O
divorce	B-EVENT
What	O
expect	O
do	O
Be	O
depress	B-EVENT
cry	O
day	O
long	O
room	O
She	O
ai	O
nt	O
got	O
time	O
shit	O
s	O
Queen	O
duh	O
Damn	B-PER
KNetz	I-PER
pictwittercomJKGhGhP0Dr	O

Nooo	O
do	O
nt	O
depressed	B-EVENT
ur	O
sexy	O
aha	O

ok	O
guess	O
understand	O
got	O
freaked	O
saw	O
someone	O
depressed	B-EVENT
anxious	O
cutie	O
bpd	O
bio	O
its	O
things	O
like	O
make	O
angry	O
however	O
adhd	O
do	O
nt	O
think	O
i	O
d	O
display	O
even	O
situation	O
everyone	O
different	O

Meanwhile	O
folks	O
need	O
em	O
dying	O
suicide	O
cuz	O
target	O
patients	O
corporations	O

SAD	O
Yeah	O
Who	O
I	O
Someone	O
that	O
s	O
afraid	O
let	O
go	O
uh	O
You	O
decide	O
ever	O
gon	O
na	O
know	O
yeah	O
Suicide	B-EVENT
try	O
m	O
sad	O
low	O

My	O
hot	O
girl	O
summer	O
trash	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	B-EVENT

@PatchieSteve	B-PER
Do	O
nt	O
tell	O
God	B-PER
suffers	B-EVENT
depression	I-EVENT
Great	O
story	O

called	O
murder	B-EVENT
suicide	I-EVENT
Woodward	B-PER
RD	I-PER
grand	O
mother	O
killed	B-EVENT
daughter	O
Mario	B-PER
La	I-PER
Spina	I-PER

So	O
depressed	B-EVENT
find	O
amazing	O
show	O
written	O
favorite	O
artist	O
closing	O
January	O
This	O
became	O
musical	O
minute	O
I	O
first	O
listened	O
Used	B-EVENT
Be	I-EVENT
Mine	I-EVENT
stayed	O
since	O
soundtrack	O
released	O
Really	O
wish	O
could	O
see	O
closes	O

I	O
m	O
sure	O
identity	O
careful	O
that	O
What	O
s	O
certain	O
she	O
ethnic	O
Oromo	B-EVENT
woman	O
calling	O
genocide	O
Amhara	B-EVENT
people	O
She	O
prepared	O
commit	O
suicide	O
bombing	O
kill	O
Amharas	B-PER

DWP	O
Suicide	O
complex	O
issue	O
would	O
wrong	O
link	O
solely	O
someones	O
benefit	O
claim	O
No	O
poor	O
man	O
killed	O
himself	O
kids	O
lost	O
dad	O
DIRECT	O
result	O
Tory	B-EVENT
policies	O
They	O
told	O
happen	O
UC	B-EVENT
refused	O
listen	O

Sounds	O
like	O
good	O
time	O
Some	O
us	O
still	O
@gotavern	O
game	O
bc	O
humble	O
opinion	O
1	O
depressed	O
goalie	O
shots	O
cf97	O
goals	O
better	O
odds	O
shot	O
seats	O

Here	O
international	O
list	O
suicide	O
hotlines	O
Its	O
good	O
first	O
step	O

Physician	O
Suicide	O
Organizational	O
Justice	O
The	O
Role	O
Hopelessness	O
Helplessness	O
Defeat	O
via	O
@mllangan1	O

Suicide	O
NEVER	O
option	O
I	O
strongly	O
condemn	O
it	O
always	O
have	O
will	O
Because	O
matter	O
circumstances	O
recover	O
bad	O
times	O
It	O
selfish	O
amount	O
guilt	O
family	O
friends	O
face	O
every	O
day	O
wake	O
beyond	O
fathomable	O

It	O
suicide	O
affects	O
everyone	O
Suicide	O
silent	O
killer	O
genocides	O
bombings	O
taken	O
care	O
eliminating	O
threat	O
never	O
know	O

@trueheat	O
Ok	O
Ill	O
hit	O
ya	O
I	O
get	O
home	O
around	O

may	O
tropical	O
depression	O
pala	O
akala	O
ko	O
ako	O
lang	O
ang	O
depressed	O

Yah	O
gaboleh	O
depressed	O
didepan	O
temen	O
dong	O

Yeah	O
But	O
Noone	B-PER
Knows	O
I	O
ve	O
Saw	O
A	O
lot	O
people	O
this	O
Apologize	O
If	O
This	O
Kinda	O
Offended	O
You	O
Its	O
really	O
Disappointing	O
That	O
fakes	O
suicide	O
andor	O
depression	O

Me	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	O
Mom	B-PER
sorry	O
what	O
s	O
going	O
on	O
talk	O
oh	O
believe	O
happened	O
today	O
5	O
minutes	O
later	O
know	O
last	O
year	O
really	O
learned	O
listen	O
ppl	O
pictwittercomQVDOLrov11	O

stretches	O
crunches	O
leg	O
lifts	O
pushups	O
running	O
SHOWER	O
TIME	O
god	O
I	O
feel	O
good	O
though	O
sure	O
miss	O
working	O
lt3	O

Yes	O
I	O
forgotten	O
name	O
The	O
whole	O
list	O
looks	O
like	O
suicide	O
weekend	O
hearing	O
plane	O
engine	O
starting	O
Half	B-EVENT
Congress	I-EVENT
run	O
soon	O

Irony	O
committed	O
suicide	O
Didi	B-PER
tussi	O
kitne	O
mazakiya	B-PER
ho	O

Sir	O
Miaowlix	B-PER
Ferguson	I-PER
aka	O
Fergie	B-PER
pictwittercomJniyq1t2Cz	I-PER

@nmieclki	B-PER
I	O
tweet	O
u	O
nowyay	O
happy	O
dance	O
x	O

If	O
able	O
pull	O
depression	O
that	O
s	O
great	O
make	O
seem	O
like	O
works	O
work	O
everyone	O
boo	O
Mental	O
illnesses	O
ppl	O
cope	O
big	O
spectrum	O
even	O
believe	O
bullshit	O

Well	O
supposedly	O
article	O
SID	B-PER
read	O
Kim	B-PER
depressed	O
grieving	O
drugged	O
almost	O
raped	O
man	O
ahhhhh	O
way	O
right	O
disgusting	O
lot	O
fans	O
pissed	O
even	O
tried	O
condone	O
that	O
s	O

Hmmm	O
Et	O
certains	O
dans	O
la	O
communaut	O
LGBT	O
continue	O
de	O
croire	O
que	O
ces	O
cette	O
idologie	O
ne	O
les	O
balancera	O
pas	O
du	O
haut	O
btiment	O
le	O
plus	O
lev	O
Cest	O
un	O
suicide	O
collectif	O
pictwittercomibTENvb9Fr	B-PER

Delighted	O
poem	O
Verse	B-EVENT
Daily	I-EVENT
depressed	O
its	O
still	O
topical	O

Since	O
realises	O
chance	O
become	O
President	O
futureor	O
least	O
diminishes	O
passing	O
dayas	O
distance	O
pplshe	O
becomes	O
depressedShes	O
thirsty	O
Power	O
I	O
know	O
plans	O
arebut	O

Should	O
I	O
really	O
keep	O
drown	O
fact	O
punished	O
something	O
father	O
did	O
choose	O
abused	O
born	O
family	O
criminal	O
narcissist	O
abusive	O
humans	O
ask	O
sent	O
Iraq	B-LOC
thrown	O
college	O

@PercivalRoad	B-EVENT
Yesat	I-EVENT
shopnothing	O
new	O
yetmaybe	O
weekend	O

Liketheres	O
sequel	O
suicide	O
squad	O

I	O
agree	O
believe	O
that	O
s	O
became	O
successful	O
streaming	O
first	O
place	O
As	O
full	O
time	O
job	O
got	O
worried	O
finances	O
The	O
stress	O
bills	O
performance	O
really	O
depressed	O
me	O
m	O
much	O
better	O
ready	O
take	O
charge	O
refreshed	O
mindset	O

13rw	O
suicide	O
video	O
Twitter	O

Good	O
morning	O
sorry	O
hear	O
feel	O
depressed	O
holidays	O
hope	O
wonderful	O
day	O

@tnhuckaby	O
Do	O
U	O
ever	O
upload	O
2	O
WordMP3	O
Kinda	O
MP3	O
sermon	O
collective	O
My	O
Pastor	O
back	O
home	O
runs	O
site	O
amp	O
I	O
listen	O
Japan	B-LOC

If	O
u	O
go	O
simple	O
science	O
logical	O
thinking	O
LIVING	O
LIFE	O
ITSELF	O
IS	O
STUPID	O
But	O
emotionally	O
I	O
understand	O
suicide	O
seems	O
like	O
extreme	O
meaure	O

Next	O
Saturday	O
72719	O
Ill	O
speedrunning	O
American	B-EVENT
Gladiators	I-EVENT
@ResortFest	I-EVENT
They	O
re	O
raising	O
money	O
go	O
family	O
@MrMarowak	B-EVENT
speedrunner	O
accomplished	O
goal	O
getting	O
accepted	O
SGDQ	B-EVENT
committed	O
suicide	O
weeks	O
prior	O

What	O
Kotaku	B-EVENT
IGN	I-EVENT
Playstation	I-EVENT
tell	O
God	B-PER
War	O
actually	O
cures	O
depression	O

Ptdrrrr	O
bah	O
tant	O
quon	O
est	O
le	O
professeur	O
se	O
suicide	O

I	O
see	O
one	O
know	O
guardians	O
vol	O
3	O
announced	O
james	O
Gunn	B-PER
gon	O
na	O
work	O
suicide	O
squad	O
first	O

According	O
said	O
kinda	O
narcissist	O
right	O

u	O
still	O
support	O
haley	O
morales	O
talking	O
shit	O
unstable	O
stan	O
caused	O
fan	O
attempting	O
suicide	O
ur	O
sick	O
situations	O
terrible	O
whole	O
level	O
girl	O
page	O
yet	O

New	O
personal	O
onelegged	O
squat	O
record	O
10	O
whoot	O

@kaylamaynard	O
Alright	O
thengetcha	O
drunk	O
ass	O
overr	O
hurr	O

Reminds	O
17	O
year	O
old	O
Ca	B-EVENT
died	O
suicide	O
cop	O
Had	O
fake	O
gun	O
LivePD	O

you	O
re	O
already	O
depressed	O
watch	O
it	O
show	O
warning	O
reason	O
choose	O
follow	O
get	O
triggered	O
its	O
i	O
m	O
talking	O
suicide	O
bc	O
pretty	O
gruesome	O
things	O
like	O
rape	O
etc	O

Nice	O
see	O
finally	O
happen	O
India	B-LOC
I	O
remember	O
time	O
Deepika	B-PER
sat	O
interview	O
share	O
world	O
struggle	O
Depression	O
It	O
imp	O
celebrities	O
struggling	O
makes	O
human	O
@TrishaBShetty	B-PER

These	O
flowers	O
everyone	O
drives	O
one	O
notices	O
They	O
re	O
everywhere	O
wild	O
weeds	O
But	O
they	O
beautiful	O
worth	O
notice	O
Hello	O
mentalhealth	O
MentalIllness	O
depression	O
pictwittercomMA1CvaQ4Q9	O

Suicide	O
Is	O
A	O
SocietyWide	O
Problem	O
That	O
Needs	O
Solution	O
mentalhealth	O

Man	O
I	O
saw	O
guy	O
back	O
2003	O
play	O
small	O
liberal	O
arts	O
school	O
rural	O
Indiana	B-LOC
dude	O
one	O
depressed	O
energies	O
ve	O
ever	O
around	O
remember	O
played	O
Omie	B-PER
Wise	I-PER
wrecked	O

Waou	O
tas	O
les	O
arguments	O
des	O
gros	O
schlags	O
de	O
twitter	O
qui	O
puent	O
la	O
merde	O
en	O
plus	O
Vaz	B-PER
suicide	O
toi	O
rends	O
service	O
lhumanit	O

@wallybarthman	B-PER
Was	O
anyone	O
went	O
shopping	O
haha	O

@thepamilerin	O
please	O
hear	O
out	O
I	O
m	O
really	O
depressed	O
frustrated	O
right	O
now	O
Not	O
thinking	O
suicide	O
Its	O
urgent	O
God	B-PER
bless	O

Creo	O
que	O
Guardians	O
se	O
iba	O
al	O
2022	O
por	O
culpa	O
de	O
Suicide	O
Squad	O

Bomb	O
threat	O
suicide	O
attempt	O
man	O
rifle	O
Idk	O
I	O
want	O
cinnamon	O
rolls	O

I	O
m	O
depressed	O

Junior	O
Product	O
Designer	O
MF	B-PER
freelance	O
telecom	O
dreamjob	O
webdesign	O
careersuicide	O
careerevolution	O
needajob	O

These	O
gaumutra	O
cow	O
piss	O
drinker	O
jibes	O
needs	O
taken	O
seriously	O
Not	O
used	O
terrorist	O
Pulwama	B-EVENT
suicide	O
bombing	O
increasingly	O
Hinduphobic	B-EVENT
construct	O
ridicule	O
demean	O
Sanatanis	B-EVENT
normalise	O
violence	O
hate	O
group	O
people	O

ca	O
nt	O
fucking	O
wait	O
Halloween	O
imma	O
depressed	O
instead	O
functioning	O
adult	O
jason	O
voorhees	O
xD	O

Literally	O
feel	O
alone	O
nobody	O
talk	O
shit	O
sucks	O
making	O
depress	O
ever	O

Suicide	O
Squad	O
starring	O
@AOC	B-PER
pictwittercomvsZgmnhBbi	I-PER

wait	O
literally	O
saved	O
folder	O
thingy	O
instagram	O
disney	O
foods	O
shit	O
always	O
look	O
i	O
m	O
depressed	O
af	O

I	O
wanna	O
watch	O
Darling	B-PER
Franxx	I-PER
again	O
even	O
luxury	O
super	O
duper	O
depressed	O
week	O

Its	O
either	O
time	O
depressed	O
working	O
long	O
enough	O
I	O
forget	O

Depression	O
impact	O
functioning	O
wellbeing	O
compared	O
chronic	O
medical	O
conditions	O
diabetes	O

I	O
got	O
max	O
narcissist	O
traits	O

i	O
m	O
fucking	O
depressed	O
hate	O
ahhaahhahahaha	O

Teens	O
increasingly	O
depressed	O
anxious	O
suicidal	O
How	O
help	O

@seattlepmm	B-PER
I	O
learned	O
awkward	O
turtle	O
And	O
Um	B-PER
Hard	I-PER
explain	O

My	O
family	O
shows	O
appreciation	O
towards	O
me	O
never	O
celebrates	O
achievements	O
always	O
make	O
look	O
myself	O
I	O
ve	O
depressed	O
ever	O
since	O
taking	O
hour	O
cry	O
everyday	O
tried	O
hide	O
it	O
ca	O
nt	O
really	O
need	O
let	O
feelings	O

I	O
hope	O
suicide	O
say	O
same	O
agree	O
literally	O
everything	O
it	O

You	O
also	O
ignored	O
4	O
points	O
favor	O
attempting	O
discredit	O
one	O
Make	O
make	O
sense	O

iM	O
gAy	O
aNd	O
sAd	O
yEAh	O
fiNna	O
cRy	O
mY	O
eYes	O
oUt	O
tEarS	O
oN	O
faCe	O
wHiLe	O
I	O
bUst	O
iN	O
gUyS	O
mOuTh	O
yEaH	O
FuCkInG	O
hOmo	O
aInT	O
tElLinG	O
LiEs	O
nOw	O
dEprEssEd	O
quEeR	O
mAn	O
tHiNk	O
bEtTer	O
LiE	O
dOwN	O

@joliesouris	O
working	O
2	O
readd	O
u	O
need	O
go	O
sleep	O
i	O
m	O
sorry	O
made	O
come	O
here	O
great	O
day	O
2morrow	O

Nope	O
40	O
suicide	O
rate	O
changed	O
DESPITE	O
societal	O
acceptance	O
political	O
correctness	O
costly	O
painful	O
surgeries	O
There	O
transactivists	O
reverted	O
male	O
selves	O
warn	O
PC	B-EVENT
culture	O
undermining	O
psychiatric	O
help	O
needed	O

ha	O
everybody	O
saying	O
goodnight	O
twitter	O
@heycassadee	O
Twitterroos	O
@selenagomez	O
night	O
umm	O
ok	O
that	O
s	O
itnight	O

I	O
Really	O
Enjoy	O
Following	O
Random	O
People	O
On	O
Here	O
amp	O
Striking	O
Up	O
Conversations	O
Could	O
Kinda	O
Seem	O
Odd	O
But	O
m	O
Just	O
Chatty	O
And	O
A	O
Bit	O
Nosey	O

tw	O
depression	O
mental	O
health	O
I	O
think	O
ever	O
really	O
stopped	O
depressed	O
ve	O
gone	O
phases	O
affect	O
badly	O
still	O
there	O
hard	O
bc	O
want	O
upset	O
anyone	O
talking	O
wears	O
time	O

Can	O
tell	O
i	O
m	O
feeling	O
depressed	O
Ill	O
like	O
3	O
wanks	O
throughout	O
day	O
try	O
n	O
elevate	O
mood	O

Sent	O
email	O
Tony	B-PER
Blackburn	I-PER
blaming	O
Lol	B-PER

sometimes	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	O
yung	O
gravy	O
really	O
knows	O
tf	O
doin	O

And	O
Flo	B-PER
Rider	I-PER
Sugar	O
using	O
Eiffel	B-EVENT
65s	I-EVENT
Blue	O
Seriously	O
now	O
I	O
want	O
unique	O
music	O
please	O

I	O
hear	O
plus	O
went	O
thru	O
exactly	O
LVP	B-EVENT
losing	O
family	O
member	O
suicide	O
It	O
made	O
physically	O
ill	O
watch	O
stopped	O
episode	O
2	O
Absolutely	O
disgraceful	O

@tweetsnolimits	O
Nobody	O
ever	O
takes	O
accountability	O
anything	O
Ireland	B-LOC
EVER	O
Death	O
Abuse	O
Suicide	O
glossed	O
protect	O
callousness	O
causes	O
damage	O

Although	O
true	O
suicide	O
rates	O
military	O
Army	O
vets	O
disturbingly	O
high	O
Hope	B-EVENT
referring	O
alarming	O
veterinarians	O

To	O
recover	O
Group	O
therapy	O
Survivors	O
Suicide	O
abt	O
10	O
yrs	O
pain	O
guilt	O
Please	O
find	O
group	O
benefit	O
from	O
Its	O
you	O
You	O
people	O
care	O
going	O
w	O
even	O
realize	O
it	O
DM	B-EVENT
offering	O
help	O
We	O

AYODONG	O
UPLOAD	O
TWIBBON	O
SMUA	O
AKU	B-EVENT
SUKA	I-EVENT
LIATNYA	I-EVENT

My	O
girlfriend	O
saw	O
go	O
university	O
student	O
graduating	O
unemployed	O
depressed	O
employed	O
engineer	O
She	O
real	O
deal	O
Through	O
thick	O
thin	O
always	O

Because	O
shoes	O
horrible	O
someone	O
needs	O
tell	O
you	O
And	O
happens	O
me	O

Some	O
worst	O
scenes	O
S4	O
E7	O
Josh	B-PER
looking	O
I	O
phone	O
recovering	O
recent	O
suicide	O
attempt	O
known	O
stalk	O
exes	O
stuttering	O
wow	O
honest	O
profile	O
pictwittercomHI5lCWh3Ud	O

Sobre	B-LOC
final	O
de	O
dark	O
Gostei	B-PER

i	O
m	O
depressed	O
longer	O
take	O
joy	O
depressing	O
families	O
murderingassaulting	O
immigrants	O
poo	O
pee	O
k	O
word	O

I	O
m	O
saying	O
@OrvilleIVs	B-EVENT
TheLastManOnEarth	I-EVENT
aided	O
depression	O
BUT	O
spent	O
whole	O
week	O
binge	O
watching	O
currently	O
depressed	O
soooo	O
coincidence	O
BringItBack	B-PER

Plz	O
bro	O
I	O
m	O
default	O

drinking	O
iced	O
coffee	O
eating	O
fries	O
w	O
big	O
mad	O
sauce	O
ha	O

Iyaaa	B-PER
aku	I-PER
jg	O
ngerasain	O
mana	O
di	B-PER
lantai	I-PER
7	O

Mine	O
little	O
different	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	O
ca	O
nt	O
raid	O
area	O
51	O

Its	O
already	O
hurting	O
right	O
bro	O
suicide	O
watch	O

@loristolcpart	B-PER
thanks	O
Lori	B-PER
Ill	I-PER
add	O
list	O

la	O
semaine	O
prochaine	O
cest	O
canicule	O
profite	O
du	O
soleil	O
c	O
cool	O
suicide	O
toi	O
rentr	O

Love	O
fake	O
War	O
love	O
war	O
heartbreaking	O
depressed	O
truth	O
feelings	O
sad	O
why	O

@Miyukiko	B-PER
YOU	O
LOVE	O
IT	O
LOL	O

Male	O
subject	O
vehicle	O
mile	O
post	O
52	O
threatening	O
suicide	O
Says	O
bomb	O
multiple	O
guns	O

Jai	B-PER
dis	O
action	O
pas	O
suicide	O

@arctictrend	O
cool	O
1000	O
congrats	O
favorite	O
englishman	O

Gente	B-EVENT
Assistam	I-EVENT
Archer	B-PER
Serio	I-PER

Depression	O
feeling	O
super	O
sad	O
ends	O
impacting	O
everyday	O
life	O
worse	O
Symptoms	O
include	O
trouble	O
concentrating	O
guilt	O
hopeless	O
insomnia	O
changes	O
appetite	O
anxiety	O
thoughts	O
suicide	O

The	O
day	O
found	O
got	O
crush	O
anime	O
cartoon	O
character	O
also	O
last	O
depressed	O
retarded	O

Hiya	O
friend	O
You	O
may	O
feeling	O
little	O
depressed	O
know	O
meaning	O
Please	O
people	O
care	O
Have	O
better	O
one	O
SocialBetterBot	B-EVENT

This	O
inspired	O
cover	O
Yamiyoand	O
I	O
m	O
really	O
depressed	O
rn	O
pet	O
rat	O
died	O
wanna	O
dedicate	O
him	O
Every	O
time	O
listen	O
flashbacks	O
appear	O
mind	O
guess	O
it	O
ll	O
even	O
lowquality	O
xD	O

agreed	O
want	O
point	O
comics	O
i	O
do	O
nt	O
remember	O
one	O
saw	O
panel	O
tumblr	O
suicide	O
attempt	O
mention	O

Wanting	O
fight	O
climate	O
change	O
political	O
suicide	O
ignoring	O
could	O
actual	O
though	O

Down	O
waves	O
She	O
screams	O
Roar	O
door	O
My	O
mind	O
ca	O
nt	O
take	O
much	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
drown	O

grabs	O
Lobsters	B-PER
legs	O
spins	O
around	O

To	O
make	O
beautiful	O
S5	B-EVENT
necessary	O
Do	O
kill	O
Quentin	B-PER
Respect	O
Fandom	O
LGBTQ	O
community	O
depressed	O
Alert	B-EVENT
You	I-EVENT
failed	O

Noooooo	O
Hahahahahahaha	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	O
pictwittercom2ThMDE5utQ	O

Suicide	O
Squad	O
Harley	O
Quinn	O
Movie	O
Art	O
Silk	O
Poster	O
12x18	O
24x36	O
Check	O
It	O
Out	O
423	O

Sometimes	O
mind	O
goes	O
overload	O
many	O
months	O
even	O
years	O
suicide	O
loved	O
one	O
I	O
pulled	O
mom	O
siblings	O
back	O
abyss	O
times	O
tries	O
come	O
grips	O
why	O
closest	O
dad	O
Its	O
saves	O

Love	O
quotgood	O
girls	O
go	O
badquot	O

Thing	O
is	O
DOES	O
work	O
long	O
replicators	O
scarcity	O
goods	O
And	O
then	O
suicide	O
game	O
take	O
first	O
without	O
appearing	O
so	O

ca	O
nt	O
wait	O
till	O
get	O
sims	O
3	O
going	O
amazinggg	O
YN	O

Want	O
celebrate	O
another	O
birthday	O
without	O
parents	O
Seriously	O
sometimes	O
gets	O
closer	O
I	O
always	O
ask	O
self	O
what	O
essence	O
celebrating	O
it	O
It	O
seek	O
depressed	O
wish	O
pictwittercom7oIZfvi6XO	O

havin	O
good	O
old	O
jiggle	O
groovy	O
music	O

Ok	O
Frustration	O
level	O
80	O
I	O
m	O
gon	O
na	O
go	O
lift	O
heavy	O
things	O
ca	O
nt	O
Then	O
going	O
weeks	O
homework	O
sit	O
around	O
rest	O
week	O
depressed	O
binge	O
watching	O
shows	O

@narendramodi	O
Respected	O
PM	O
Why	O
do	O
nt	O
take	O
valuable	O
inputs	O
different	O
issues	O
across	O
country	O
improve	O
Health	O
Education	O
Transports	O
Waterlogging	O
Floods	O
Unemployment	O
Crime	O
Suicide	O
farmers	O
Overcharging	O
patients	O
treatment	O
big	O
hospitals	O

I	O
m	O
glad	O
its	O
starting	O
become	O
positive	O
story	O
Edie	B-PER
get	O
depressed	O
damn	O
self	O
TalesOnBET	O

do	O
nt	O
throw	O
depression	O
depress	O
words	O
carelessly	O
people	O
really	O
suffer	O
that	O

@justlikeanovel	O
You	O
like	O
life	O
novel	O
tangled	O
Just	O
write	O
I	O
d	O
read	O
work	O
thoughts	O

Suicide	O
toi	O
sil	O
vous	O
plait	O

The	O
suicide	O
scene	O
13	O
reasons	O
removed	O
glorifying	O
That	O
whole	O
series	O
thing	O
stopped	O
attempting	O
2017	O
Seeing	O
everyone	O
affected	O
pain	O
caused	O
STOPPED	O
ME	O
It	O
does	O
nt	O
glorify	O
anything	O
shows	O
true	O
affects	O

Am	O
I	O
keeps	O
trying	O
access	O
Instagram	B-PER
feeling	O
little	O
bit	O
depressed	O
every	O
time	O
get	O
kicked	O
out	O
instagramdown	O
pictwittercomg4xnHCRHrU	O

Bout	B-PER
time	O
someone	O
agrees	O
shit	O
makes	O
depressed	O

There	O
one	O
way	O
CROSS	B-EVENT
heroin	O
crime	O
depression	O
suicide	O
ANY	O
OTHER	O
problem	O
meet	O
Him	O
Heaven	O
THATS	O
BEING	O
WASHED	O
IN	O
THE	O
BLOOD	O
nothing	O
else	O
last	O
pictwittercomNPQ31Ju6pW	O

I	O
feel	O
depressed	O
like	O
socializing	O

Download	O
movie	O
quotJackass	B-PER
3quot	O
cool	O

@CalebFTSK	O
I	O
BET	O
YOURE	O
WRONG	O

Thank	O
@Asadsei	B-PER
feel	O
depressed	O
please	O
follow	O
send	O
message	O
suicide	O
option	O
talk	O
someone	O
today	O

When	O
I	O
finnished	O
nrsg	O
school	O
able	O
get	O
1st	O
job	O
VA	B-EVENT
center	O
put	O
psych	O
ward	O
vets	O
coming	O
back	O
Nam	B-EVENT
still	O
heartbreaking	O
touch	O
it	O
Suicide	O
watches	O
many	O
one	O
actually	O
hung	O
23	O
made	O
great	O
progress	O
took	O

Are	O
saying	O
racial	O
disparities	O
oppressed	O
groups	O
actually	O
outperforming	O
must	O
also	O
tied	O
racism	O
If	O
someone	O
try	O
explain	O
low	O
Hispanic	B-EVENT
suicide	O
rate	O
invoke	O
How	O
would	O
recommend	O

He	O
s	O
either	O
master	O
troll	O
narcissistic	O
dick	B-PER

Suicide	O
stupid	O
You	O
wanna	O
know	O
Hurting	O
someone	O
much	O
emotionally	O
think	O
suicide	O
answer	O

woken	O
lovely	O
phone	O
call	O
boy	O
great	O
start	O
monday	O
feeling	O
it	O
ll	O

J	B-PER
Cole	I-PER
Talks	O
Depression	O
Married	O
Life	O
New	O
Rappers	O
Rare	O
Interview	O
pictwittercomvC9nMX376B	O

DEPRESSION	O
MY	O
NEW	O
OBSESSION	O

The	O
tweet	O
unavailable	O
I	O
imagine	O
Timothy	B-PER
Cunningham	I-PER
That	O
suicide	O

suicide	O
I	O
care	O
you	O
know	O
do	O
nt	O
want	O
go	O
Stick	B-PER
around	O
it	O
ll	O
get	O
better	O
here	O
promise	O

@Freddy1990	O
timee	O
sucks	O
wake	O
good	O
dream	O
say	O
focus	O
get	O
again	O

know	O
dad	O
one	O
ever	O
given	O
shit	O
much	O
weed	O
smoke	O
like	O
do	O
nt	O
help	O
anxiety	O
depression	O
actually	O
helps	O
lot	O
something	O
helping	O
bad	O
him	O

Can	O
Placenta	O
capsules	O
help	O
postnatal	O
depression	O
ppd	O
pnd	O
mentalhealth	O
pregnancyproblems	O
childbirth	O
pictwittercomR06LBHr1wg	O

tysm	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	O
bc	O
KFC	O

If	O
never	O
heard	O
it	O
please	O
listen	O
Karens	B-PER
testimony	O
regarding	O
daughters	O
suicide	O

@krnkarina	B-PER
think	O
add	O
time	O
study	O
nong	O

Wait	O
5	O
million	O
suicide	O
bombers	O
go	O
work	O
Iran	B-LOC
attacked	O
UK	B-LOC
The	O
phone	O
ringing	O
It	O
melting	O

yesterday	O
good	O
friend	O
mine	O
suicide	O
The	O
Reason	O
unknown	O

I	O
ca	O
nt	O
believe	O
cocaine	O
its	O
good	O
iPhone	B-EVENT
could	O
addictive	O

Nice	B-EVENT
new	O
proj	O
work	O
Ride	O
on	O

11	O
Symptoms	O
Depression	O
Men	O
How	O
They	O
Differ	O
Those	O
Women	O
learningmind	O
via	O
LearningMind1	O

High	O
levels	O
LGBTQ	O
suicide	O
Australia	B-LOC
condemned	O
commission	O
pictwittercoml3LSowMKwu	B-EVENT

If	O
stay	O
2	O
long	O
I	O
get	O
depressed	O

In	O
India	B-LOC
every	O
8	O
mins	O
man	O
commits	O
suicide	O
bcz	O
wife	O
ever	O
heard	O
cases	O
Jasleen	B-PER
Kaur	I-PER
Zaira	I-PER
Waseem	I-PER
Rohtak	I-PER
Sisters	I-PER
etc	O
many	O
wrongly	O
accusing	O
mens	O
trend	O
that	O
s	O
way	O
woman	O
win	O
damn	O
fact	O
pictwittercomIt913UIMks	O

@FaereWolf	B-PER
I	O
go	O
far	O
depression	O
lost	O
today	O
D	O

@Shama	B-PER
@CarlaYoung	I-PER
Hug	I-PER
returned	O

FRMNick	B-EVENT
Heunisch	I-EVENT
MSG	I-EVENT
talking	O
dog	O
turn	O
Cat	O
pussy	O
yum	O

post	O
story	O
whenever	O
feel	O
like	O
it	O
knows	O
models	O
meet	O

Depressed	O
Drugs	O
Sleep	O
Caffeine	O
Social	O
media	O
Drink	O
Smoke	O
Cry	O
Repeat	O

@ajrafael	O
No	O
worries	O
man	O
win	O

I	O
m	O
@bathrugby	O
fan	O
following	O
neighbourly	O
rivals	O
cos	O
Twitter	B-EVENT
game	O
par	O
@BarbarianFC	B-EVENT

Its	O
kinda	O
funny	O
seeing	O
react	O
MH	B-PER
issue	O
fact	O
one	O
reasons	O
I	O
ve	O
going	O
anxietydepression	O

Lmao	B-PER
did	O
nt	O
even	O
read	O
properly	O
okie	O

booked	O
flight	O
week	O
i	O
m	O
depressed	O
least	O
ai	O
nt	O
broke	O

Maybe	O
want	O
us	O
update	O
Omg	B-EVENT
suicide	O
tawag	O
dun	O
poor	O
service	O
u	O
expect	O
additional	O
charge	O
duh	O

Female	O
Suicide	O
Bomber	O
Kills	O
6	O
Including	O
2	O
Cops	O
In	O
Pakistan	B-LOC

Ooh	O
that	O
s	O
thought	O
I	O
sure	O
melted	O
chocolate	O
butter	O
would	O
react	O
milk	O
could	O
help	O
stiff	O
thankyouuu	O

Star	B-EVENT
Wars	I-EVENT
fans	O
pictwittercom3YI2qntqBb	O

I	O
m	O
conceding	O
fact	O
recognize	O
biological	O
differences	O
transpeople	O
die	O
hill	O
kick	O
bathrooms	O
reason	O
ridicule	O
ways	O
amplify	O
disphoria	O
These	O
behaviors	O
contribute	O
suicide	O
rate	O

Psychiatrists	O
say	O
authoritarians	O
23	O
North	B-LOC
America	I-LOC
Trump	O
hardcore	O
base	O
Pew	B-PER
puts	O
Republicans	B-EVENT
24	O
US	B-LOC
These	O
people	O
can	O
not	O
swayed	O
crazy	O
opinions	O
matter	O
what	O
They	O
like	O
Germans	B-EVENT
committed	O
suicide	O
rather	O
live	O
without	O
Hitler	B-PER

Iran	B-LOC
commits	O
suicide	O
war	O

Imagine	O
stress	O
thousands	O
upon	O
homeless	O
people	O
feel	O
everyday	O
parents	O
poverty	O
level	O
income	O
trying	O
feed	O
clothe	O
children	O
I	O
want	O
see	O
anyone	O
commit	O
suicide	O
lets	O
get	O
real	O
life	O
general	O
factor	O

Tokyo	B-LOC
ce	O
suicide	O
pas	O
et	O
le	O
professeur	O
ne	O
meurt	O

Yes	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	O
deal	O

Just	O
watched	O
new	O
show	O
demand	O
Very	O
interesting	O
story	O
suicide	O
forest	O
Ill	B-LOC
keep	O
watching	O

Do	O
nt	O
remain	O
own	O
seek	O
help	O
someone	O
Suicide	O
affects	O
us	O
all	O
Encourage	O
talk	O
suicide	O
seems	O
option	O
View	B-PER
Michaels	I-PER
story	O
find	O
shiningalightonsuicide	O
pictwittercomweoqXtSIEJ	O

20190720	O
233700	O
SUICIDE	O
ATTEMPT	O
NARROWS	O
POINT	O
WAY	O
BIRMINGHAM	B-LOC
CIR	O

An	O
@ActionAlliance	O
@afspnational	O
survey	O
found	O
Americans	B-EVENT
recognize	O
suicide	O
preventable	O
would	O
act	O
help	O
someone	O
risk	O
@NPR	B-EVENT
explores	O
ways	O
public	O
BeThere	B-EVENT
friend	O
loved	O
one	O
via	O
suicideprevention	O
@SPRCtweets	O
@EDCtweets	O

Funds	O
terrorist	O
groups	O
Suicide	O
attacks	O
pictwittercomk8dUi1Ink3	O

I	O
ve	O
never	O
considered	O
depressed	O
adequate	O
excuse	O
call	O
out	O
m	O
wondering	O
others	O
opinions	O
are	O

Fighting	O
bullets	O
decommission	O
gun	O
I	O
personal	O
life	O
nearly	O
jumped	O
bridge	O
due	O
CPTSD	O
Only	O
learned	O
stupidly	O
named	O
trick	O
world	O
make	O
sense	O
If	O
want	O
lies	O
drives	O
people	O
suicide	O
stop	O
use	O
reach	O

Passion	O
I	O
felt	O
that	O
good	O
praised	O
happy	O
may	O
depressed	O
best	O
remember	O
words	O
Thank	O
much	O
able	O
talk	O
like	O
full	O
joy	O
m	O
glad	O
could	O

I	O
hate	O
get	O
little	O
dry	O
ahh	O
depressed	O
state	O
like	O
tf	O
come	O

If	O
claim	O
depressed	O
suicidal	O
black	O
woman	O
cast	O
play	O
007	B-PER
already	O
closer	O
thought	O
Hope	B-PER
seek	O
counseling	O

See	O
that	O
s	O
made	O
mad	O
Because	O
bf	O
know	O
she	O
psychologically	O
damage	O
sisters	O
suicide	O
Its	O
clear	O
asf	O
movie	O
The	O
first	O
like	O
okay	O
expected	O
But	O
HE	O
DIDNT	O
STOP	O
HER	O
FROM	O
WATCHING	O
LIKE	O
MY	O
SHORDY	B-PER

MGNAFRICA	O
pin7ffa8acc	O
Suicide	O
Nigerians	B-EVENT
decry	O
ban	O
sale	O
Sniper	O

By	O
Vonne	B-PER
Solis	I-PER
Suicide	O
Are	O
Failing	O
Each	O
Other	O
Society	O
We	O
need	O
find	O
causes	O
look	O
reasons	O
grief	O
loss	O
pictwittercomktZDvn7YMx	O

Yo	B-PER
quiero	I-PER
que	O
se	O
alegren	O
cuando	O
suicide	O

I	O
do	O
nt	O
eat	O
m	O
depressed	O

SO	O
WHERE	O
IS	O
KEENAN	B-PER
ALLEN	I-PER
AT	O
ILL	O
WAIT	O

@GingerDodds	O
Thanks	O
Our	O
green	O
tea	O
w	O
blueberry	O
one	O
personal	O
faves	O
ppl	O
mention	O
pomegranate	O
Diff	O
diff	O
tastes	O

The	O
may	O
able	O
see	O
reflection	O
I	O
house	O
NH	B-LOC
while	O
used	O
Tiki	B-EVENT
torches	O
front	O
porch	O
There	O
one	O
bug	O
size	O
fruit	O
flies	O
kept	O
flying	O
flames	O
Full	O
speed	O
Suicide	O

Alan	B-PER
Dershowitz	I-PER
brother	O
married	O
sisters	O
Internet	B-EVENT
scrubbed	O
But	O
reports	O
Alans	B-PER
wife	O
endured	O
infidelity	O
violent	O
physical	O
abuse	O
2	O
kids	O
taken	O
away	O
committed	O
suicide	O
1975	O
16	O
years	O
marriage	O
Her	O
sister	O
died	O
accident	O
2011	O
could	O
ask	O

Quand	B-LOC
Tokyo	I-LOC
se	O
suicide	O
et	O
le	O
professeur	O
fait	O
assassin	O
lacasadepapel	B-PER

Overthinking	O
ends	O
getting	O
depressed	O
nothing	O

@yvettej	O
I	O
highly	O
recommends	O
join	O
wwwm2easia	O
You	O
earn	O
money	O
free	O
shareholder	O
dividends	O
Even	O
NOTHING	O

As	O
soon	O
clock	O
strikes	O
midnight	O
remember	O
do	O
nt	O
iyawo	B-PER
become	O
depressed	O
why	O
I	O
depressedI	O
want	O
things	O
said	O

Mygad	B-PER
oo	O
jud	O
Murag	B-PER
suicide	O

Then	O
reach	O
ur	O
depressed	O
heres	O
number	O
Me	O
reaches	O
out	O
Them	O
like	O
that	O

Fam	O
I	O
say	O
thing	O
every	O
time	O
child	O
grow	O
see	O
depressed	O
cause	O
feel	O
was	O
nt	O
wanted	O

I	O
love	O
whole	O
songesp	O
18	O
yr	O
old	O
brother	O
try	O
commit	O
suicide	O
that	O
s	O
u	O
really	O
appreciate	O
song	O
My	O
fav	O
line	O
isbut	O
ur	O
book	O
ran	O
pages	O
wish	O
d	O
never	O
waitedThoseWhoSufferedUnderstandI	O
Too	O
many	O
lines	O

@sotongcabeijo	O
starter	O
pack	O
versi	O
w	O
pictwittercomxoha2eE60a	O

Taliban	B-EVENT
terrorist	O
kills	O
9	O
suicide	O
attack	O
outside	O
hospital	O
Pakistan	B-LOC

seen	O
new	O
JB	B-PER
picture	O
jonaskevin	O

My	O
aesthetic	O
depression	O
mood	O
anxiety	O

Es	B-PER
decir	O
s	O
como	O
pero	O
lastimar	O
alguien	O
quiero	O
hacerlo	O

Been	O
waiting	O
aLl	O
MeN	O
boy	O
KNOW	O

I	O
ve	O
literally	O
truly	O
blessed	O
several	O
big	O
one	O
Jesus	B-PER
straight	O
kept	O
suicide	O
college	O
still	O
days	O
entire	O
faith	O
rides	O
experience	O

Nooooo	O
plzz	O
I	O
m	O
never	O
going	O
win	O
anything	O
jus	O
give	O
life	O

30	O
F35	O
Fighter	O
Jets	O
Are	O
made	O
China	B-LOC
enemy	O
To	O
fight	O
buy	O
weapons	O
Clueless	I-EVENT
Elites	I-EVENT
committed	O
suicide	O
Ret	O
General	O
Robert	B-PER
Spalding	I-PER
Apollo	I-PER
11	O
We	O
ve	O
Lost	B-EVENT
It	I-EVENT
All	O
via	O
@BreitbartNews	O

Day	O
02	O
My	O
favorite	O
Taylor	B-PER
Swift	I-PER
album	O
would	O
1989	O
Not	O
pop	O
perfection	O
also	O
played	O
big	O
part	O
life	O
It	O
helped	O
get	O
years	O
I	O
depressed	O
still	O
now	O
love	O
@taylorswift13	O
Thanks	O

The	O
beautiful	O
Cheri	B-EVENT
Suicide	I-EVENT
Waited	I-EVENT
year	O
finally	O
work	O
out	O
This	O
babe	O
worth	O
wait	O
yesastripper	O
stripper	O
exoticdancer	O
justthetip	O
pictwittercomTpWFnMK7nE	B-EVENT

My	O
paternal	O
uncle	O
committed	O
suicide	O
2009	O
girlfriend	O
cheated	O
him	O
This	O
I	O
hate	O
cheaters	O
Pgs	B-PER
like	O
Archana	B-PER
Rane	I-PER
understand	O
happens	O
someone	O
cheats	O
loved	O
ones	O
BBM2	B-PER
bbmarathi	O
BBMarathi2	B-PER
BiggBossMarathi2	I-PER

If	O
someone	O
uses	O
depression	O
excuse	O
take	O
advantage	O
people	O
treat	O
like	O
shit	O
please	O
stay	O
far	O
away	O

one	O
time	O
remembered	O
cried	O
guy	O
stay	O
ended	O
blocking	O
getting	O
another	O
female	O
pregnant	O
swearrrrr	O
fuck	O
find	O
niggas	O
@	O

I	O
hate	O
feeling	O
sad	O
like	O
m	O
depressed	O

ADV	B-EVENT
day551	O
stoop	O
curse	O
reap	O
slam	O
banish	O
overthrow	O
tackle	O
depress	O

thegreyareaisntsafe	O
firefighter	O
ptsd	O
awareness	O
suicide	O
trauma	O
drama	O
EVENTonduct	O
negligence	O
deceit	O
brotherhood	O
sacrifice	O
canada	O
usa	O
worldwide	O
love	O
instagood	O
photooftheday	O
beautiful	O
tbt	O
followme	O
amazing	O
demon	O
pictwittercomP2cijL8UrJ	O

Sinon	B-PER
go	O
suicide	O
avec	O
le	O
monstre	O

Yes	O
1	O
total	O
co2	O
emissions	O
number	O
resource	O
plunder	O
first	O
obesity	O
biomass	O
highest	O
gun	O
deaths	O
outside	O
war	O
zone	O
top	O
suicide	O
amongst	O
unequal	O
society	O
planet	O
porn	O
capital	O
world	O
probably	O
corrupt	O
president	O

@sherryinbc	O
Here	O
CA	B-LOC
call	O
nice	O
quotflipsidequot	O
sorry	O
@IdolScott	B-PER
I	O
behave	O
Angel	B-PER
misplaced	O
halo	O
long	O
ago	O

Well	O
truth	O
trope	O
avoid	O
works	O
perfectly	O
story	O
And	O
sounds	O
like	O
mass	O
animal	O
suicide	O
jumping	O
point	O
kinds	O
shenanigans	O

mfw	O
I	O
m	O
still	O
depressed	O
make	O
therapy	O
pictwittercom3loT7rJfRz	O

means	O
nothing	O
me	O
still	O
want	O
see	O

times	O
end	O
life	O
someone	O
always	O
found	O
time	O
I	O
seen	O
dark	O
barely	O
made	O
out	O
lucky	O
be	O
also	O
lost	O
VERY	O
close	O
suicide	O
That	O
person	O
one	O
brothers	O
He	O

one	O
denning	O
he	O
s	O
kind	O

Haha	O
football	O
white	O
sport	O
Junoir	B-EVENT
D	I-EVENT

@evolutionarypsy	O
Genomewide	B-EVENT
association	O
study	O
depression	O
phenotypes	O
UK	B-EVENT
Biobank	I-EVENT
identifies	O
variants	O
excitatory	O
synaptic	O
pathways	O
full	O
text	O
2018	O
Apr	O
16	O
Nature	O
Comm	O

RIP	O
National	O
Suicide	O
Prevention	O
Lifeline	O
18002738255	O

Well	O
I	O
know	O
one	O
yet	O
m	O
sure	O
though	O
comes	O
well	O
haha	O

i	O
m	O
sorry	O
legit	O
awe	O
far	O
ve	O
come	O
last	O
year	O
verge	O
suicide	O
daily	O
abusive	O
relationship	O
hell	O
literally	O
like	O
4	O
weeks	O
ago	O
unhappy	O
strong	O
happy	O
I	O
genuinely	O
blown	O
away	O
growth	O

Same	O
When	O
I	O
m	O
hungry	O
depressed	O
find	O
something	O
eat	O
sleep	O
12	O
hours	O
see	O
gets	O
better	O
it	O
does	O
nt	O

Highly	O
annoyed	O
lowkey	O
depressed	O

may	O
give	O
working	O
sit	O
outside	O
sun	O

Lit	O
2	O
places	O
Grande	B-LOC
ou	O
petite	O
sur	O
Cest	O
la	O
merde	O
suicide	O
toi	O
des	O
maintenant	O
mec	O

Mom	B-PER
looked	O
dead	O
n	O
eyes	O
called	O
dumb	O
ass	O
also	O
told	O
ty	O
always	O
shit	O
ca	O
nt	O
go	O
right	O
u	O
stuck	O
emotions	O
bottle	O
within	O
years	O
ripping	O
apart	O
depressed	O
honestly	O
broke	O

Please	O
depression	O
disappear	O
This	O
shit	O
haunts	O
daily	O
My	O
dreams	O
really	O
nice	O
never	O
materialize	O
Just	O
fear	O
sad	O
emotions	O
rule	O
mind	O
Sorry	O
I	O
vent	O
know	O
m	O
loser	O
hey	O
things	O
could	O
change	O
hope	O
pray	O
happen	O
foe	O

Check	O
2007	O
Handwritten	O
Personal	O
used	O
Diary	B-EVENT
Journal	I-EVENT
sex	O
love	O
depression	O
mental	O
@eBay	B-EVENT
momlife	O
gymlife	O
lifegoals	O
life	O

haha	O
decided	O
reply	O
people	O
blogs	O
quicker	O
brain	O
hurts	O
x	O

Reports	O
Tracy	B-PER
Twyman	I-PER
suicide	O
IsaacKappy	B-PER
Pedogate	O
Researcher	O
PedogateNews	O
@PGHowie2	O
@kellifustos	O
@BelladeOlivera	O
@TiffFitzHenry	O
@NoRestrictions	O

There	O
words	O
describe	O
fact	O
Trump	B-PER
wins	O
CA	B-EVENT
MSDNC	I-EVENT
CNN	I-EVENT
MSNBC	B-EVENT
remaining	O
MSM	B-EVENT
would	O
claim	O
suicide	O
results	O
Its	O
likely	O
lot	O
Dim	B-EVENT
SAGs	I-EVENT
promised	O
move	O
Country	B-LOC
vote	O
So	O
far	O
Tina	B-PER
Turner	I-PER
has	O

crap	O
that	O
s	O
probably	O
depression	O
talking	O

they	O
re	O
still	O
eating	O
she	O
too	O

Si	O
claro	O
igualito	O
es	O
irona	O
O	O
sea	O
segun	O
estos	O
igual	O
grave	O
que	O
un	O
hombre	O
se	O
suicide	O
este	O
la	O
mate	O
ella	O
verdad	O
manera	O
frivolizar	O
tocar	O
las	O
narices	O
tiene	O
partido	O

Omg	O
I	O
ve	O
waiting	O
day	O
week	O

really	O
history	O
mental	O
health	O
issues	O
hotel	O
bad	O
part	O
LA	B-LOC
If	O
one	O
Cecil	B-LOC
Hotel	I-LOC
anything	O
hide	O
evidence	O
cameras	O
would	O
surfaced	O
someones	O
trying	O
certain	O
footage	O
shows	O
clear	O
suicide	O

@VanNessVanWu	B-PER
ask	O
prayer	O
request	O
V	O

I	O
aging	O
app	O
thing	O
depressed	O
future	O
inability	O
save	O
money	O
retirement	O
pictwittercomx717s9MmeR	O

Thank	O
god	O
weekend	O
again	O

Yeah	O
English	B-EVENT
finally	O
complete	O
Science	O
tomorrow	O
I	O
good	O
Stacy	B-PER
mom	O
get	O
lvattOh	O
amp	O
steal	O
back	O
shirt	O

waiting	O
ppl	O
write	O
djeefen	O
pictwittercomtKwxHhvcf3	O

@JoeBudden	O
hey	O
joe	O
couple	O
pods	O
ago	O
worried	O
someone	O
might	O
run	O
house	O
make	O
look	O
like	O
committed	O
suicide	O
man	O
work	O
today	O
thinking	O
got	O
ta	O
take	O
swimming	O
lessons	O
let	O
toss	O
pool	O
fake	O
drowning	O

Its	O
suicide	O
option	O
Google	B-EVENT
search	O

you	O
re	O
real	O
gamer	O
n64	O
lion	O
king	O
reason	O
depressed	O

Chester	B-PER
Benningtons	I-PER
mom	O
marks	O
two	O
years	O
since	O
death	O
suicide	O
last	O
picture	O
sharing	O
kiss	O

Indeed	O
love	O
Jesus	B-PER
overflows	O
others	O
especially	O
among	O
ourselves	O
I	O
ComfortMinistry	O
SuicidePreventionInitiativeNg	O
MentalHealthAwareness	B-EVENT
MentalHealth	I-EVENT

Pls	O
give	O
break	O
This	O
quacks	O
rappers	O
might	O
forced	O
commit	O
suicide	O

Your	O
career	O
pretty	O
well	O
washed	O
out	O
However	O
standing	O
lying	O
trump	O
character	O
suicide	O

Awwww	B-PER
that	O
s	O
nice	O
I	O
m	O
depressed	O

Maino	B-EVENT
@MainoHustleHard	I-EVENT
Uncle	O
Murda	B-PER
@UncleMurda	O
Suicide	O
Squad	O
Gang	O
Clean	O

severe	O
major	O
depression	O
cool	O
basically	O

Yay	O
insomnia	O
s	O
Getting	O
ready	O
long	O
day	O
social	O
things	O
five	O
hours	O
sleep	O
less	O
I	O
m	O
officially	O
Fatigued	O
today	O
well	O
heartbroken	O
depressed	O
pictwittercomy9h1dY6X1l	O

Aww	O
poor	O
Labor	O
rustedons	O
make	O
feel	O
bit	O
less	O
depressed	O
Labors	O
shift	O
right	O
attack	O
Greens	B-EVENT
old	O
rubbish	O
Do	O
something	O
useful	O
support	O
increase	O
Newstart	B-EVENT

let	O
break	O
Jehovah	O
God	B-PER
expanded	O
women	O
35	O
Jennifer	B-PER
committed	O
suicide	O
lowered	O
back	O
1827	O
younger	O
handle	O
love	O
pressure	O
put	O
whores	O
check	O
Jasmine	B-PER
Cull	I-PER
reviewed	O
openly	O
I	O
okd	O
it	O

Meet	O
depressed	O
congress	O
goes	O
home	O
high	O
must	O
priority	O
list	O
leavIn	O
order	O
1	O
Border	O
2	O
Budget	O
3	O
Personal	O
4	O
Healthcare	O
5	O
Drugs	O
Nope	O
Trump	O
hurt	O
feelings	O
today	O
Democratics	B-EVENT
do	O
nt	O
throw	O
stones	O
They	O
come	O
back	O
harder	O
Get	O
work	O

A	O
bitter	O
divorce	O
leave	O
feeling	O
depressed	O
overwhelmed	O
especially	O
go	O
unprepared	O
Our	O
complimentary	O
report	O
highlights	O
costly	O
mistakes	O
avoid	O
Download	O
free	O
copy	O

Monster	O
Gym	O
Blackjack	O
suicide	O
Boozieo	B-PER
315	O
225	O
135	O

@fakkedap	B-PER
sucks	O
Have	O
good	O
trip	O
tho	O

Caren	B-PER
quiere	I-PER
que	O
suicide	O
con	O
los	O
temas	O
pone	O
esta	O
perra	O
est	O
loca	O

Us	O
making	O
love	O
TL	O

@coolacid	O
Well	O
got	O
email	O
must	O

Again	O
todays	O
50th	O
anniversary	O
Apollo	B-EVENT
11	I-EVENT
I	O
find	O
depressed	O
Cuz	B-EVENT
whole	O
lot	O
happened	O
since	O
pertains	O
space	O
exploration	O
least	O
enough	O
get	O
cockpit	O
RVR	B-EVENT
or	O
something	O
comparable	O
irl	O
via	O
pictwittercom8a8Aar73wA	O

video	O
ovguide	O
porn	O
nude	O
celbrities	O
adult	O
comics	O
tube	O
dragon	O
ball	O
bulma	O
add	O
depression	O
pictwittercomD72grmZblK	O

first	O
impression	O
uzairs	O
slt	O
nickname	O
head	O
nen	O
closeness	O
ratings	O
3	O
like	O
you	O
yea	O
my	O
depressed	O
bayo	O
mutual	O
7	O
honest	O
I	O
m	O
glad	O
showcase	O
bayos	O
kill	O
power	O
blew	O

Trying	O
like	O
tweet	O
deleted	O

@ksprior	O
post	O
something	O
moron	O

Longest	O
sound	O
check	O
ever	O
So	O
long	O
I	O
time	O
type	O
this	O
stage	O

According	O
Pakistani	B-EVENT
Taliban	I-EVENT
claimed	O
responsibility	O
suicide	O
attack	O
attacker	O
man	O
women	O

@ZakBagans	O
Zach	B-PER
Mariah	I-PER
Florida	I-PER
I	O
used	O
live	O
St	B-LOC
Louis	I-LOC
lids	O
commit	O
suicide	O
murdered	O
know	O
see	O
hear	O
spirits	O
told	O
almost	O
lived	O
born	O
raised	O
limbs	O

We	O
condemn	O
suicide	O
attack	O
whoever	O
u	O
keep	O
digging	O
political	O
personal	O
goals	O

I	O
received	O
2500	O
donation	O
supporting	O
American	B-EVENT
Foundation	I-EVENT
Suicide	I-EVENT
Prevention	I-EVENT

Por	B-PER
si	O
lo	O
conocen	O
ahora	O
saben	O

In	O
nailing	O
colours	O
Brexit	B-PER
mast	O
Corbyn	B-PER
backed	O
him	O
committed	O
political	O
suicide	O
They	O
nominally	O
Labour	B-EVENT
voters	O
UKIP	B-EVENT
mindsets	O
hence	O
RedKIP	B-EVENT
whilst	O
alienating	O
believed	O
true	O
values	O
one	O
internationalism	O

Tous	B-PER
les	I-PER
spoils	O
genre	O
Tokyo	B-LOC
tue	O
le	O
professeur	O
se	O
suicide	O
sont	O
faux	O

He	O
s	O
fucking	O
15	O
age	O
I	O
getting	O
beaten	O
days	O
depressed	O
dealing	O
suicide	O
meanwhile	O
he	O
tired	O

Last	O
week	O
I	O
TURNT	O
ready	O
bday	O
planned	O
getting	O
locs	O
donecolored	O
lashes	O
ALLAT	O
m	O
like	O
blahhhh	O
cares	O
smfh	O
always	O
got	O
ta	O
get	O
depressed	O
ishh	O
around	O
day	O
aggravated	O
Cancers	B-EVENT

@DonnieWahlberg	B-PER
Wondering	O
he	O
s	O
still	O
listening	O
If	O
soldiers	O
get	O
goodnight	O

Why	O
suicide	O
get	O
back	O
together	O
Alice	B-PER
when	O
could	O
stayed	O
love	O
Ellliot	B-PER

Depressed	O
acne	O
scars	O
fb	O

I	O
m	O
scared	O
smart	O
people	O
are	O
nt	O
depressed	O

I	O
opened	O
dad	O
depressed	O
pansexual	O
He	O
super	O
accepting	O
m	O
happy	O
actually	O
ca	O
nt	O
believe	O

Bro	O
ah	O
think	O
man	O
dead	O
u	O
quoted	O
ruled	O
suicide	O

I	O
come	O
realm	O
Dazais	B-PER
dreams	O
true	O
superior	O
Chuuyas	B-PER
He	O
starts	O
poke	O
cheek	O
nose	O

I	O
m	O
always	O
depressed	O
wintertime	O
especially	O
around	O
Christmas	O
feel	O
like	O
reason	O
really	O
take	O
care	O
baby	O
needs	O
healthy	O
mama	O

When	O
I	O
age	O
also	O
suicidal	O
able	O
get	O
medical	O
treatment	O
it	O
HOWEVER	O
suicide	O
ATTEMPT	O
sent	O
straight	O
hospital	O
Literally	O
actually	O
try	O
take	O
life	O
Period	O

Last	O
minute	O
rhus	O
Monday	O
interesting	O
people	O
inspiring	O
presentation	O
juicy	O
steaks	O

RT	O
@dietpatch	O
@pjforguk	O
Profitable	O
Advertisingpromoted	O
junkfood	O
heightens	O
blood	O
sugar	O
inflammation	O
hence	O
obesity	O
depression	O

Katakanlah	B-PER
sekarang	O
bahwa	O
kau	O
tak	O
bahagia	O

Holy	O
fuck	O
insane	O
proves	O
Lebron	B-PER
would	O
shit	O
mjs	O
era	O
mj	O
clearly	O
was	O
nt	O
tough	O
dominant	O
old	O
heads	O
say	O
@Phantuums	B-PER
bro	O
u	O
show	O
stream	O
its	O
fucking	O
debunks	O

Guns	O
second	O
leading	O
cause	O
death	O
among	O
children	O
complete	O
BS	O
btw	O
The	O
statistic	O
conflates	O
suicide	O
homicide	O
data	O
Harris	B-PER
uses	O
conclude	O
guns	O
problem	O

A	O
40yearold	O
Zimbabwean	B-EVENT
Jotham	B-PER
Chakawa	I-PER
committed	O
suicide	O
two	O
wives	O
allegedly	O
cheating	O
him	O

This	O
Might	O
Be	O
Year	O
Clippers	O
Win	O
Finals	O
But	O
It	O
Also	O
We	O
Are	O
Wiped	O
Out	O
By	O
Measles	O

WomenforTrump	O
repressed	O
depressed	O
desperate	O
women	O
fall	O
twobit	O
thug	O
bully	O
sexual	O
predator	O
He	O
respect	O
wants	O
sleep	O
daughter	O
belongs	O
behind	O
bars	O
Oval	B-EVENT
Office	I-EVENT

Dershowitz	B-PER
1st	O
wifetragic	O
abuse	O
divorce	O
suicidegoogle	O
groups	O

Ultimate	O
makes	O
depressed	O
player	O
alot	O
I	O
always	O
doubt	O
never	O
go	O
set	O
positive	O
healthy	O
mindset	O

Nashville	B-LOC
pictures	O
I	O
get	O
home	O
tonight	O
plane	O
land	O
730	O

Besides	O
attacking	O
battle	O
station	O
ai	O
nt	O
idea	O
courage	O
Its	O
like	O
suicide	O
EpIV	O

Definitely	O
agree	O
that	O
Faith	O
alone	O
enough	O
time	O
I	O
ve	O
said	O
Ill	O
say	O
though	O
Anyone	O
reading	O
feels	O
rut	O
depressed	O
etc	O
turn	O
shoot	O
DM	B-PER
We	O
better	O
were	O
happier	O

Shed	O
rather	O
commit	O
suicide	O
go	O
back	O
Honduras	B-LOC
Tells	O
everything	O
need	O
know	O
great	O
USA	B-LOC
is	O

Bitches	O
get	O
offended	O
called	O
depressed	O
yet	O
call	O
endlessly	O
tweet	O
lonely	O
are	O
Hehehehehe	O
Ridiculous	O
Kinda	O
like	O
people	O
hearing	O
truth	O

Chester	B-PER
Benningtons	I-PER
widow	O
bandmates	O
remember	O
rocker	O
death	O
anniversary	O
Bennington	B-PER
committed	O
suicide	O
20	O
July	O
2017	O
age	O
41	O

@BreeOlson	O
I	O
wonder	O
someone	O
extremely	O
depressed	O
convinced	O
fugly	O
people	O
take	O
advantage	O
you	O
especially	O
weirdos	O
internet	O
guess	O
m	O
meant	O
happy	O
lifetime	O

want	O
kermit	O
suicide	O
i	O
m	O
feeling	O
froggy	O
enough	O
jump	O
pictwittercomZLzDOE8yj2	O

Feeling	O
depressed	O
counseling	O
homework	O
oxymoron	O

Cest	O
vrai	O
les	O
jeunes	O
adorent	O
le	O
suicide	O
collectif	O
dans	O
une	O
nuit	O
de	O
fte	O
surtout	O
lorsquils	O
sont	O
chargs	O
par	O
des	O
fachistes	O
flics	O
qui	O
en	O
dautres	O
occasions	O
massacre	O
F	O
ges	O
SANS	O
RAISON	O
autre	O
q	O
ordres	O
CastanerNunes	O
nazis	O
gouvernementaux	O
officiels	O
Quelle	B-PER
ordure	O

@ddlovato	B-PER
Apparently	O
concert	O
last	O
night	O
Jo	B-PER
Bro	I-PER
AMAZING	I-PER
My	O
friends	O
love	O
finally	O
haha	O

Plz	O
let	O
win	O
one	O
I	O
spam	O
anymore	O

mom	O
forced	O
go	O
doctors	O
today	O
thought	O
normal	O
checkup	O
told	O
doctor	O
depressed	O
practically	O
laughed	O
face	O
cuz	O
knew	O
i	O
m	O

air	O
supply	O
rem	O
ways	O
commit	O
suicide	O

My	O
therapist	O
We	O
talked	O
spending	O
less	O
time	O
social	O
media	O
mentioned	O
making	O
feel	O
depressed	O
How	O
s	O
going	O
Me	O
pictwittercomQGmoiPay9y	O

@mp3mad	O
Lol	O
One	O
personal	O
faves	O

I	O
do	O
nt	O
care	O
man	O
Three	O
immigrants	O
die	O
like	O
9	O
months	O
When	O
22	O
veterans	O
day	O
suicide	O
Who	O
government	O
owe	O
more	O
Immigrants	B-EVENT
returned	O
vets	O

Emouvant	O
hommage	O
au	O
jeune	O
exil	O
qui	O
sest	O
suicid	O
dans	O
le	O
18eme	O
samedi	O
dernier	O
Lindiffrence	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
la	O
Mairie	I-LOC
Paris	I-LOC
et	O
du	O
gouvernement	O
face	O
situation	O
des	O
migrants	O
fait	O
morts	O
Combien	O
vatil	O
en	O
falloir	O
pour	O
que	O
vous	O
ragissiez	O
@AnneHidalgo	O
@EmmanuelMacron	B-PER
pictwittercomELuOSUPpPm	I-PER

forces	O
suicide	O
want	O
enemy	O
s	O
god	O
helping	O

Just	O
leave	O
vhs	O
car	O
Blockbuster	B-EVENT
fit	O

Yessirrr	O
that	O
s	O
answer	O
I	O
hoping	O
WHOLETEAM	O

Suicide	O
immensely	O
complex	O
individual	O
issue	O
sweeping	O
generalisation	O
suggests	O
Depression	B-EVENT
post	O
traumatic	O
stress	O
cowardice	O
Neither	O
living	O
pain	O
poverty	O
grief	O
homelessness	O
social	O
media	O
peer	O
pressure	O
list	O
goes	O
on	O
Do	O
better	O
mate	O

Good	O
Luck	O
Ashley	B-PER
I	O
love	O
you	O
Bolivia	B-LOC

watched	O
whole	O
first	O
season	O
like	O
day	O
half	O
maybe	O
15	O
even	O
depressed	O
nd	O
remember	O
pretty	O
cool	O
nothing	O
groundbreaking	O
fuckin	O
love	O
MCU	O
tho	O
episode	O
lady	O
sif	O
dope	O
Want	O
Her	O
waititis	O
inevitable	O
thor	O
4	O

E	O
na	O
real	O
maior	O
responsvel	O
pela	O
emisso	O
de	O
gases	O
efeito	O
estufa	O
indstria	O
desmatamento	O

depressed	O
lifeismeaningless	O
@JaymeKirb	B-PER
naay	O
nag	O
away	O
sa	O
atong	O
amigo	O
bai	O

Israel	B-LOC
better	O
check	O
suicide	O
vest	O

Just	O
grateful	O
killary	O
president	O
would	O
silenced	O
suicide	O

How	O
kill	O
without	O
making	O
look	O
like	O
suicide	O

Ca	O
nt	O
wait	O
Austin	B-LOC
way	O
least	O
I	O
m	O
feeling	O
depressed	O
alone	O
its	O
actually	O
bc	O
everyone	O
around	O
trash	O

Plz	O
I	O
barely	O
skins	O
never	O
win	O
gaw	O

three	O
competition	O
running	O
moment	O
gig	O
tickets	O
amp	O
sunglasses	O
check	O
wwwonesmallseednet	O
find	O
details	O

i	O
m	O
depressed	O
want	O
talk	O
one	O
person	O
ca	O
nt	O

Fr	O
I	O
getting	O
hit	O
random	O
depression	O
outta	O
nowhere	O
Emoji	O
Upsidedown	O
faceEmoji	O
Disappointed	O
face	O

Harassed	O
By	O
Upper	B-EVENT
Class	I-EVENT
Classmates	O
20YearOld	O
Dalit	O
Student	O
Commits	O
Suicide	O
In	O
Ghaziabad	B-LOC

Idc	O
excessive	O
This	O
weird	O
obsession	O
virginity	O
mind	O
blowing	O
double	O
standards	O
men	O
women	O
even	O
crazier	O
12	O
is	O
nt	O
young	O
know	O
sex	O
performing	O
it	O
yes	O
no	O
As	O
parent	O
that	O
s	O
communication	O
come	O
play	O

Just	O
caught	O
glimpse	O
The	O
Dish	B-EVENT
Style	I-EVENT
Check	I-EVENT
out	O

ugh	O
I	O
wanna	O
die	O
Gtg	B-PER

Can	O
life	O
damn	O
harmful	O
love	O
ones	O
I	O
swear	O
mom	O
sick	O
grandpa	O
hospital	O
baby	O
depressed	O
would	O
give	O
make	O
pain	O
go	O
away	O

How	O
many	O
cases	O
depressionsuicide	O
social	O
media	O
going	O
see	O
people	O
stop	O
cancel	O
culture	O
Its	O
toxic	O
hell	O

Retards	B-EVENT
think	O
modern	O
movie	O
actually	O
even	O
mention	O
gays	O
suicide	O
abuse	O

I	O
ve	O
always	O
felt	O
like	O
this	O
many	O
years	O
mental	O
health	O
problems	O
found	O
Autistic	B-EVENT
Since	O
kinder	O
forced	O
situations	O
make	O
uncomfortable	O
You	O
sound	O
may	O
depressed	O
spoken	O
anyone	O

Its	O
thing	O
alive	O
commit	O
suicide	O
due	O
mental	O
distress	O
what	O
could	O
I	O
done	O
prevent	O
this	O
If	O
man	O
dies	O
kills	O
you	O
ll	O
probably	O
put	O
big	O
D	O
twitter	O
logo	O
say	O
RIP	O
dustan	B-PER

whatever	O
Your	O
team	O
probably	O
robots	O
anyway	O
he	O
walks	O
away	O

Playing	O
Rock	O
band	O
Unplugged	O
Digging	O
it	O
I	O
liked	O
Amplitude	B-PER
never	O
got	O
fits	O
pretty	O
close	O

My	O
favorite	O
time	O
is	O
Me	O

Might	O
need	O
someone	O
talk	O
stuff	O
I	O
get	O
really	O
depressed	O
whole	O
awful	O
situation	O

@pinkelephantpun	O
Books	O
tape	O
cd	O
makes	O
drive	O
interesting	O
Hope	B-PER
helps	O

Alienasi	B-PER
tidak	O
terhindarkan	O
selepas	O
abolisi	O
poin2	O
dan	O
membuat	O
diri	O
bertanya	O
sehabis	O
ini	O
apalagi	O
Bagaimana	B-PER
lagi	O
Lalu	B-PER
Apakah	I-PER
N	O
berbagai	O
pertanyaan	O
tetek	O
bengeknya	O
sampai	O
akhirnya	O
paralisis	O
walau	O
manungsa	O
punya	O
keinginan	O
tekad	O
tapi	O
tetap	O
sa	O
pikir	O
bahwa	O
there	O
s	O
future	O

fare	O
thee	O
well	O
tweetdom	O

Happy	O
mothers	O
day	O
mom	O

This	O
crazy	O
story	O
I	O
fact	O
check	O
make	O
sure	O
was	O
nt	O
fake	O
Asda	B-EVENT
mental	O
How	O
is	O
suing	O
emotional	O
trauma	O
beyond	O
me	O
Do	O
get	O
also	O
calling	O
suicide	O
bomber	O
wanker	O
unislamic	O
Most	O
Muslim	B-EVENT
people	O
know	O
would	O
call	O
that	O

They	O
really	O
mean	O
whole	O
Leaving	O
Neverland	O
bullshit	O
Even	O
sad	O
lot	O
shit	O
Michaels	B-PER
kids	O
like	O
would	O
anyone	O
think	O
something	O
good	O
grow	O
them	O
Referencing	O
Pariss	B-PER
attempted	O
suicide	O
I	O
even	O
thd	O
energy	O
write	O
back	O
then	O

@kynagelaver	O
slr	O
uhmm	O
yeah	O
kinda	O
lol	O

@MarksVoice	B-PER
another	O
time	O
classic	O

If	O
dropped	O
bitcoin	O
I	O
told	O
bought	O
Silver	I-EVENT
would	O
400	O
today	O
Instead	O
people	O
calling	O
suicide	O
hotline	O
2018	O
These	O
arguments	O
meaningless	O
Morons	O
put	O
eggs	O
one	O
basket	O
Smart	O
guys	O
diversify	O
hold	O
ALL	O
Gold	B-EVENT
Bitcoin	I-EVENT

Only	O
2	O
days	O
sophmore	O
year	O
left	O
thank	O
godd	O
lt3	O
txt	O
mehhh	O
i	O
m	O
boredd	O

u	O
wanna	O
make	O
depressed	O
smth	O

They	O
cut	O
them	O
sustainable	O
Not	O
actually	O
would	O
It	O
political	O
suicide	O
Those	O
tax	O
cuts	O
constitute	O
tiny	O
margin	O
overall	O
deficit	O
projected	O
debt	O
Its	O
little	O
taxes	O
problem	O
much	O
spending	O

So	O
conclusion	O
Twitter	B-EVENT
depressed	O
AND	O
wants	O
raid	O
Area	B-EVENT
51	O

In	O
7	O
years	O
followed	O
I	O
done	O
amazing	O
things	O
met	O
people	O
travelled	O
places	O
Imagining	O
experience	O
scary	O
rewarding	O
sense	O
truly	O
appreciate	O
lifes	O
purpose	O
suicide	O

I	O
ca	O
nt	O
wait	O
Suicide	O
Squad	O
also	O
happen	O
even	O
little	O
pull	O
@warnerbros	B-EVENT
maybe	O
politely	O
request	O
they	O
clears	O
throat	O
ReleaseTheSnyderCut	B-EVENT

No	O
wonder	O
everyones	O
fucking	O
depressed	O
since	O
life	O
becomes	O
harder	O
lmao	O
should	O
nt	O
like	O

My	O
mental	O
health	O
ruined	O
working	O
bully	O
manager	O
20	O
years	O
ago	O
It	O
made	O
depressed	O
ill	O
I	O
ended	O
eating	O
disorder	O
Now	O
tell	O
work	O
cure	O

Ahhhhh	O
bakit	O
ba	O
I	O
hate	O
feeling	O
amp	O

Frodd	B-PER
evicted	O
Tommorow	B-PER
ii	O
foresee	O
deppression	O
suicide	O
BBNaija	B-PER
pictwittercomgjB9v3ZH26	I-PER

Need	O
know	O
spotting	O
signs	O
depression	O
young	O
people	O
Does	O
work	O
bring	O
close	O
contact	O
teens	O
These	O
3	O
common	O
symptoms	O
watch	O
communitymentalhealth	O
mentalhealthtraining	O
mentalhealtheducation	O

AthleticWght	B-EVENT
switched	O
weights	O
230	O
cable	O
chest	O
depressed	O
20	O
wings	O
delts	O
15	O
pounds	O

Desolation	O
Row	O
I	O
ve	O
depressed	O
lately	O

Almost	O
advertising	O
product	O
seminaked	O
ladies	O
saying	O
looking	O
friends	O
men	O
category	O
I	O
look	O
profile	O
send	O
Mostly	O
let	O
commit	O
suicide	O
block	O

camping	O
w	O
family	O
weekend	O

Jvous	O
conseille	O
vivement	O
daller	O
voir	O
le	O
film	O
A	O
Silent	O
VoiceKoe	O
Katachi	O
Ce	O
voque	O
des	O
ralits	O
blessantes	O
harclement	O
limpact	O
que	O
a	O
peut	O
avoir	O
sur	O
la	O
personne	O
suicide	O
perte	O
de	O
confiance	O
en	O
soi	O
Clairement	O
un	O
1010	O
Foncez	O
pictwittercomSnBgWgH7qn	O

Oliver	B-PER
Long	I-PER
getting	O
ready	O
come	O

Three	O
killed	O
eight	O
injured	O
suicide	O
blast	O
inside	O
Trauma	O
Centre	O
District	O
Headquarter	O
Hospital	O
Dera	B-LOC
Ismail	I-LOC
Khan	I-LOC
Pakistan	B-LOC
Media	O
pictwittercomueOG0lqyb8	O

So	O
energy	O
left	O
something	O
nice	O
meaningful	O
twice	O
week	O
Without	O
get	O
seriously	O
depressed	O
Its	O
quality	O
life	O
long	O
term	O
Some	O
people	O
unpredictable	O
serious	O
relapses	O
6	O

OMG	O
50k	O
Depressed	O
already	O
Thank	O
information	O

cool	O
guitarist	O
Wear	O
LANA	O
The	O
Diana	B-PER
Set	I-PER
@	O
ACCESS	O
Backdrop	O
Joplino	O
Music	O
Speaks	O
Suicide	O
Dollz	O
Guitar	O
Pose	O
MMotion	O
Pose6Set	O
BLOG	O

Making	O
toads	O
kermit	O
suicide	O
pictwittercoms1OS9yc3E5	B-EVENT

Lucky	O
was	O
nt	O
wearing	O
suicide	O
vest	O
She	O
needs	O
cover	O
hair	O
stop	O
boobs	O
place	O

@NoToriousTori	B-PER
Love	I-PER
new	O
pic	O

Beijing	B-EVENT
Suicide	I-EVENT
Research	I-EVENT
Prevention	I-EVENT
Center	I-EVENT
Hotline	I-EVENT
8008101117	O

responds	O
suicide	O
letter	O
like	O
lol	O
weird	O
bitch	O

I	O
suggest	O
read	O
@johnpavlovitz	O
say	O
suicide	O

Douglas	B-PER
Todd	I-PER
Suicide	O
among	O
BC	B-LOC
foreign	O
students	O
little	O
talked	O
studentmentalhealth	O

Endgame	O
Ppl	O
still	O
sleeping	O
serious	O
depression	O
Thor	O
experiencing	O
I	O
m	O
saying	O
turned	O
eating	O
alcohol	O
video	O
games	O
seclusion	O
Not	O
good	O
combo	O
debating	O
desire	O
weild	O
glove	O
attempt	O
suicide	O

O	B-PER
Triste	I-PER
quando	O
voc	O
dar	O
toda	O
ateno	O
mundo	O
pra	O
pessoa	O
acaba	O
deixando	O
pessoas	O
que	O
gostam	O
de	O
verdade	O
l	O
e	O
depois	O
quebra	O
cara	O
porque	O
tudo	O
nica	O
coisa	O
ganhou	O
foi	O
mais	O
uma	O
decepo	O
sua	O
coleo	O

Oh	O
hey	O
guys	O
Apparently	O
14	O
year	O
girls	O
PTSD	B-EVENT
I	O
guess	O
WWII	O
seeing	O
best	O
friend	O
die	O
going	O
suicide	O
mission	O
waking	O
new	O
century	O
count	O
trauma	O
PS	O
You	O
realize	O
men	O
women	O
fighting	O
current	O
wars	O
come	O
home	O

Loneliness	O
solutionless	O
problems	O
hit	O
again	O
How	O
cure	O
Idk	O
But	O
I	O
know	O
shat	O
make	O
anxtious	O
depressed	O
Let	O
open	O
Anxiety	O
Depression	O
playlist	O

Live	O
life	O
get	O
one	O
shoot	O

I	O
m	O
glad	O
committed	O
suicide	O
@Machin3Mad3Man	O

En	O
gros	O
Rin	O
avait	O
Sanbi	O
le	O
dmon	O
3	O
queus	O
en	O
elle	O
les	O
ninjas	O
de	B-PER
Kiri	I-PER
la	I-PER
poursuivait	O
et	O
Madara	B-LOC
fait	O
sorte	O
quelle	O
se	O
suicide	O
sur	O
bras	O
Kakashi	I-PER
devant	O
Obito	B-PER

got	O
ta	O
say	O
ca	O
nt	O
believe	O
white	O
aways	O
terribly	O

I	O
drinking	O
lot	O
trying	O
forget	O
busy	O
week	O

I	O
think	O
did	O
nt	O
go	O
difficult	O
times	O
would	O
know	O
God	B-PER
deliverer	O
trust	O
Him	O
Pippa	B-PER
Gumbel	I-PER
Day	I-PER
75	O
Bible	B-EVENT
one	O
year	O
You	O
ll	O
fine	O

I	O
want	O
watch	O
Bungou	B-EVENT
Stray	I-EVENT
Dogs	I-EVENT
cuz	O
Chuuya	B-PER
Ranpo	I-PER
type	O
characters	O
Aesthetics	B-PER
like	O
Dazai	B-PER
too	O
really	O
hate	O
whole	O
obsession	O
suicide	O

I	O
get	O
saying	O
Its	O
true	O
suicide	O
even	O
murder	O
rate	O
high	O
The	O
struggle	O
real	O
painful	O

stopped	O
smoking	O
cigarettes	O
i	O
m	O
proud	O
abusing	O
drugs	O
alcohol	O
suicide	O
attempts	O
got	O
abusive	O
relationship	O

I	O
know	O
m	O
depressed	O

Well	O
pointed	O
replica	O
gun	O
police	O
Textbook	O
suicide	O
cop	O
Not	O
unjustified	O

Gpp	O
deh	O
yg	O
penting	O
blake	O
senang	O

@melyt	B-PER
good	O
little	O
diseases	O

douard	O
Manet	B-PER
The	O
Suicide	O
1877	O

It	O
took	O
multiple	O
suicide	O
attempts	O
break	O
downs	O
2	O
psychiatrists	O
shit	O
ton	O
medication	O
realize	O
love	O
really	O
meant	O
As	O
cheesey	O
sounds	O
means	O
Richard	B-PER

Same	O
takes	O
place	O
Suicide	B-EVENT
Squad	I-EVENT

ChiefPolice	O
overstates	O
pedophile	O
case	O
tells	O
patriots	O
patientSpeak	B-PER
issue	O
tortureforced	O
suicide	O
murder	O
fbi	O
today	O

ppl	O
graduated	O
getting	O
engaged	O
i	O
m	O
just	O
depressed	O

These	O
kids	O
stfu	O
suicide	O
shit	O
Bc	O
I	O
ve	O
alr	O
found	O
2	O
people	O
faking	O
it	O
If	O
got	O
enough	O
energy	O
go	O
twitter	O

Mais	O
mec	O
ton	O
thread	O
sert	O
rien	O
psk	O
tu	O
dis	O
que	O
limite	O
sen	O
branle	O
quils	O
soient	O
comme	O
au	O
bord	O
du	O
suicide	O
ce	O
qui	O
est	O
totalement	O
faux	O
et	O
donc	O
nous	O
fait	O
chier	O
les	O
locals	O
vous	O
faites	O
mme	O
idoles	O
de	O
kpop	O
cquon	O
veux	O

@jimpeel	O
Exact	O
problem	O
I	O
months	O
ago	O
Ended	O
buy	O
new	O
one	O
fixed	O
it	O
Result	O
mixed	O

Remember	O
14	O
20	O
Vets	O
Suicide	O
day	O
age	O
50	O
Do	O
use	O
VA	O
Are	O
often	O
VietnamWar	O
Veterans	O
Another	O
4	O
ACTIVE	O
DUTY	O
entered	O
service	O
w	O
PREEXITING	O
mental	O
illness	O
POST	O
911	O
PTSD	O
LOWEST	O
suicide	O
risk	O
Focus	O
vets	O

My	O
depressed	O
ass	O
gets	O
damn	O
that	O
s	O
crazy	O
lemme	O
make	O
u	O
feel	O
better	O
y	O
all	O
take	O
notes	O
plz	O

The	O
dummy	O
committed	O
suicide	O
ai	O
nt	O
getting	O
peace	O
thatRIPChesterBennington	O

Why	O
u	O
wanna	O
commit	O
suicide	O

Btw	O
I	O
tripped	O
front	O
store	O
The	O
top	O
metal	O
piece	O
still	O
attached	O
time	O
slightly	O
depressed	O
rest	O
small	O
opening	O
center	O
Now	O
completely	O
broken	O
exposed	O
wires	O
Wtf	O
pictwittercomNHW6XQBRxi	O

woke	O
shit	O
ton	O
people	O
dms	O
panicked	O
thinking	O
depressed	O
main	O
passing	O
last	O
night	O
bro	O
pictwittercomYd5xGR8lf5	O

Why	O
depressed	O
sad	O
time	O
like	O
little	O
bitch	O

One	O
day	O
I	O
forget	O
name	O
Ill	O
naaaaame	O

Eurabia	B-LOC
they	O
re	O
already	O
toast	O
need	O
2	O
avoid	O
type	O
suicide	O
defend	O
America	B-LOC

So	O
i	O
m	O
depressed	O
bought	O
birthday	O
present	O
Bought	O
weighted	O
blanket	O
oodie	O
Yeah	O
gon	O
na	O
nice	O
Help	O
hopefully	O
sleep	O
depression	O
pictwittercomHuoHIuffIJ	O

pano	O
pumayat	O
Maging	O
depress	O
Rt	O
boi	O
Depress	O
kaya	O
blis	O
nangayayat	O

hand	O
u	O
suicide	O
note	O
leak	O
die	O

Meditation	I-EVENT
contribute	O
overall	O
wellbeing	O
decreasing	O
stress	O
anxiety	O
even	O
depression	O
turn	O
increasing	O
positive	O
emotions	O
Join	O
30Day	B-EVENT
Challenge	I-EVENT
see	O
yourself	O
BONUS	O
receive	O
free	O
meditation	O
instruction	O
May	O
pictwittercomJkF4qGA4Hw	O

Sweetie	O
I	O
got	O
Masters	B-EVENT
back	O
90s	O
So	O
m	O
impressed	O
college	O
kids	O
NEVER	O
lived	O
experienced	O
life	O
When	O
women	O
required	O
register	O
draft	O
start	O
dying	O
job	O
like	O
MEN	O
committing	O
suicide	O
lecture	O
privilege	O

suggested	O
use	O
suicide	O
guide	O

No	O
Voljin	B-PER
The	O
shadow	O
hunter	O
jealous	O
SENT	O
suicide	O
mission	O
did	O
nt	O
go	O
one	O
himself	O
My	O
HCs	B-EVENT
rather	O
different	O
norm	O
I	O
suppose	O
least	O
comes	O
Darkspear	B-EVENT
trolls	O
monogamy	O
jam	O
yeah	O

Hey	O
happy	O
birthday	O
I	O
hope	O
things	O
get	O
better	O
feel	O
good	O
soon	O

Suicide	O
Do	O
nt	O
unrealistic	O
expectations	O
children	O
FG	O
tells	O
parents	O

Have	O
pic	O
Harry	B-PER
Connick	I-PER
Jr	I-PER
strategically	O
placed	O
office	O
continuous	O
inspiration	O
constant	O
swooning	O
happyclam	O

I	O
fantastic	O
day	O
Shoeing	O
horses	O
ridding	O
life	O
good	O

You	O
depressed	O
muhfuckas	O
loveeeee	O
express	O
via	O
social	O
media	O
thing	O
keeps	O
interaction	O
reality	O
distant	O

Y	O
la	O
vuelto	O
cagar	O

Yup	O
Believe	O
makes	O
happy	O
live	O
fulfilling	O
life	O
possible	O
If	O
I	O
believed	O
nothing	O
would	O
seriously	O
depress	O
play	O
mind	O
believe	O
m	O
wrong	O
well	O
Ill	O
never	O
know	O
anyway	O

S	O
olhar	O
cara	O
Hugh	B-PER
Grant	I-PER
deixa	O
molhada	O

I	O
need	O
isolate	O
again	O
feel	O
starting	O
become	O
depressed	O

The	O
girl	O
asked	O
boyfreiebd	O
die	O
thought	O
nothing	O
cause	O
suicide	O
either	O
found	O
guilty	O
Just	O
saying	O

HOY	O
SBADO	O
ABIERTO	O
30	O
cortes	O
x	O
5	O
miiiiil	O
20panko10palta	O
Incluye	O
salsas	O
soja	O
unagui	O
Reserva	B-PER
al	O
whatsapp	O
56961980205	O
siento	O
entusiasmada	O

little	O
buzz	O
epoxy	O
paint	O

Wow	O
I	O
m	O
feeling	O
depressed	O
want	O
work	O
tomorrow	O
o	O

@lizponce	O
Me	O
too	O
YeahI	B-PER
thinking	O
ILL	O
one	O
I	O
love	O
watching	O
drift	O
cause	O
always	O
makes	O
feel	O
good	O

Suicide	O
hotline	O
numbers	O
United	B-LOC
Kingdom	I-LOC
116	O
123	O
States	I-LOC
18002738255	O
Canada	B-LOC
1	O
800	O
456	O
4566	O
Ireland	B-LOC
Philippines	B-LOC
2919	O
Australia	B-LOC
131	O
114	O
Someone	O
dies	O
suicide	O
every	O
40	O
seconds	O
Will	O
take	O
01	O
second	O
Retweet	O
maybe	O
save	O
life	O

Lire	O
dans	O
Les	O
penses	O
niveau	O
business	O
a	O
serai	O
incroyable	O
un	O
peu	O
dambition	O
et	O
tu	O
peux	O
arriver	O
trs	O
haut	O
vachement	O
facilement	O
Ou	B-PER
contrler	O
le	O
temps	O
mais	O
je	O
pense	O
quau	O
bout	O
dun	O
moment	O
te	O
suicide	O

Orr	B-PER
ladko	I-PER
ka	O
kya	B-PER

wait	O
i	O
ve	O
decided	O
m	O
depressed	O
anymore	O

i	O
m	O
stating	O
like	O
since	O
apparently	O
did	O
nt	O
read	O
reply	O

THE	O
SUICIDE	O
MACHINES	O
TAMASONICextra2019	O

pathetic	O
quit	O
job	O
i	O
m	O
depressed	O
really	O

@sairasameerarao	B-PER
get	O
offended	O
words	O
lets	O
forget	O
rs	O
ism	O
suicide	O
bombers	O
London	B-LOC
attacks	O
much	O
worse	O
Your	O
hypocrite	O
ok	O
non	O
white	O
stuff	O

@albynomonk	O
Hi	O
How	O
Soren	B-PER

tw	O
hi	O
please	O
put	O
tweets	O
suicide	O
self	O
harm	O
eating	O
disorders	O
timeline	O
without	O
trigger	O
warning	O
damn	O
thank	O
u	O

@elyse	B-PER
thanks	O
I	O
sometimes	O
control	O
stop	O
eating	O
xD	O

Heavy	O
use	O
Facebook	O
linked	O
stomach	O
aches	O
sleeping	O
problems	O
anxiety	O
depression	O
narcissism	O
teens	O

Three	O
girls	O
commit	O
suicide	O
Chitral	B-PER

L	O
I	O
great	O
time	O
rowing	O
Avon	B-EVENT
Bath	I-EVENT
learnt	O
row	O
Now	O
cooking	O
dinner	O
watch	O
House	O
Feel	O
knackered	O

i	O
m	O
simple	O
guy	O
I	O
like	O
watching	O
combat	O
sports	O
japanese	O
idols	O
years	O
go	O
realize	O
never	O
needed	O
much	O
that	O
maybe	O
water	O
do	O
nt	O
even	O
care	O
room	O
temp	O
cold	O

depressed	O
remove	O
film	O
top	O
eye	O
replace	O
orange	O
polymer	O
eliminate	O
blue	O
light	O
entering	O

This	O
does	O
nt	O
look	O
like	O
turkey	O

I	O
hate	O
depressed	O
make	O
feel	O
days	O

11	O
Linkin	B-EVENT
Park	I-EVENT
Songs	O
That	O
Take	O
On	O
A	O
Whole	O
New	O
Meaning	O
After	O
Chester	B-EVENT
Benningtons	I-EVENT
Suicide	O
YourTango	O
National	O
Prevention	O
Hotline	O
tel18002738255	O
Veterans	O
press	O
1	O

Eu	B-LOC
choro	O
de	O
raiva	O
nos	O
picos	O
meu	O
lol	O

culkin	O
cringe	O
aidsmoby	O
wo	O
nt	O
even	O
ask	O
mj	O

Logan	O
like	O
ugly	O
ass	O
bitch	O
motherfucker	O
licks	O
bad	O
old	O
meat	O
recording	O
dada	O
porno	O
suicide	O
forest	O
cought	O
hanging	O
dorito	O
tree	O

If	O
I	O
shed	O
tears	O
time	O
ve	O
disappointed	O
life	O
could	O
probably	O
replace	O
waters	O
many	O
oceans	O
Yet	O
try	O
remain	O
hopeful	O
hold	O
times	O
impressed	O
instead	O
depressed	O

@LivPsy	B-PER
If	O
hear	O
sing	O
increased	O
depression	O
anxiety	O

Once	O
all	O
If	O
leaders	O
clean	O
1	O
Why	O
hide	O
Karaqiq	B-PER
Arkan	I-PER
And	O
many	O
2	O
commit	O
suicide	O
prison	O
slobodan	O
qetnik	O
miloqevic	O

layout	O
looks	O
fucking	O
depressed	O
rly	O
dom	O
like	O
angel	O
scene	O

This	O
movie	O
made	O
depressed	O
I	O
m	O
going	O
sleep	O

Are	O
depressed	O
Or	O
anemic	O

Still	O
ai	O
nt	O
bed	O
Walking	O
home	O
getting	O
coffee	O
You	O
know	O
hanover	O
bad	O
hour	O
Kinda	O
peacefull	O

This	O
one	O
best	O
tweets	O
I	O
ve	O
seen	O

He	O
acts	O
like	O
Martes	B-PER
fault	O
team	O
sucks	O

Suicide	O
Squad	O
2	O
leaked	O

Me	O
depressed	O
tired	O
sleep	O
Goodnight	B-PER

TW	O
drug	O
usage	O
borderline	O
alcohol	O
abuse	O
strong	O
language	O
parent	O
neglect	O
possible	O
implied	O
suicide	O
attempts	O
physical	O
violence	O
psychological	O
marie	O
larry	O
calls	O
annie	O
25	O
pan	O
dropped	O
hs	O
senior	O
year	O

@SHABAZGIL	O
Sir	O
please	O
take	O
notice	O
suicide	O
See	O
police	O
powerless	O
poor	O

Pag	B-PER
ako	O
bumalik	O
ng	O
svcc	O
depress	O
talaga	O
kayong	O
lahat	O
mga	O
gago	O

@smck11	O
Sorry	O
hear	O
root	O
canal	O
good	O
luck	O
fun	O
soft	O
foods	O

Fall	O
season	O
makes	O
happy	O
yet	O
depressed	O
time	O

Memphis	B-LOC
Couple	O
Found	O
Dead	O
Apparent	O
MurderSuicide	O
pictwittercomlHk3b8Uruw	O

He	O
s	O
AS	O
suicide	O
watch	O

@melaniejane	B-PER
I	O
m	O
arriving	O
7	O
days	O
Woohooo	O
Soooooo	O
excited	O
SteelBridgeSongFest	B-EVENT

kids	O
elementary	O
committing	O
suicide	O
breaks	O
heart	O
usually	O
does	O
nt	O
affect	O
middle	O
school	O
younger	O
getting	O
bullied	O
seriously	O
people	O
talk	O
children	O
family	O
members	O
remind	O
they	O
re	O
amazing	O

Australias	B-EVENT
ZeroSuicide	I-EVENT
initiative	O
promising	O
new	O
And	O
possible	O
Zero	B-EVENT
Suicide	I-EVENT
It	O
not	O
complex	O
desire	O
amazing	O
claim	O
Its	O
goal	O
far	O
reaching	O
prevent	O
suicide	O
time	O

@CBClick	O
Do	O
it	O
Happy	O
ATampTBold	O
user	O

@MeridianPD	O
proof	O
police	O
negligent	O
andor	O
corrupted	O
How	O
possibly	O
rule	O
ChristianAndreacchio	B-EVENT
death	O
suicide	O
45	O
minutes	O
Police	O
care	O
own	O
JusticeforChristianAndreacchio	B-EVENT
@CulpablePodcast	O
@TenderfootTV	O
thank	O
caring	O

Allegedly	O
Genesis	O
chapter	O
5	O
lists	O
supposed	O
descendants	O
along	O
many	O
lived	O
900s	O
Putting	O
aside	O
know	O
genetic	O
perils	O
incest	O
its	O
completely	O
plausible	O
course	O

Hindi	B-EVENT
pero	O
para	O
maka	O
suicide	O
kana	O

539	O
I	O
encourage	O
take	O
suicide	O
pills	O
do	O
nt	O
suffer	O
EditsForWinners	B-EVENT

Une	O
qui	O
se	O
plaint	O
de	O
son	O
mari	O
boulot	O
feint	O
des	O
tentatives	O
suicide	O
10	O
fois	O
par	O
semaine	O

There	O
time	O
villains	O
beat	O
left	O
front	O
police	O
station	O
cuz	O
going	O
far	O

X	O
full	O
childish	O
optimism	O
matured	O
enough	O
sealed	O
away	O
He	O
ca	O
nt	O
understand	O
siblings	O
really	O
depressed	O
Megaman	B-EVENT
use	O
power	O
anymore	O
without	O
damaging	O
core	O
years	O
worth	O
neglect	O
repairs	O

Hi	O
You	O
may	O
noticed	O
posting	O
lot	O
more	O
its	O
I	O
m	O
using	O
insta	O
accountabilibuddy	O
tool	O
seek	O
joy	O
life	O
ve	O
stuck	O
feeling	O
depressed	O
and	O

Twsuicide	O
I	O
ve	O
kinda	O
made	O
plan	O
never	O
its	O
normally	O
impulse	O
small	O
part	O
like	O
stop	O
do	O
nt	O
feel	O
fading	O

@yuhngfresh	O
well	O
hey	O
weekendz	O
ca	O
nt	O
Cool	O
THEY	O
BE	O
PRODUCTIVE	O
work	O
BEATZ	O

Read	O
latest	O
review	O
I	O
depressed	O
stressed	O
came	O
Mr	O
Weed	B-PER
due	O
illness	O
mounting	O
medical	O

You	O
pal	O
uneducated	O
subject	O
I	O
sure	O
hope	O
one	O
close	O
unexpectedly	O
commits	O
suicide	O
experience	O
it	O

Disney	B-EVENT
waited	O
sign	O
GOTG	O
3	O
By	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
d	O
already	O
signed	O
contract	O
write	O
direct	O
The	O
Suicide	B-EVENT
Squad	I-EVENT
Warner	I-EVENT
Bros	I-EVENT

si	O
vraiment	O
a	O
cest	O
pass	O
tu	O
nas	O
donc	O
pas	O
vu	O
tous	O
les	O
dgts	O
causs	O
Les	B-PER
vidos	O
et	O
photos	O
montrant	O
ces	O

When	O
sure	O
depressed	O
energy	O
drink	O
that	O
s	O
making	O
chest	O
tighten	O
Oops	O

@ZaynnAbel	O
Take	O
several	O
depression	O
naps	O
like	O
bc	O
bitch	O
ME	O
TOO	O

Suicide	O
bombers	O
embracing	O
diversity	O

quotAlready	O
Gonequot	B-PER
Kelly	I-PER
Clarkson	I-PER
beautiful	O

Would	O
nt	O
great	O
live	O
world	O
suicide	O
never	O
event	O
Listen	O
David	B-PER
Covington	I-PER
explain	O
ZeroSuicide	B-EVENT
initiative	O
healthcare	O

Also	O
make	O
advert	O
inclined	O
Its	O
pair	O
jeansLee	B-EVENT
Jeans	I-EVENT
clearly	O
done	O
purpose	O
get	O
peoples	O
backs	O
up	O
Then	O
wonder	O
male	O
suicide	O
high	O
constantly	O
persecuted	O
media	O

offers	O
hugs	O
although	O
I	O
depressed	O
myself	O

Tomei	B-PER
um	O
suco	O
chamado	O
Pele	B-PER
Firme	I-PER
aguardando	O
ansiosamente	O
pelo	O
resultado	O
se	O
no	O
funcionar	O
propaganda	O
enganosa	O

I	O
m	O
straight	O
back	O
java	O
dis	O
week	O

My	O
personal	O
blog	O
recently	O
updated	O
follow	O
here	O

No	O
money	O
Three	O
weeks	O
without	O
help	O
20000	O
debt	O
1000	O
loan	O
shark	O
interest	O
Hungry	O
kids	O
Suicide	O
Welcome	O
Britain	B-LOC

anybody	O
love	O
The	B-LOC
Hills	I-LOC
used	O
think	O
boring	O
i	O
m	O
quite	O
big	O
fan	O
dunnoi	O
like	O
looks	O
real	O
life	O

Suicide	O
hotline	O
0917	O
854	O
9191	O

It	O
sucks	O
I	O
honestly	O
hope	O
go	O
suicide	O

Spoiler	O
alert	O
Chick	B-PER
commits	O
suicide	O
jumping	O
high	O
rise	O
end	O
hentai	O
Definitely	O
feel	O
good	O
situation	O
Do	O
nt	O
ask	O
I	O
know	O

If	O
Cancer	O
probably	O
depressed	O
af	O
feeling	O
sorry	O
complete	O
waste	O
time	O

That	O
completely	O
false	O
Dysphoria	B-EVENT
resolved	O
therapy	O
one	O
tries	O
anymore	O
bc	O
socially	O
progressive	O
whatever	O
Transition	O
suicide	O
young	O
dysphoric	O
ppl	O
pressured	O
start	O
HRT	B-EVENT
statistically	O
desist	O
NO	O
1	O

@tluckow	B-PER
lol	O
I	O
knew	O
would	O
approve	O

Former	O
advisor	O
Obama	B-PER
Clinton	I-PER
commits	O
suicide	O
months	O
book	O
release	O

ftr	O
icon	O
moody	O
depressed	O
promise	O
i	O
m	O
holding	O
friend	O
make	O
new	O
one	O
think	O
suitable	O
standin	O
besides	O
pink	O

THIS	O
BEAR	O
LOOKS	O
SO	O
DEPRESSED	O
I	O
WANT	O
pictwittercomgrRzizZYDP	O

Even	O
ignore	O
solvency	O
never	O
mind	O
liquidity	O
concerns	O
duration	O
risk	O
sky	O
high	O
yields	O
depressed	O
Fluctuations	O
wealth	O
pays	O
little	O
income	O
wild	O

depressed	O
kay	O
kulangan	O
ang	O
pizza	O
maka	O
bitin	O

Been	O
feeling	O
really	O
depressed	O
lately	O
grateful	O
friends	O
helping	O
get	O

10	O
Do	O
nt	O
wanna	O
cry	O
MGMAVOTE	O
SEVENTEEN	O
@pledis17	O

I	O
m	O
going	O
starting	O
Toy	B-EVENT
Drive	I-EVENT
Christmas	I-EVENT
year	O
Those	O
familieschildren	O
need	O
effected	O
SuicideIf	B-EVENT
anyone	O
interested	O
donating	O
please	O
inbox	O
meThank	O
You	O
Breakthesilence	O
Suicidepreventionawareness	O

Reiss	B-PER
needs	O
starter	O
year	O
AMN	B-EVENT
games	O
middle	O

I	O
m	O
gon	O
na	O
cry	O
bc	O
that	O
s	O
fun	O
fresh	O

Islam	B-PER
ne	O
bhee	O
diya	O
sambit	O
bhai	O
terrorism	O
suicide	O
bombers	O
diye	O
jannat	O
janey	O
ka	O
shortcut	O
rasta	O
radicalization	O
Itna	B-PER
kuch	O
hai	O

okay	O
that	O
s	O
true	O
way	O
got	O
depressed	O
started	O
behavior	O
does	O
nt	O
make	O
happy	O
think	O
better	O
end	O
relationship	O
lil	O
proscons	O
list	O
hard	O
let	O
go	O
sometimes	O
best	O
thing	O

When	O
17	O
mom	O
found	O
suicide	O
notes	O
old	O
notebook	O
exposed	O
first	O
time	O
young	O
adult	O
everything	O
truly	O
changed	O
bruh	O

I	O
watched	O
edge	O
17	O
last	O
night	O
made	O
happy	O
m	O
longer	O
dramatic	O
depressed	O
teen	O
growth	O
able	O
see	O
older	O
sibling	O
baby	O
parents	O
parent	O
siblings	O

Kawhi	B-PER
looks	O
like	O
white	O
walker	O

Never	O
would	O
suicide	O
business	O
Swipingmatching	O
processes	O
drive	O
dopamine	O
users	O
get	O
hooked	O
It	O
like	O
Altria	B-EVENT
voluntarily	O
taking	O
nicotine	O
cigarettes	O
Also	O
is	O
nt	O
best	O
interest	O
remain	O
single	O

Unappreciated	O
made	O
depressed	O
bitch	O
I	O
today	O

Ira	B-PER
Mehlman	I-PER
Democrats	B-EVENT
commit	O
political	O
suicide	O
immigration	O
Fox	B-EVENT
News	I-EVENT

People	O
chatting	O
shit	O
suicide	O
cowards	O
way	O
out	O
Have	O
ever	O
felt	O
close	O
wondered	O
world	O
would	O
better	O
without	O
you	O
watched	O
someone	O
feel	O
powerless	O
anything	O
If	O
answer	O
no	O
STFU	B-PER

@LisaVeronica	O
5more	O
votes	O
pass	O
tawnyheath	O
Voted	O
every20mins	O
2dayscom	O
sartin	O
lagg	O
lol	O
think	O
worth	O
xoxlt3	O

Gngngn	B-LOC
Tokyo	I-LOC
se	O
suicide	O
gngngn	O
vos	O
vieux	O
spoil	O
de	I-LOC
merde	O
CEST	O
FAUX	O
Hte	B-LOC
voir	I-LOC
la	I-LOC
suite	O

Ah	O
Mondays	O
The	O
start	O
great	O
week	O
I	O
hope	O

A	O
depressed	O
generation	O
hiding	O
behind	O
excessive	O
alcohol	O
consumptionpartyingmemes	O
jokesBut	B-EVENT
deep	O
inside	O
alot	O
feel	O
dead	O
empty	O
yet	O
see	O
many	O
fake	O
smiles	O

What	O
depressed	O
boy	O
say	O
broke	O
pencil	O
There	O
point	O

I	O
Do	O
nt	O
Fit	O
Stereotype	O
Depressed	O
Person	O
Madeline	B-PER
Riddle	I-PER
via	O
@TheMightySite	O
@MindsCountFndn	O
depression	O

@OsasCruz	B-PER
@TheHauteNurse	I-PER
@DrOlufunmilayo	I-PER
@Healthertainer	O
@Deekachymd	B-PER
@EmiNiTybaba	I-PER
@trendingmedic	O
@louwhiz	B-PER
@aninomso	I-PER
@JosephineAvid	I-PER
Jonathan	I-PER
LP	O
Andrew	B-PER
LF	I-PER
2016	O
Depression	O
children	O
adolescents	O
University	B-EVENT
Kansas	I-EVENT
Clinical	I-EVENT
Child	I-EVENT
Psychology	I-EVENT
Program	I-EVENT

shit	O
really	O
made	O
depressed	O
af	O

I	O
Lasik	O
20	O
years	O
ago	O
m	O
still	O
depressed	O
time	O
Explain	O
yourself	O
Grimes	B-PER

depressed	O
bitch	O
dumbass	O
thot	O

Lack	O
sleep	O
making	O
depressed	O
lol	O

They	O
coming	O
G	O
word	O

Female	O
suicide	O
bomber	O
kills	O
eight	O
northwest	O
Pakistan	B-LOC
The	O
blast	O
damaged	O
emergency	O
ward	O
hospital	O
forced	O
wounded	O
transferred	O
cities	O

Si	O
elle	O
est	O
dans	O
le	O
domaine	O
de	O
lart	O
cest	O
tranquille	O
mais	O
sinon	O
je	O
trouve	O
du	O
suicide	O
faire	O
a	O

post	O
vacation	O
depression	O
real	O

@JMartorelli	B-PER
Yes	O
maam	O
I	O
will	O
He	O
also	O
brings	O
wonderful	O
people	O
life	O
remind	O
me	O
Thanks	O
Have	O
blessed	O
day	O

The	O
highlight	O
weeks	O
marrshow	O
Chancellor	O
Exchequer	O
Philip	B-PER
Hammond	I-PER
MP	O
committing	O
political	O
suicide	O
live	O
nation	O
Good	O
riddance	O
bad	O
rubbish	O

I	O
wrote	O
note	O
went	O
sleep	O
mom	O
came	O
home	O
thought	O
suicide	O

Breaks	O
heart	O
whilst	O
simultaneously	O
making	O
angry	O
policy	O
mess	O
leads	O
terrible	O
loss	O
life	O
publicpolicy	O
austerity	O
suicide	O
UniversalCredit	O
Single	O
dad	O
461	O
killed	O
3	O
week	O
wait	O
Universal	B-EVENT
Credit	I-EVENT

@misspaola	O
I	O
wish	O
u	O
talkin	O
bout	O
ME	O

Dr	O
Kent	B-PER
answers	O
question	O
regarding	O
suicide	O
caregiver	O
support	O
meeting	O
chronic	O
pain	O
caregivers	O

fatezero	O
prequel	O
spoils	O
backstory	O
stay	O
night	O
zero	O
i	O
d	O
still	O
watch	O
first	O
cuz	O
right	O
way	O
better	O

But	O
I	O
say	O
sincerely	O
try	O
connect	O
anyone	O
tweet	O
with	O
Because	O
want	O
community	O
alone	O
help	O
live	O

Recommend	O
@dcjc	B-EVENT
Tea	I-EVENT
Party	I-EVENT
20	O

I	O
received	O
1000	O
donation	O
supporting	O
American	B-EVENT
Foundation	I-EVENT
Suicide	I-EVENT
Prevention	I-EVENT

Inhome	O
nurse	O
came	O
yesterday	O
months	O
seeing	O
due	O
BUSY	O
AF	O
Did	O
year	O
PP	O
testing	O
PPD	O
PPA	O
anxiety	O
gone	O
last	O
test	O
I	O
m	O
showing	O
depressed	O
Super	O
awesome	O
She	O
said	O
resilient	O
do	O
nt	O
feel	O
it	O
pictwittercomWkJyo8suRc	O

C	O
faux	O
elle	O
dit	O
nimp	O
il	O
se	O
suicide	O
pas	O

I	O
never	O
realized	O
depressed	O
last	O
two	O
months	O
Life	O
amazing	O
people	O
Fuck	O
depression	O

Ill	O
never	O
understand	O
people	O
brag	O
hospital	O
due	O
suicide	O
attempts	O
promote	O
stay	O
like	O
fashion	O
showI	O
get	O
posting	O
social	O
media	O
I	O
it	O

Its	O
late	O
depressed	O
dude	O

watched	O
first	O
30min	O
dad	O
long	O
ass	O
time	O
ago	O
left	O
room	O
currently	O
pretend	O
does	O
nt	O
exist	O

Substance	O
abuse	O
suicide	O
crushing	O
millennials	O
Financial	O
stress	O
affordability	O
housing	O
creating	O
massive	O
mental	O
health	O
issues	O
This	O
longer	O
genetics	O
its	O
societal	O
problem	O
well	O
@hillarytweets	O

Some	O
best	O
school	O
chums	O
Japanese	B-EVENT
Had	O
atomic	O
bombs	O
dropped	O
Hiroshima	B-LOC
Nagasaki	I-LOC
end	O
WW2	O
friends	O
father	O
would	O
ve	O
flown	O
Kamikaze	B-EVENT
fighter	O
plane	O
suicide	O
mission	O
Allied	B-LOC
Pacific	I-LOC
fleets	O
Hiroshi	B-PER
here	O
We	O
still	O
see	O
other	O

Du	O
coup	O
cest	O
quoi	O
exactement	O
qui	O
te	O
dgotes	O
dans	O
estu	O
Alaska	B-LOC
Je	O
lai	O
lu	O
rcemment	O
et	O
javoue	O
quil	O
ma	O
p	O
tw	O
suicide	O
quand	O
je	O
javais	O
une	O
certaine	O
passion	O
pour	O
le	O
fin	O
a	O
fascinait	O
jidalisa	O

Allah	B-PER
Akbar	I-PER
battle	O
cry	O
Islamic	B-EVENT
jihadist	O
commit	O
mass	O
suicide	O
You	O
obviously	O
find	O
Google	B-PER
@IlhanMN	I-PER
hates	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
America	I-LOC
She	O
supports	O
ISIS	B-EVENT
entire	O
Jewish	B-EVENT
nation	O
allies	O
WHY	O
allowed	O
TRUTH	O
MUST	O
BE	O
TOLD	O
MAGA	O

Done	O
rest	O
week	O
Going	O
back	O
depressed	O

35	O
year	O
old	O
woman	O
blasts	O
suicide	O
boys	O
every	O
sunday	O
morning	O

Evans	B-PER
shoves	O
Rae	B-PER
steps	O
Cameron	B-PER
comes	O
ropes	O
suicide	O
dive	O
esque	O
move	O
Both	O
women	O
rises	O
ring	O
takes	O
another	O
table	O
out	O
She	O
sets	O
outside	O
climbs	O
apron	O
slaps	O
her	O
pictwittercom4XN18xHPpo	O

Brought	O
home	O
2	O
kennewickrescue	O
Eskimo	B-EVENT
pups	O
foster	O
Seattle	B-EVENT
Humanecute	I-EVENT
overloadcould	O
use	O
ShamWow	B-EVENT
puppy	O
diapers	O
however	O

You	O
keep	O
saying	O
depressed	O
honestly	O
sounds	O
like	O
you	O
re	O
covering	O
bullshit	O
feel	O
better	O
yourself	O
The	O
real	O
work	O
internal	O
Might	O
want	O
check	O
out	O
Good	O
day	O
sir	O

An	O
83yearold	O
woman	O
killed	O
89yearold	O
man	O
critical	O
condition	O
authorities	O
described	O
possible	O
murderattempted	O
suicide	O
unincorporated	O
South	B-LOC
Whittier	I-LOC

I	O
m	O
depressed	O
want	O
raid	O
Area	B-EVENT
51	O

@stillsoyoungxo	O
soooo	O
I	O
bother	O
look	O
tom	O
imma	O
wait	O
till	O
comes	O
Tuesday	O
wc	O
m	O
really	O
excited	O

Ca	O
nt	O
wait	O
get	O
shitfaced	O
Neyland	B-PER
fall	O

I	O
m	O
suicidal	O
well	O
thought	O
committing	O
suicide	O
never	O
really	O
want	O
it	O
Stay	O
strong	O
whatever	O
ure	O
facing	O
sis	O

It	O
means	O
sadistic	O
brutes	O
commit	O
suicide	O
provided	O
unarmed	O
victims	O
weekly	O
biweekly	O
paycheck	O
pictwittercomIHLupxoj7X	O

You	O
think	O
Serge	B-PER
level	O
Russ	B-PER
KD	I-PER

hard	O
leave	O
realize	O
i	O
m	O
narcissistic	O
maniac	O

currently	O
depressed	O
remembered	O
gf	O
liked	O
girls	O

First	O
date	O
idea	O
commit	O
suicide	O

Approximately	O
22	O
Veterans	O
day	O
commit	O
suicide	O
Would	O
least	O
Twitter	O
friends	O
please	O
copy	O
tweet	O
Not	O
RT	O
Crisis	O
Line	O
8002738255	O
Thank	O
@TheFaulkLine	O

Suicide	O
rates	O
among	O
physicians	O
nurses	O
much	O
higher	O
general	O
population	O
BehavioralHealthIntegration	B-EVENT
SuicidePrevention	I-EVENT
seriously	O
needed	O
SharedFacts	B-EVENT

Il	O
sest	O
suicid	O
car	O
pensant	O
trouver	O
une	O
terre	O
daccueil	O
un	O
espoir	O
denfin	O
mieux	O
vivre	O
il	O
dcouvert	O
la	O
cruaut	O
de	O
ltre	O
humain	O
dans	O
toute	O
son	O
horreur	O
La	B-LOC
France	I-LOC
tait	O
loin	O
des	O
promesses	O
quon	O
lui	O
avait	O
vant	O
ParisestUneFte	B-PER

Th	O
thing	O
helped	O
ironically	O
forgiving	O
narcissist	O
ex	O
telling	O
forgave	O

I	O
100	O
push	O
ups	O
sit	O
15	O
min	O
ab	O
workout	O
run	O
3	O
miles	O
day	O
Even	O
work	O
go	O
hang	O
meeting	O
intoxicated	O
blowed	O
depressed	O
12	O
degrees	O
yes	O
ask	O
friends	O
90	O
whatever	O
pussy	O
excuse	O
come	O
with	O

Bas	B-PER
ek	I-PER
Sanam	I-PER
chahiye	O
aashiqui	O
ke	O
lie	O

1	O
Deadpool	O
2Deadpool2	O
3	O
avengers	O
infinity	O
war	O
4	O
endgame	O
5	O
suicide	O
squad	O

Is	O
going	O
lunch	O
hubby	O

You	O
got	O
I	O
believe	O
smarter	O

I	O
swear	O
one	O
sexiest	O
thing	O
guy	O
ask	O
go	O
date	O
